<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044049817315_0392" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="C.C.D. La." jurisdiction="United States">United States Circuit Court for the District of Louisiana</court>
          <name abbreviation="Johnson v. Jumel">JOHNSON v. JUMEL</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 7,392</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">13 F. Cas. 755</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">3 Woods, 69</citation>
          <decisiondate>1877-04</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-10T00:25:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:27:33Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:41:28Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00379_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="cad492f401bef5335182bf264e8ca825" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="77412">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00379_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00379_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="9c8c5a7c6e9e51ceeb6717711d1c33c9" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="19708">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00379_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00380_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="f61cf0eb6ccbe60f478d7054eaa9fb54" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="112972">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00380_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00380_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="22951bdff308f1b8bf61457a6c9d46c4" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="28650">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00380_1.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00379_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="306ff54c9d422195ab272371e5932bcc" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2974426">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00379_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00379_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="a7b185bd91df37f553a0f5757313bdae" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="1366775">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00379_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00380_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="11b56c98b2f659dd59d2ac9e2c0b9674" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3820752">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00380_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00380_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="59125ddfc948cd305b1782dfdde14197" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="1728404">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00380_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00379_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="9a72517968032213d7e291e73c9358a2" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="165464">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00379_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00379_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="834a70bdffa0806e3bb5a727a90ca4cd" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="32150">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00379_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00380_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="8aa52dcd3a1e796233a599193ca9add9" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="248111">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00380_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00380_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="4e250f67736af0c7bbd408142ce0239d" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="57456">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00380_1.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0392" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="758" firstpage="755">
              <court pgmap="757" id="AzA9">Circuit Court, D. Louisiana.</court>
              <docketnumber pgmap="757" id="b757-7">Case No. 7,392.</docketnumber>
              <citation pgmap="757" id="A10s">[3 Woods, 69.] <footnotemark>1</footnotemark>
              </citation>
              <parties pgmap="757" id="Aazf">JOHNSON v. JUMEL.</parties>
              <decisiondate pgmap="757" id="ABzL">April Term, 1877.</decisiondate>
              <attorneys pgmap="758" id="b758-5">John Ray and H. J. Campbell, for peti­tioner.</attorneys>
              <attorneys pgmap="758" id="b758-6">J. C. Egan, Asst. Atty. Gen., of Louisiana, for defendant.</attorneys>
              <footnote label="1">
                <p pgmap="757" id="b757-15">1 [Reported by Hon. William B. Woods. Cir­cuit Judge, and here reprinted by permission.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author pgmap="758" id="b758-7">BILLINGS, District Judge.</author>
                <p pgmap="758(103) 759(513)" id="A8W">The sub­stance of the petition is, that the petitioner was a candidate for the office of auditor of public accounts of the state of Louisiana at the election held on the 7th of November, 1870; that voters in various parishes who were entitled to vote were denied the right to vote at said election on account of race, color or previous condition of servitude, to the number of 10,000; that the officers known as the returning board were by law vested with complete jurisdiction to correct the errors and wrongs which had then arisen in these various parishes, and that they did make suck corrections and returned the pe­titioner elected to said office; that he was duly commissioned and entered upon and enjoyed the possession of said office for the period of four months, when he was forci­bly ejected by a government established by domestic violence, insurrection and revolu­tion; that the claim or pretense upon which they have ousted him from his office is that the petitioner was not elected, and that the votes which were cast in the parishes in which the right to vote was denied should be counted against him. According to the allegations of this petition, petitioner has not been defeated or deprived of any election; but, on the contrary, was elected and was declared elected by the competent state au­thority, was duly commissioned, and retain­ed his office for the period of four months. True, there had been an unsuccessful at­tempt to defeat petitioner by an exclusion of votes in the various parishes, but he avers that that attempt had been completely thwarted by the tribunal which had the final revision of the returns. Every vote that was cast, or was attempted to be cast, for the petitioner and against the defend­ant had, according to his allegations, full effect given to it, and was finally and ef­fectively. counted by the board of returning officers. He has thus, so far from having been defeated, succeeded in an election, and instead of having been deprived of an elec­tion, has secured an election, and four months after the election has been deprived, not of an election, but of an office, to which he has been elected and authoritatively de­clared elected; and he has been deprived of an office, not by the exclusion of votes for any reason, but'by force, which took the proportions of a revolution. The statute un­der which jurisdiction is given to the cir­cuit court-is set forth in the act of May 31, 1S70. § 23 (10 Stat. 146; Rev. St. § 2010), as follows: “That whenever any person shall be defeated or deprived of his election to any office, except elector of president or vice-­president, representative or delegate in con­gress, or member of a state legislature, by reason of the denial to any citizen or citi­zens, who shall offer to vote, of the right to vote, on account of race, color or previous condition o'f servitude, his right to hold and enjoy such office and the emoluments there­of shall not be impaired by such denial, and such person may bring any appropriate-suit or proceeding to recover possession of such office, and in cases where it shall appear that the sole question touching the title to such office arises out of the denial of the right to vote to citizens who so offered to vote on account of race, color or previous condition of servitude, such suit or proceed­ing may be -instituted in the circuit or dis­trict court of the United States of the cir­cuit or district in which such person re­sides.’-</p>
                <p pgmap="759" id="b759-4">From this it appears that the cases in which the circuit courts have jurisdiction of such actions as this are limited to those in which it shall appear that the sole question-­touching the title to such office arises out of the denial of the right to vote, to citizens who so offered to vote, on account of race, color or. previous condition of servitude, and that the jurisdiction of the circuit court is only given to the extent of determining the rights of the parties to such office, by reason of the denial of the right guaranteed by the fifteenth article of amendment to the con­stitution of the United States.</p>
                <p pgmap="759" id="b759-6">There is no doubt that the scope of this statute, under the limitations which it con­tains, extends from the first act required to be done in the matter of an election down to and including the final and effective can­vass of the votes by the officers who are charged with the duty of determining and certifying the result. If, in any of the stages of an election, in registration, in the re­ceipt of votes, the certificates of the votes by the local authorities, or the final canvass of the votes or the certificate of election by the returning board, there had been such a de­nial of the right to vote as the statute con­templates, on account of race, color or pre­vious condition of servitude, that matter this court would have had, under the act of con­gress. jurisdiction to inquire into and adju­dicate upon, and it could determine the rights of the parties to office, so far as they depended upon the denial of the right guar­anteed by the fifteenth article of the amend­ment to the constitution. But the jurisdic­tion of the court begins and ends with the denial of the right to vote.</p>
                <p pgmap="759(234) 760(134)" id="b759-7">If,- therefore, there is a preliminary exclu­sion or an exclusion at the polls, and that er­ror is corrected by the proper state authori­ties and there is no final and effective exclu­sion of votes or discrimination, or if after an election has been held and the result reached and declared without discrimination or ex­clusion from any cause, the person elected is deprived of his office, then the statute closes the doorway upon the jurisdiction of this court. The defeat of a candidate at an election or his deprivation of an election, must be accomplished by the machinery of the election, in one of its stages, and must be contained in the result. If the election terminates in the success of the candidate, the essential ground of jurisdiction on the part of this court is wanting. The wrong which the petitioner sets forth is, that after being elected and installed, he has not been retained in the office. The object of the statute was to secure an election free from all possible exclusion on any of the specific grounds. It secured this object by giving to this court jurisdiction to correct, through this form of action, such exclusion effected .by the machinery or practices attending the elec­tion. When, as the petitioner alleges, all this has been accomplished, and the very result aimed at by the statute has been worked out and declared, the statute gives no jurisdic­tion over a cause merely to enable a party to physically retain or regain’ an office to which he had a title established by an elec­tion, and from which he has subsequently been ejected. • In this case the question by virtue of which the court could take jurisdic­tion, and by the terms of the statute it must be unmixed with any other question, is not presented. According to the allegations of the petition, the election had been completed for four months when the ouster took place, and his loss of office is as independent of any denial of the right to vote as if he had been ejected by a government set up by a foreign invasion, claiming authority by the right of conquest.</p>
                <p pgmap="760" id="b760-3">Let the demurrer be sustained and the pe­tition dismissed.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="757" ORDERLABEL="755" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00379_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00379_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00379_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_757.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00379_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="758" ORDERLABEL="756" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00379_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00379_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00379_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_758.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00379_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="759" ORDERLABEL="757" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00380_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00380_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00380_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_759.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00380_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="760" ORDERLABEL="758" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00380_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00380_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00380_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_760.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00380_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b759-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0392"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_759.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00380_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_759.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00380_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AzA9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0392"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_757.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00379_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b759-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0392"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_759.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00380_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b757-15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0392"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_757.18" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00379_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b757-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0392"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_757.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00379_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b758-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0392"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_758.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00379_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b760-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0392"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_760.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00380_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="ABzL" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0392"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_757.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00379_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Aazf" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0392"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_757.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00379_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="A8W" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0392"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_758.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00379_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_758.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00379_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_759.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00380_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b759-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0392"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_759.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00380_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_760.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00380_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="A10s" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0392"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_757.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00379_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b758-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0392"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_758.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00379_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b758-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0392"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_758.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00379_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
