<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044049817315_0515" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="W.D.N.C." jurisdiction="United States">United States District Court for the Western District of North Carolina</court>
          <name abbreviation="In re Jordan">In re JORDAN</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 7,514</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">13 F. Cas. 1079</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">8 N. B. R. 180; 5 Leg. Op. 169; 30 Leg. Int. 296</citation>
          <decisiondate>1873-06</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-10T00:25:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:27:33Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:41:29Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00541_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="14769ecdab21a3224b0dc0c356753c78" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="55104">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00541_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00541_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="cceb4a569e2d1e4775f9f369c6e8a3f3" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="117372">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00541_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00542_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="740f9c501f3929c59c10dcd913cb100a" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="116798">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00542_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00542_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="d9418f79dd147c13d989aad565bcafb8" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="83766">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00542_1.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00541_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="dd6beb4825503dc9a7c45fa8be1a193b" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2425006">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00541_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00541_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="aafb41723e8c4df1083b274ef39ba3ad" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3825367">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00541_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00542_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="ca1f74c860b2d9f6b0452a88a9fd1393" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3831806">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00542_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00542_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="5ad74349cf7713773831dc1173336c7a" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3013071">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00542_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00541_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="32ae47f6191aa2dfdf9cdbfbb1fcb211" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="112964">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00541_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00541_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="f960b07ef74130cc6cb2cc4415e16bc4" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="241411">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00541_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00542_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="531bbbaa657a4277a0a33c9c47ed4fa9" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="244041">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00542_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00542_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="1caae9ade95eea05cc6ffdecf585e2ea" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="168308">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00542_1.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0515" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="1082" firstpage="1079">
              <court pgmap="1081" id="b1081-8">District Court, W. D. North Carolina.</court>
              <docketnumber pgmap="1081" id="b1081-5">Case No. 7,514.</docketnumber>
              <citation pgmap="1081" id="b1081-7">[8 N. B. R. 180;<footnotemark>1</footnotemark> 5 Leg. Op. 169; 30 Leg. Int. 296.]</citation>
              <parties pgmap="1081" id="AKJ1">In re JORDAN.</parties>
              <decisiondate pgmap="1081" id="Axxc">June, 1873.</decisiondate>
              <attorneys pgmap="1081" id="b1081-19">Graves &amp; Hyman, for bankrupt</attorneys>
              <attorneys pgmap="1081" id="b1081-20">Mr. Pickins, for creditors.</attorneys>
              <footnote label="1">
                <p pgmap="1081" id="b1081-15">1 [Reprinted from 8 N. B. R. 180, by permis­sion.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author pgmap="1081" id="b1081-21">DICK, District Judge.</author>
                <p pgmap="1081(153) 1082(249)" id="AiIH">I concur in the able and well prepared opinion of the register up­on the several questions which have been certified to this court for adjudication. In Re Beekerford [Case No. 1,209], the United States circuit court of Missouri decided that, “the provisions of section fourteen of the bankrupt act adopting the exemptions in favor of exe­cution debtors established by the laws of the several states does not destroy the uniformity of the bankrupt act, nor violate any of the provisions of the federal constitution.” The question decided was directly presented for adjudication, and the opinion of Miller and Krekel, JJ., is positive and forcible,. and seems to .have been well considered. I feel safe in relying upon any legal decision of Mr. Justice Miller, as there is no judge in any country whose judicial opinions are entitled to more consideration or greater weight of authority. The amendment of June 8, 1872 [17 Stat. 334], floes not materially vary the question of uniformity decided in lie Becker-­ford [supra], as it only changes the date when the state exemptions are adopted; and the act of March 3, 1873, declares the true in­tent and meaning of the act of June S, 1S72, and re-enacts it with some alterations renuer-­ed necessary by the circumstances of the times. The general policy and purpose of bankrupt laws is to make an equal distribu­tion of the effects of an insolvent debtor among all of his creditors, and then dis­charge an honest debtor from all prior debts. Before the adoption of the federal constitu­tion, each state possessed the general powers of sovereignty and could pass bankrupt laws to operate upon its own citizens, but could not I affectthe rights of the citizens of other states. As it was easy to foresee that there would be many business transactions and much com­mercial intercourse between the citizens of the several states which would necessarily produce considerable individual indebtedness, which might result in extensive financial em­barrassments. it was obvious to the framers of the federal constitution that the benefits of a Avise, humane and general system of bank­ruptcy. which might, under certain exigen­cies, become necessary to promote the happi­ness and commercial prosperity of the na­tion. could only be effectually established by the federal government adopted by the peo­ple of the several states for general and na­tional puiposes.</p>
                <p pgmap="1082" id="b1082-4">To provide for any emergency that might arise for a general bankrupt law, the consti­tution vested the necessary sovereign power in congress with no other limitation than that the laAvs upon such subject should be uniform in thrtr operation among the several states. The iniformity required is as to the general policy and operation of such laws; as, for in­stance, that the common law right Avhich a debtor has to prefer one creditor over an­other shall be taken away and his property be equally distributed among all of his cred­itors; that bankrupts who make an honest surrender of their effects shall be discharged from all prior debts; that all questions relat­ing to bankrupts, their estates and creditors, shall be adjusted and administered in the same courts, and by the same forms and modes of proceeding. These general pur­poses of bankruptcy are certainly provided for in the present bankrupt act, and are ev­erywhere administered with uniformity in the federal courts; and this is the extent of the uniformity required by the constitution to make such laws operate equally, justly, effectually and beneficially in every part of the nation. The bankrupt act, in some mi­nor particulars, must necessarily operate dif­ferently in the different states. Thus, the bankrupt law regards as valid the legal and equitable liens existing by law in the several states; and as the nature, force and effect of such liens are dependent upon local laAvs, they will, in.some respects, be different in the different states. The English doctrine of the equitable lien of a vendor or purchaser of real estate is recognized in some of our states, and not in others; and where it ex­ists it is enforced in the courts of bankrupt­cy. A bankrupt court adjusts the rights of creditors, and administers the effects of a bankrupt, subject to the charges, whether by way of lien or exemption, which are created by the laws of the states in which such court is held or the property to be disposed of is situated. This rule was adopted to make the bankrupt law as uniform as possi­ble among the states, by recognizing local laws and thus preserving the harmony and spirit of comity which should always exist between the federal and state governments. This rule does not violate, but carries into effect, that provision of the constitution which requires all national bankrupt laws to be uniform in their operation among the sev­eral states.</p>
                <p pgmap="1082(358) 1083(430)" id="b1082-6">The principles involved in the second ques­tion certified by the register are too obvious and too well settled by numerous adjudica­tions to need any further discussion. Con­gress certainly has the plenary and. para­mount power, save the restriction above con­sidered, to pass bankrupt laws which will not only impair the obligation of contracts, but entirely discharge the debtor from such obligation, no matter when or where con­tracted. Congress, also, has the poAver in establishing a uniform system of bankruptcy to do away with the effects of liens created by the judgments of any court. If a judg­ment can be discharged by a bankrupt law there is no reason why a lien Avhich is an incident to a judgment, cannot also be dis­charged. A lien by judgment does not create any vested right in the property subject to such lien which the constitution protects from legislative encroachment. It is neither a right in, nor to, such property, but simply a charge imposed thereon by statute. It is a part of the remedy which the local law gives a creditor in the collection of his debts, and a particular remedy is not a vested right. As a general, rule every state has complete control over the remedies which it shall af­ford to parties in its courts. Horton v. Mc­Call, 66 N. C. 159; Ladd v. Adams, Id. 164; Cooley, Const. Lim. 358, 361. The extent, force and effect of a lien created by a state statute must depend upon the interpretation given such statute by the highest court of the state. We have seen, in the cases above cited, that in this state a judgment lien is not a vested right. As a remedy it may be modified by the legislature, and any change that does not virtually destroy the remedy does not impair the obligation of existing contracts. The homestead laws of this state do not abolish judgment liens, but merely postpone the time of their enforcement. This modification of a legal remedy may well be regarded as reasonable by a court of justice which takes into consideration the anoma-­Ions condition of things existing when the modification was made, and that it was prompted by a wise and humane policy which must necessarily result in the general public good. While the states are prohibited by the constitution from impairing the obligation of contracts — either directly, or by virtually abolishing existing remedies — no such inhibi­tion is imposed upon congress. The power expressly conferred upon congress to enact uniform bankrupt laws, is necessarily an express power to do away entirely with con­tracts, as such a result is the very object and essence of bankrupt laws. But it is insisted that while congress may have this paramount power over contracts, it exceeds its authority in enacting that state exemptions shall be “valid against liens by judgment or decree of any state courts.” This is equivalent to saying that the contract may be impaired, but the remedy must not be interfered with— the principal may be destroyed, but the in­cident is protected against legislative action. There is nothing in the nature of liens why they should be thus specially protected, as they are not vested rights; but there are strong reasons why they should not be recog­nized and enforced by bankrupt laws. The enforcement of liens is certainly contrary to the policy of a general system of bankruptcy, the object of which is to distribute the es­tate of an insolvent debtor among all of his creditors, upon the principle that equality is equity. Liens, upon general principles, cer­tainly deserve no special favor and protec­tion in bankrupt laws. The bankrupt act, before the amendment of March 3, 1873, in express terms avoids liens valid under state laws and created by the levy of an attach­ment within four months before the com­mencement of proceedings in bankruptcy, and this action of congress is generally con­ceded to be constitutional. Congress has even interfered with vested rights, for by the thirty-fifth section of the bankrupt act, assignments and conveyances made under certain circumstances are avoided, although such assignments and conveyances are valid at common law and under the laws of the state, and the parties have acquired a com­plete title and possession of the- property con­veyed. I have a very decided opinion that congress did not exceed the limits of its con­stitutional powers in enacting the act of March 3, 1S73. I also think that congress, under its general powers over the subject of bankruptcy, could avoid all liens, whether existing by statute, by usage, by express con­tract, or at common law.</p>
                <p pgmap="1083" id="b1083-4">The case of Gunn v. Barry [15 Wall. (82 U. S.) 610], recently decided in the supreme court of the United States, has been called to my attention in the argument, and is wor­thy of my most careful consideration, as it is an exposition of the law by the supreme judicial tribunal of the nation. The opinion is read with great interest, both by lawyers and laymen, in every section of the country, and the decision may result in serious con­sequences to many of our people. The ques­tions of law involved have been frequently discussed by able counsel, and have been decided differently in many of the supreme courts of the states. The opinion of Mr. Justice Swayne is not elaborate, and the ques­tions presented are not as fully considered as I had supposed they would have been, on account of their importance and general pub­lic interest, when the homes of tens of thou­sands of our unfortunate citizens inay de­pend upon the decision, and when the action of so many state conventions, legislatures and supreme courts may be overruled. The abstract principles decided in Gunn v. Barry­, supra, are announced in almost the same j language to be good law in Hill v. Kesle­r [63 N. C. 437], in the supreme court of this ! state, and the apparently different decisions : in the two cases may be easily reconciled. ; The decision in Gunn v. Barry would have i been made in Hill v. Kesler under a similar i state of facts. The exemption law of Georgia I gave a homestead absolutely to the debtor, ■ and deprived the creditor of all remedy. I­n Hill v. Kesler, it is conceded that if a state • abolish or injuriously change the legal rem­edy existing at the time a contract is made, such action would be void, as in violation of the constitution of the United States. In both the cases which we are considering it is agreed that a state may change legal rem­edies provided such change does not impair a substantial right. Such changes are usually made to meet some new condition of things, and are influenced by reasons of public pol­icy. The legislature is the proper body to consider and act upon questions of public policy, and the legislative will, upon such subjects, ought to be regarded as the law of the land by the judiciary, unless it is mani--­festly in violation of the constitution. Im­prisonment for debt was a X’emedy in this state for the enforcement of contracts. .The legislature thought this remedy a relic of barbarism and ought not to exist in a free, enlightened and Christian state, and such remedy was abolished. The constitutionality of this legislative action would be sustained in any court, although it impaired existing and substantial rights. The enlightened le­gal principles that control this question will certainly sustain the homestead laws of this state, upon the grounds of humanity and a wise public policy. These laws do not destroy vested rights, disturb specific liens, or abolish any legal remedy, but only postpone the time of their enforcement. I do not regard "the case of Hill v. Kesler as overruled by Gunn v. Barry, but I will not consider the question further, as it belongs more appropriately to another tribunal.</p>
                <p pgmap="1083(40) 1084(580)" id="b1083-9">The question presented for my determina­tion is — how far does the case of Gunn v. Barry affect the homestead rights of insol­vent debtors in a court of bankruptcy. In that case it is decided thus: “Congress can­not, by authorization or ratification, give the slightest effect to a state law or constitution in conflict with the constitution of the United States. This instrument is above and be­yond the power of congress and the states, and is alike obligatory upon both.” I admit the soundness of the legal principle so clearly and forcibly expressed. A state statute that is in violation of the constitution of the Unit­ed States is absolutely void, and no power in the government can give it vitality or au­thorize, its operation as a state law. But there are some subjects upon which a state can­not rightfully legislate, and yet congress may do so under the constitution. A state can­not coin money, emit bills of credit, make anything but gold and silver coin a tender in payment of debts, &amp;e., but congress can pass laws upon such subjects, and in legislat­ing may adopt and enact the very principles and terms of an unconstitutional state law. If this state had adopted the present bank­rupt law it would have been unconstitutional, as it impairs the obligation of contracts and affects the rights of the citizens of other states. Congress, however, could adopt the very language and principles of such state, law and enact it as a national law, and such action would be constitutional; as it would constitute a system of bankruptcy uniform among the states. The act of March 3, 1S73, does not profess, by “authorization or rati­fication,” to make valid, state exemption laws which are unconstitutional, but adopts the principles of such laws and to a certain ex­tent makes them a part of the general bank­rupt law. The act says in express terms "that the exemptions allowed the bankrupt shall be the amourt allowed by the constitu­tion and laws of each state respectively as existing in the year eighteen hundred and seventy-one.” It will be observed that the act of March 3,1873, makes a material change in re-enacting the act of June 8,1872, by sub­stituting the words “as existing” in place of the words “in force.” It is manifest from the terms of the act of March 3, 1873, that the object of congress was to do away with a difficulty that arose under the act of June S, 1872, by some state court declaring that exemptions to debtors in state constitutions and laws were not in force as to antecedent debts; as such part of such laws were in conflict with the constitution of the United States. Congress therefore expressly declared that such state exemptions should be valid against antecedent debts; and ex industria substituted the words “as existing” in place of'the words “in force,” and intended that the exemptions allowed under the bankrupt law should be the amount designated in the constitution and laws of the states respec­tively in existence in the year 1S71, even if such laws, as state laws, should be declared to be unconstitutional by the courts. As the power of congress over the subject of bank­ruptcy is plenary and paramount, and as its intent is so clearly manifested by its action, we are of the opinion that the act of March 3r 1873, is constitutional and must be adminis­tered in the bankrupt courts according to its true intent and meaning unmistakably ex­pressed in its language. The exceptions to the report of the assignee are disallowed, and said report is in all things confirmed.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="1081" ORDERLABEL="1079" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00541_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00541_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00541_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_1081.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00541_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="1082" ORDERLABEL="1080" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00541_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00541_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00541_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_1082.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00541_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="1083" ORDERLABEL="1081" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00542_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00542_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00542_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_1083.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00542_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="1084" ORDERLABEL="1082" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00542_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00542_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00542_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_1084.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00542_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1081-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0515"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1081.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00541_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AiIH" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0515"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1081.26" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00541_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1081.27" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00541_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1082.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00541_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1081-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0515"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1081.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00541_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1082-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0515"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1082.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00541_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1083.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00542_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1082-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0515"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1082.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00541_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1082.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00541_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1081-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0515"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1081.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00541_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AKJ1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0515"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1081.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00541_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1081-21" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0515"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1081.25" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00541_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1081-19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0515"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1081.23" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00541_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Axxc" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0515"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1081.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00541_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1081.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00541_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1081-20" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0515"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1081.24" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00541_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1083-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0515"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1083.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00542_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1084.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00542_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1084.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00542_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1083-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0515"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1083.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00542_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1083.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00542_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1081-15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0515"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1081.19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00541_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
