<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044046873683_0408" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="C.C.S.D. Ala." jurisdiction="United States">United States Circuit Court for the Southern District of Alabama</court>
          <name abbreviation="Eslava v. Mazange’s Adm’r">ESLAVA v. MAZANGE’S ADM’R et al.</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 4,527</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">8 F. Cas. 780</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">1 Woods, 623; 3 Chi. Leg. News, 297</citation>
          <decisiondate>1871-04</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-12T19:40:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-26T10:42:09Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-26T10:56:34Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00391_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="dfe37368dbff2add93bf753caefaf17d" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="33568">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00391_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00392_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="104fcb566fc25e2f846bae5a6475e7ab" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="111178">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00392_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00392_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="1ca83c7c6abd5e9b0a123c589a56afa2" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="95006">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00392_1.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00391_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="09dca1e6b1bd52467a52c648eb4a8a4e" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2078392">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00391_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00392_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="56cd827cca2adbbaa5cbb5a672e741f7" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3808785">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00392_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00392_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="dbdc7ca8ce0a8f1196e3eed334ba5661" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3506767">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00392_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00391_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="4cfe047feb3cfdcb563ea5b6ccdb7127" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="64458">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00391_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00392_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="3c718e2bb6554a5edb5df87db9e98723" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="248004">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00392_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00392_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="c34dfacf7345837d87646bf2754242ba" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="202684">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00392_1.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0408" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="782" firstpage="780">
              <court id="b782-24" pgmap="782">Circuit Court, S. D. Alabama.</court>
              <docketnumber id="b782-21" pgmap="782">Case No. 4,527.</docketnumber>
              <citation id="b782-23" pgmap="782">[1 Woods, 623;<footnotemark>1</footnotemark> 3 Chi. Leg. News, 297.]</citation>
              <parties id="b782-22" pgmap="782">ESLAVA v. MAZANGE’S ADM’R et al.</parties>
              <decisiondate id="AGqs" pgmap="782">April Term, 1871.</decisiondate>
              <attorneys id="b783-3" pgmap="783">Alex. McKinstry, for complainant</attorneys>
              <attorneys id="b783-4" pgmap="783">Geo. N. Stewart J- Little Smith, A. K. Manning, and Percy Walker, for defendants.</attorneys>
              <footnote label="1">
                <p id="b782-36" pgmap="782">1 [Reported by Hon. William B. Woods, Cir­cuit Judge, and here reprinted by permission.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author id="b783-5" pgmap="783">BBADLEY, Circuit Justice.</author>
                <p id="AxIG" pgmap="783">The hill is filed in this case to subject certain property, conveyed by the complainant to Ovid Mazange many years since, to a parol trust, in favor of the complainant, on which, as he alleges, the conveyance was made. The Bank of Mobile is made a defendant because it has an execution against Eslava which has been levied on the property in ques­tion. On filing the bill and before issuing the subpoena, the complainant obtained an order to examine himself and his wife as to any transactions with or statements by Ovid Mazange, deceased, upon interroga­tories to be served on the parties to the suit, or upon notice to them, before some com­missioner of the United States. The rule suggests that Eslava and his wife are aged and infirm, and reside in New Orleans. As soon as issue was joined in the cause, the defendants gave notice to the complainant that they desired the testimony in the cáse should be taked orally, under the 67th rule of the court, and soon after filed written ob­jections to taking the testimony of the plain­tiff and his wife on the grounds, amongst others, that the complainant was not a competent witness in the case (Mazange be­ing dead), and that the wife could not be a witness for her husband. The complain­ant’s counsel, nevertheless, after this, pro­ceeded to file and serve interrogatories with a view to examine the complainant and his wife on commission. The defendants filed cross interrogatories under protest. The ex­amination having been taken and the depo­sitions returned, the defendants at the last term moved to suppress the same. The motion, not being disposed of, is now re­peated. One ground of the motion is, that the complainant and his wife are not com­petent witnesses in the case.</p>
                <p id="b783-6" pgmap="783">In general the competency of witnesses in the United States courts in civil cases is governed by the la\\T of the state in which the court is held. Such was the rule enacted by the statute of July 6, 1862 (12 Stat 588). But congress has specially regulated the subject now before the court By the act of July 2,^ 1864 (13 Stat 351), it was de­clared, amongst other things, that there should be no exclusion of any witness in the federal courts because he was a party to, or interested in, the issue tried. This act was modified by that of March 3, 1865 (13 Stat. 533), by which it was enacted that in actions by or against executors, admin­istrators, or guardians, neither party should be allowed to testify against the other as to any transaction with, or statement by, the testator, intestate or ward unless called to testify thereto by the opposite party, or required to testify thereto by the court. This act is a recognition of the glaring in­justice it would involve, to permit one party to propound himself as a witness in his own behalf as to a transaction between him and a deceased person, who can no longer give his version of the affair. If the law were to allow a man to wait until his antag­onist were dead, and then to sue his heirs, and put himself upon the witness stand and give his version of the affair, with no one to contradict or qualify his testimony, it would be as gross a prostitution of the forms of law, as to allow a man to be judge in his own cause. Every honest mind re­volts against it. There may be special cases, it is true, in which the court can see- that no injustice would be done by calling on a party to testify, even though his adversary be deceased. But it is useless to attempt to anticipate such cases. When they arise it will be for the court, and not the party himself, to suggest that he be called. Or, if he make the suggestion, the other party ought at least to be heard upon it</p>
                <p id="Ai2" pgmap="783(362) 784(10)">It is claimed in this case that the court has made an order to take the testimony. But how was it made? It was an ex parte order taken before the defendants were sub­poenaed to appear in the cause. When the statute authorizes such testimony to be taken if “required by the court,” it does not refer to such a requirement or order as that which was made in this case. If an ex parte order can be got in this way, the statute would be practically abrogated. The reservation of power in the court to require the evidence to be taken was made in order to provide for such extreme and special cases as might arise, in which it would be a great hardship not to take it. The court will exercise this power with great care and caution. This case is one in which it would be eminently improper to allow the evidence. The complainant seeks to set up a parol trust in property conveyed away by him over twenty years ago, and possessed by the grantee and his assigns ever since. It would be most dangerous to allow a parti to prove his own case under such circumstances, after his grantee was dead. Whether it is provable at all is an­other question, not now before the court. But no man’s property would be safe under such a rule of evidence. Of course, the wife is incompetent to testify for or against her husband. The fact that the Bank of Mo­bile has filed a cross bill in the case can make no difference. The order to examine the parties is taken on behalf of the com­plainant, not on behalf of-the bank, and; if it were taken on behalf of the bank, it would not help the case. The bank is not the “opposite party” referred to in the act who is authorized to call the plaintiff as a witness. The “opposite” party meant is that party against whom the evidence is sought to be used. The interests of the complain­ant and of the bank in the matter are the same. The testimony is clearly incompe­tent and must be disallowed, and the depo­sitions suppressed.</p>
                <p id="b784-3" pgmap="784">It is urged that the witnesses were did and infirm, and, therefore, that the order to take their testimony was strictly regular under the 70th rule in equity. That rule was not originally intended for the examin­ation of a party; and it may be questioned whether, under any circumstances, it ought to be extended to the case of a party pro­pounding himself as a witness. But it cer­tainly cannot legalize testimony taken as the plaintiff’s has been taken in this case. It may also be urged that the order for tak­ing the testimony must stand until it is regularly discharged. It is undoubtedly the general rule that, after the close of the term in which an order is made, it must stand until it is regularly discharged. But orders obtained upon motion may be dis­charged upon motion; and a fortiori, orders obtained ex parte may be thus discharged which have never been assented to, but al­ways resisted by the other party; and a motion to suppress depositions fairly brings up the regularity of an ex parte order di­recting them to be taken, as well as the competency of the witnesses examined, if the party moving to suppress has never done anything to waive the objection.</p>
                <p id="b784-4" pgmap="784">From an examination of the minutes and files in this case, I am satisfied that the de­fendants have taken every opportunity fairly in their power to express their oppo­sition to the testimony of these parties, as well as to the taking of it by deposition. The motion to suppress the depositions will be granted; but, as they were taken under an order of the court, though an irregular order, the cause will be continued until the next term, and the time for taking tes­timony enlarged until the rule day in Sep­tember, to enable the complainant to take other testimony in the cause, with like lib­erty to the defendants.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="782" ORDERLABEL="780" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00391_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00391_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00391_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_782.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00391_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="783" ORDERLABEL="781" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00392_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00392_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00392_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_783.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00392_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="784" ORDERLABEL="782" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00392_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00392_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00392_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_784.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00392_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AGqs" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0408"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_782.34" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00391_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_782.35" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00391_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b782-21" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0408"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_782.30" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00391_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b784-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0408"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_784.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00392_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Ai2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0408"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_783.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00392_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_784.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00392_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b784-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0408"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_784.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00392_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b783-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0408"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_783.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00392_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b783-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0408"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_783.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00392_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b783-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0408"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_783.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00392_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_783.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00392_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b783-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0408"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_783.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00392_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b782-22" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0408"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_782.31" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00391_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b782-36" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0408"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_782.44" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00391_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b782-23" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0408"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_782.32" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00391_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b782-24" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0408"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_782.33" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00391_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AxIG" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0408"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_783.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00392_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_783.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00392_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
