<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044049817315_0291" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="C.C.D. Mass." jurisdiction="United States">United States Circuit Court for the District of Massachusetts</court>
          <name abbreviation="The Jerusalem">The JERUSALEM</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 7,293</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">13 F. Cas. 559</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">2 Gall. 191</citation>
          <decisiondate>1814-10</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-10T00:25:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:27:33Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:41:28Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00281_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="48db37fff238cfee284b8444a7b75218" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="86020">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00281_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00281_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="ed458e2bdaaebed18f818a5c4aad1526" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="8442">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00281_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00282_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="c8f3ea6f5d9f93e6c4b4c95a3cc4be50" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="68950">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00282_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00282_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="1518c17fdf2731278fd633139edf9857" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="110542">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00282_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00283_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="c11acd689fca8d9d457240545b96d61d" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="106802">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00283_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00283_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="e928f1d38705475c3d081e4cfbd77dac" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="26202">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00283_1.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00281_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="8685e8e19673b9a9dc08346a1c46b078" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3267594">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00281_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00281_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="02ad1c892c11a2a85098b5fb9ec75b30" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="1054456">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00281_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00282_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="37d48b4645c2d17884148283c3f88698" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2756864">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00282_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00282_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="cca85a4f91c4790a22688a6f3f78583d" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3778820">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00282_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00283_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="30e7ec5d8970b8db184434c4cf0056f4" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3738627">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00283_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00283_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="e9c7ed1cd6d54b02047da8a767218c58" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="1658571">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00283_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00281_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="d81343addf9e3b123e17c144a6d4fb61" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="184587">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00281_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00281_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="469a2e5d83fe120bac1003a6202a2be5" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="4838">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00281_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00282_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="bc5c17a19c1745484b4e8927d048f1a3" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="148037">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00282_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00282_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="1640f63877b8e6ff2c6131eb0a41fe08" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="240495">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00282_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00283_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="760e28b0b34971f33fb5de77a4a89bae" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="239173">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00283_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00283_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="8b079654ee8680bb85389c0f0da4f0df" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="45425">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00283_1.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0291" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="564" firstpage="559">
              <court pgmap="561" id="b561-10">Circuit Court, D. Massachusetts.</court>
              <docketnumber pgmap="561" id="b561-7">Case No. 7,293.</docketnumber>
              <citation pgmap="561" id="b561-9">[2 Gall. 191.] <footnotemark>1</footnotemark>
              </citation>
              <parties pgmap="561" id="b561-8">The JERUSALEM.</parties>
              <decisiondate pgmap="561" id="Am_2">Oct. Term, 1814.</decisiondate>
              <attorneys pgmap="562" id="b562-7">Mr. Hubbard, for libellant.</attorneys>
              <attorneys pgmap="562" id="b562-9">Mr. Blake, Dist. Atty., for claimants.</attorneys>
              <attorneys pgmap="563" id="b563-4">Mr. Prescott, in reply.</attorneys>
              <footnote label="1">
                <p pgmap="561" id="b561-14">1 [Reported by John Gallisou, Esq.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author pgmap="563" id="b563-9">STORY, Circuit Justice.</author>
                <p pgmap="563" id="AIBr">It is not necessary,' in this stage of the cause, to inquire info the exactness or regularity of the allega­tions of the parties. A preliminary ques­tion, as to the right of this court to ad­judicate upon the merits, of the case, has been brought forward upon a protest to its jurisdiction, and after an ample discussion, remains now to be decided.</p>
                <p pgmap="563" id="b563-10">The question in short is this, whether the courts of the United States, in the exercise of their authority over causes of admiralty and maidtime jurisdiction, have cognizance of maritime suits in rem between foreign­ers, whose permanent domicil is in a for­eign country, when the specific property is within our territory. I state this as the general question, although in the acts of court the parties have alleged facts, which, if proved, might perhaps somewhat nar­row the discussion. But it is fit, that the general principle, that governs this class of cases, should be extracted from the embar­rassment of minute circumstances, exam­ined in its more extended application. Whatever may be the case as to other mar­itime contracts, respecting which I affirm or deny nothing, it cannot be doubted, that the contract of bottomry is one, over which the admiralty exercises an undisputed juris­diction. It is indeed, the only tribunal capable of enforcing a specific performance in rem by seizing into its custody the very subject of hypothecation. To its guardian care, I may without rashness affirm, the whole commercial world look for security and redress, and without its summary in­terference, maritime loans would, in all probability, become obsolete. A jurisdiction so ancient and beneficial, which exercises its powers according to the law of nations, and those rules and maxims of civil right, which may be said to form the basis of the institutions. of all Europe, ought not to be restrained within narrow bounds, unless authority or public policy distinctly requires It.</p>
                <p pgmap="563(289) 564(19)" id="Aqef">It is argued, that the courts of a country cannot consistently with the law of nations, take cognizance of any controversy between foreigners, who are not domiciled within its territory; and Vattel (book 2, c. 7, §§ 84, 85; book 2, c. 8, § 103) is cited in support of the position. It is true, that Yattel con­tends that personal controversies between foreigners, or between a foreigner and a citizen, are to be determined by the judge of the place, wnere the defendant has his settled abode, or where he is, when any sudden difficulty arises. But this rule is so far from being universally acknowledged, that many nations exercise jurisdiction over the property and persons of foreigners found transiently in their territory, not only in favor of citizens, but also of other foreign­ers. Vinn. Comm. Inst, de Actionibus, lib. 4, tit. 6, p. 777, §§ 8, 9; 2 Hub. lib. 5, tit. 1, § 46; De Carriere v. De Calonne, 4 Ves. 577. The rule seems indeed exclusively drawn from the civil law. But, however the case may be, as to remitting the de­fendant to his domestic forum in personal ■ controversies, it is very clearly settled, that in proceedings in rem, or the real actions of the civil law, the proper forum is the locus rei sitae. Indeed, it seems to have been a question among civilians, whether the action in rem could be brought before any other tribunal. 8 Vinn. Comm. Inst, de Actionibus, lib. 4, tit. 6, p. 777; 2 Hub. lib. 5, tit. 1, p. 728, § 50; Heinec. Ad. Pan­dect, lib. 5. tit. 1. § 36; Bynk. De For­Leg. c. 4; Casar. Disc. 43, § 53; Id. Disc. 179, § 52; 2 Emer. Des Contrats a la Grosse, c. 9, § 2; Id. p. 528, § 4.</p>
                <p pgmap="564" id="b564-3">With reference, therefore, t.o what may he deemed the public law of Europe, a pro­ceeding in rem may well be maintained in our courts, where the property of a for­eigner is within our jurisdiction. Nor am T able to perceive how the exercise of such judicial authority clashes with any princi­ples of public policy. The refusal might indeed well be deemed a disregard of na­tional comity, inasmuch as it would be withholding from a party the only effectual means of obtaining his right. And, accord­ingly, it has been held, that it is a good cause of reprisal for a sovereign not to compel his courts to execute the sentence of a foreign court, where the person or goods sentenced are within his jurisdiction. 2 Brown, Adm. 120. It is argued, that the ex­ercise of such authority would be highly inconvenient, inasmuch as this contract, like many other maritime contracts, is dif­ferently regulated in different countries, and therefore the construction of the contract, as well as the remedy on it, might in many cases essentially differ. And it is urged, that on this ground courts of law uniformly re­fuse to interfere, in respect to the contracts of foreigners made with their own seamen for marine services. I am not aware, that the inconvenience is so great as has been represented. It is a general rule, that for­eign contracts are to be construed accord­ing to the law of the place where they are made, or to be executed. And I do not per­ceive the hardship of compelling a party to perform his engagements according to the construction, which the courts of his own country would put upon them. In respect to maritime contracts, there is still less rea­son to decline the jurisdiction, for in almost all civilized countries, these are in general substantially governed by the same rules. Almost all Europe have derived their mari­time codes from the Mediterranean; and even in this country we take a pride in con­forming our decisions to the rales of the venerable Oonsolato del Mare.</p>
                <p pgmap="564" id="b564-4">As to the case alluded to. of the contracts of seamen for wages. I am not aware that any authority countenances the position, to the extent in which it is laid down. Where the voyage has not terminated,' or the sea­men have bound themselves to abide by the decisions of the tribunals of their own eountry, foreign courts have declined any interference, and remitted the parties to their own tribunals for redress. But where the contract has been dissolved by the reg­ular termination of the voyage, or by the wrongful act of the other party, the cases are not unfrequent, in which foreign courts have sustained the claim for mariners’ wages. Limland v. Stephens, 3 Esp. 269; Hulle v. Heightman. 4 Esp. 75. 2 East. 145; Sigard v. Roberts, 3 Esp. 71: Thompson v. The Catharina [Case No. 13.949]; Willend-­son v. The Forsoket [Id. 17.682]; Moran v. Baudin [Id. 9,785]; Weiberg v. The St. Oloff [Id. 17,357]; Thomson v. The Nanny [Id. 13,984]. And although the doctrine in Gie­nar v. Meyer, 2 H. Bl. 603, and the intima­tions in The Two Friends, 1 C. Rob. Adm, 271, look the other way, it does not seem to me that they outweigh the authorities on the other side, even supposing (which is not admitted) that they are not to be reconciled.</p>
                <p pgmap="564(433) 565(9)" id="b564-7">It is admitted, that suits for salvage have been entertained between foreigners in the admiralty, and it is urged that these form exceptions to the general rule, as cases standing upon the jus gentium, or upheld by the consent of the parties. Independent, however, of the principle, that consent can never give a jurisdiction to a court, which it cannot otherwise sustain, the decisions on this subject evidently proceed upon the ground, that the court has a competent ca­pacity, and leave the policy of its exercise to be judged of by the circumstances of the particular case. The Two Friends, 1 C. Rob. Adm. 271; Mason v. The Blaireau, 2 Cranch [6 U. S.] 240. And although Sir W. Scott intimated, in The Two Friends, that if there was the slightest disinclination of the parties to submit to the jurisdiction, he should not incline to interfere; yet he evidently refers to cases, where all the for­eign parties decline the jurisdiction (as might happen in eases like that before him), and not to cases, where the jurisdiction was sought by one of them. And the whole current of his reasoning strongly leans in favor of the policy of sustaining the general jurisdiction of the admiralty over foreign­ers. In the same case, it was asserted by counsel, and not denied, that the admiralty frequently entertained bottomry suits be­tween foreigners. And. accordingly, we And that in The Gratitudine, 3 C. Rob. Adm. 240, and The Jacob. 4 C. Rob. Adm. 245. both of which cases were contested on other points with great ability, the court sustain­ed the jurisdiction and decreed in favor of the bottomry holders. It may be said that the question of jurisdiction passed without objection; but it is difficult to conceive, that it could have escaped the attention of the court and of the bar, if it had been deemed tenable. It has been argued, that these were cases where the voyage ended within the British dominions, and therefore are distinguishable. But I know of no principle, which sustains this distinction. It was not the ease of a contract made with reference to the laws, and to be executed within the dominions, of Great Britain. The most that can be said is, that there the lien first attached absolutely upon the property. In the latter case, however, this lien grew out of a former voyage, and was applied to reach proceeds of freight, which accrued in a subsequent voyage. The ground then of the jurisdiction could not have been, that the voyage terminated in Great Britain, but that the proceeds were within the reach of the ■court.</p>
                <p pgmap="565" id="b565-3">And this leads me to the consideration, that the jurisdiction of the admiralty, in matters of contract, depends not on the char­acter of the parties, but on the character of the contract, whether maritime or not. When once its jurisdiction, therefore, rightfully at­taches on the subject matter, it will exercise it conformably with the law of nations, or the lex loci contractus, as the case may re­quire. It will enforce a foreign maritime judgment between foreigners, where either the property or the person is within its juris­diction. 2 Brown, Adm. 120. Yet the ob-. jection to such proceedings, so far as touches the remedy, applies as forcibly here as in other maritime causes.</p>
                <p pgmap="565" id="b565-4">It has been urged, that whatever may be the propriety of interfering- in cases arising between the subjects of the powers of Europe, the court ought studiously to abstain where the parties are subjects of the Sublime Ot­toman Porte. It is certainly true, that m prize causes an indulgence is granted to the subjects of the Ottoman empire, which is not allowed to any foreigners of Christian Eu­rope, in consideration of the peculiarities of their situation and character, and of their not being professors of exactly the same law ■of nations with ourselves. • The Madonna del Burso, 4 C. Rob. Adm. 109. But in mat­ters of contract between such persons, or be­tween them and other foreigners, I am not aware that courts have thought themselves at liberty to act otherwise, than by the gen­eral rules applicable to all forensic busi­ness; especially where one subject of the empire has asked for redress against an­other, and upon a maritime contract, tbe stipulations of which seem to require a sum­mary interference, and to recognize an ac­quaintance with the general maritime codes of Europe.</p>
                <p pgmap="565" id="b565-5">On the whole. I am of opinion, that the rule of the civil law, “in aetionibus in rem ■speciale forum tribuit locus in quo res sitae sunt” (Yinn. Comm. Inst, de Aetionibus, lib. 4 tit. 6, p. 777; Heinec. Comm, in Band. pt. 2, p. 147, § 36), applies to this case; that there is no solid ground against the exercise ol the jurisdiction, and in the language of Sir W. Scott, on another occasion (The Two Friends, 1 C. Rob. Adm. 271, 280), I will add: “I go farther, and say, that I think there is great reason for it. because it is the only way of enforcing the best security, that ol the lien on the property itself.”</p>
                <p pgmap="565" id="b565-6">I have thus far considered the case upon general principles; and if I had felt any difficulty in the conclusion, which 1 have already stated, I should have felt none, when the contract itself carries on its face a stipu­lation, that the voyage was to terminate in a foreign country; and therefore that a suit in rem in such a foreign country would not only be sustained (as the claimants counsel has admitted) but was evidently within the contemplation of the parties. Where the parties have, therefore, waived the benefit of the exclusive jurisdiction of their own tribunals, the whole reasoning, upon which they should be remitted to such forum, falls to the ground. To remit this cause from the present to another foreign forum, I imagine would be “but to change postures on an un­easy bed.”</p>
                <p pgmap="565" id="b565-9">There is also another fact alleged, and which, if true, brings this case directly with­in the authorities cited, and that is, that the voyage really ended in the United States. The voyage stated in the bottomry bond is from Smyrna to the West; and a different rate of interest is payable, as the cargo shall be discharged in Malta, or Sicily, Majorca, Minorca or other port in Spain or in Lisbon. And the claimant expressly stipulates to make payment in Smyrna, on his safe return, or in any other places where the obligation should be presented to him, after the sale of the cargo then on board. And the allegation of the proponent states, that the cargo was whol­ly sold, part in the United States, and part at the Havanna. But I forbear to dwell on this and other peculiarities, because I am entirely satisfied to rest the cause on the soundness of the general doctrine. I overrule the protest of the claimant to the jurisdiction of the court, and assign him to answer peremptorily to the libel of the plaintiff.<footnotemark>3</footnotemark>
                </p>
                <p pgmap="565" id="b565-10">Prescott &amp; Hubbard, for libellant.</p>
                <p pgmap="565" id="b565-11">G. Blake, for claimant.</p>
                <p pgmap="565" id="b565-12">At a subsequent day of the term Blake read the answer in chief of Catara, which, among other things, denied that the instrument of hypothecation relied upon was his deed. The replication averred the bond to be the deed of Catara. A copy of the contract in the hand­writing of the Swedish consul at Smyrna, and attested by him as a true copy, was pro­duced by the counsel of the libellant, and up­on this they founded a motion for a continu­ance, to afford them time for procuring tbe original.</p>
                <p pgmap="565" id="b565-13">Mr. Blake, Dist. Atty., opposed this motion. He represented to the court the extreme hard­ship of this case, and contended, that there had been such remissness and laches in not procuring the original, that no postponement ought to be granted to the libellants for this cause; that three originals were executed, and probably delivered to the obligee; that one of these might have been sent at the same time with the copy; that it would be impossi­ble to obtain the original from Smyrna in any reasonable time, and that the libellant had therefore commenced this action prematurely, and ought not be permitted to hold the claim­ant in fetters for so long a time, as must nec-­sarily elapse.</p>
                <p pgmap="565(24) 566(153)" id="b565-14">STORY, Circuit Justice, said, he did not wish to hear the other side; that the princi­ples of law were clear; that admitting three originals to have been executed, it would have been difficult, considering the nature of this voyage, for the libellant to obtain such intelligence, as would enable him to deter­mine, to what'place the originals should be sent; that the hardship was common to both parties; and that the court could not be in­fluenced by the distressed situation of Catara, however it might be deserving of pity; that, at common law, it was the practice to allow time for procuring originals, as in cases of bills of exchange; that there did not appear, in this case, to have been any laches on the part of the libellant, and there being evidence to satisfy the court of the existence of an original, the cause must therefore be con­tinued. If, as was alleged, the vessel was in a perishing condition, an order of sale might be made, upon a proper application for this purpose.</p>
                <footnote label="3">
                  <p pgmap="565" id="b565-15">3 See the case of The See Reuter, 1 Dod. 22.</p>
                </footnote>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="561" ORDERLABEL="559" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00281_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00281_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00281_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_561.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00281_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="562" ORDERLABEL="560" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00281_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00281_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00281_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_562.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00281_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="563" ORDERLABEL="561" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00282_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00282_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00282_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_563.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00282_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="564" ORDERLABEL="562" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00282_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00282_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00282_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_564.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00282_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="565" ORDERLABEL="563" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00283_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00283_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00283_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_565.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00283_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="566" ORDERLABEL="564" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00283_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00283_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00283_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_566.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00283_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Aqef" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0291"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_563.16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00282_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_564.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00282_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b565-11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0291"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_565.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00283_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b564-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0291"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_564.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00282_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_565.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00283_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b564-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0291"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_564.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00282_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_564.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00282_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b565-12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0291"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_565.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00283_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b565-15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0291"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_565.16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00283_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b564-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0291"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_564.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00282_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b561-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0291"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_561.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00281_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b561-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0291"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_561.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00281_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b561-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0291"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_561.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00281_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b565-13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0291"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_565.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00283_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b563-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0291"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_563.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00282_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_563.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00282_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b565-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0291"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_565.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00283_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b565-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0291"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_565.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00283_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b565-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0291"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_565.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00283_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AIBr" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0291"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_563.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00282_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_563.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00282_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b565-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0291"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_565.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00283_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_565.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00283_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b565-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0291"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_565.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00283_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b565-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0291"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_565.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00283_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b562-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0291"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_562.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00281_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b562-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0291"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_562.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00281_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b565-14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0291"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_565.15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00283_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_566.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00283_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b563-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0291"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_563.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00282_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Am_2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0291"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_561.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00281_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_561.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00281_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b563-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0291"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_563.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00282_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b561-14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0291"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_561.19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00281_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b561-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0291"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_561.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00281_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
