<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044046873683_0395" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="C.C.S.D.N.Y." jurisdiction="United States">United States Circuit Court for the Southern District of New York</court>
          <name abbreviation="Erie Ry. Co. v. Heath">ERIE RY. CO. et al. v. HEATH et al.</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 4,515</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">8 F. Cas. 763</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">9 Blatchf. 226</citation>
          <decisiondate>1871-12-19</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-12T19:40:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-26T10:42:09Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-26T10:56:34Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00383_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="77e48873c707b3b4106567ff77b89c99" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="80784">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00383_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00383_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="bb4da328af3c283b309c67c96103a2ab" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="117296">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00383_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00384_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="db8b19313377caeb69a742536b8ff6f3" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="114650">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00384_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00384_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="2bbd1e4006a8107f9b94b5ed4d5062bd" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="89022">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00384_1.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00383_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="de99ff644230dd564382c73a2b9c82a4" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3117516">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00383_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00383_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="7292452cfe6f0ff6cf8d010004594bdb" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3818534">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00383_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00384_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="cdbdb29ba55aedf7a71b44b0c46bf37a" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3819328">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00384_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00384_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="bcf3e7041489f45cbc4811b1c1535c9a" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3332588">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00384_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00383_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="94961e2c8dfe5756b0fb3e0da7c5b21f" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="168822">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00383_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00383_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="df8f182d75b1bdf2b4938ad1be5424ec" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="244970">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00383_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00384_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="957509fc1a366b41bf19b5eb22652ccc" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="243013">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00384_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00384_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="63eed0f8ca540c6cdc5a7bf2fbff0cf8" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="185305">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00384_1.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0395" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="766" firstpage="763">
              <court id="b765-8" pgmap="765">Circuit Court, S. D. New York.</court>
              <docketnumber id="b765-5" pgmap="765">Case No. 4,515.</docketnumber>
              <citation id="b765-7" pgmap="765">[9 Blatchf. 226.] <footnotemark>1</footnotemark>
              </citation>
              <parties id="b765-6" pgmap="765">ERIE RY. CO. et al. v. HEATH et al.</parties>
              <decisiondate id="Az7Y" pgmap="765">Dec. 19, 1871.</decisiondate>
              <attorneys id="b765-13" pgmap="765">David Dudley Field and William A. Beach,' for petitioner.</attorneys>
              <attorneys id="b765-14" pgmap="765">William M. Evarts and Charles F. South-­mayd, for Heath and Raphael.</attorneys>
              <footnote label="1">
                <p id="b765-16" pgmap="765">1 [Reported by Hon. Samuel Blatckford, Dis­trict Judge, and here reprinted by permission.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author id="b765-15" pgmap="765">BLATCHFORD, District Judge.</author>
                <p id="A6Yc" pgmap="765(628) 766(177)">The sub­stance of the allegations of the petition of Jay Gould, how presented to the court, is, that there were put into the hands of the defendants Heath and Raphael, by the own­ers thereof, certificates for and representing shares of stock in the Erie Railway Company amounting .to over 300,000 shares; that such certificates, when so put into their hands, were each of them accompanied by a power of attorney to transfer the same, signed in blank by the holder on the back of the cer­tificate, with permission to such defendants to stamp their names in such blank power of attorney, thereby conferring upon them power to cause the shares represented by each certificate to be transferred on the books of the corporation to the name of them, thus giving them full power and authority over the stock to the same extent as though they were bona fide owners and holders thereof; that thereupon the defendants caused their names to be stamped in the blank powers of attorney, so executed, authorizing them to cause the stock to be transferred on the transfer, books of the company, to the names of them or their nominees;. that, for the stock so received, the defendants caused to be delivered to the shareholders, in exchange for each certificate of stock received, a re­ceipt in substance as follows: “No. -. Received of-,-certificates for-­shares in the Erie Railway Company, to be forwarded to America for registration in the names of Messrs. Robert Amadeus Heath and Henry Lewis Raphael;” that all of the stock so received was stamped with the names of the said Heath and Raphael, in the power of attorney so signed in blank, there by empowering them to cause said stock to be transferred upon the books of the corpo­ration to their own names; that such receipts do not represent, and were not intended to represent, any particular certificates of stock, or class of such certificates, and do not des­ignate any of such certificates to which the holders of such certificates are entitled, but, on the contrary, entitle the holders thereof to demand any portion of the certificates held by the defendants, without any discrimina­tion; that the petitioner is the holder and owner of 12,735 shares of the stock of the company, the certificates or evidence where­of, issued by the company, have been so de­livered to the defendants, with a blank pow­er of attorney, for a transfer thereof, signed on the back thereof, with the names of the said Heath and Raphael stamped thereon; that the only evidence the petitioner has of his ownership of such certificates is a quan­tity of such receipts in said form, the num­ber of each receipt and the quantity of shares represented by it being set forth, the receipts being 124 in number; that 60,000 shares or over of the stock of the company, with said blank powers of attorney endorsed thereon, and with the names of Heath and Raphael stamped thereon, have been presented at the office of the company, with the request that the same be transferred to the names of the said Heath and Raphael, and the company, under the orders of this court herein, has, to a great extent, caused such shares to be put in condition to be transferred to the names of said Heath and Raphael, and is diligent­ly engaged in completing such transfer; that the certificates representing the shares of the stock of the company owned by the peti­tioner, and represented by such receipts now held by him, are a part of and among such certificates so delivered to Heath and Ra­phael, with such blank powers of attorney endorsed thereon, and which have been stamped with the stamp of Heath and Ra­phael in the blank power of attorney, and are either a part of such 60,000 shares or of the residue not embraced therein; that the petitioner has no means of identifying such certificates, his only evidence of ownership thereof being the receipts he holds for the same, in the form before mentioned; that the petitioner is unwilling that the stock owned by him, or the certificates represent­ing the same, should be held by or in the names of said Heath and Raphael, or any of their nominees; that said Heath and Ra­phael acquired no title to or interest in said stock, by virtue of said receipts, or any right to hold the same; and that no trust was cre­ated for any purpose by which said stock can be held by said Heath and Raphael as against the owners thereof, nor were such re­ceipts intended by such owners to create in said Heath and Raphael any right, title, or interest therein, either in trust or otherwise.</p>
                <p id="b766-4" pgmap="766">The prayer of the petition is, that this court will cause proof to be taken of the title of the petitioner to the said shares of stock and certificates, and that the same, to the extent of the receipts held by him, may be delivered to him, and that, in the mean­time, the delivery of such shares and certifi­cates to said Heath and Raphael, or any other person, to the extent above claimed by the petitioner, may be suspended, until the title of the petitioner thereto shall be ad­judged by this court</p>
                <p id="b766-5" pgmap="766">In answer to this petition, it is shown, by affidavit, that the receipts referred to in the petition are not specially for parts of the 60,056 shares of stock involved in this suit, but are foi portions of a much larger quan­tity of stock deliyered over to said Heath and Raphael for registration in their names, the 60,056 shares forming part of the entire larger quantity; that the transfer to said Heath and Raphael, or registration in their names, of the said stock other than said 60,056 shares, has been hitherto prevented by the refusal of the company to permit such transfers; that, at present, any at­tempt, of said Heath and Raphael to ef­fect such transfer is practically enjoined by an order of receivership granted by the supreme court of New York, by the terms of which any such stock, upon being pre­sented for transfer or registration, is to be forthwith taken into the possession of a receiver; that, by the terms of the arrange­ment by which the stock was delivered by its owners to Heath and Raphael, for registration, and such receipts were is­sued therefor, the delivery of the new stock certificates to the owners, after the making of such transfer and registration in the names of Heath and Raphael, was to be made not in this country, but in London; that information has been received from the person who signed the receipts, that there is reason to believe that spurious and forged documents, purporting to be such receipts for shares delivered for registration, have been put in circulation, and are outstanding; that, if this court should undertake to enter­tain jurisdiction in respect of the obligations of Heath and Raphael under such receipts, and to compel delivery of the stock called for by the receipts to be made in this country to the holders of the receipts, instead of requiring it to be done in London, accord­ing to the arrangement under which the stock was received for registration, there is not believed to be any safe basis here upon which the agents or attorneys of Heath and Raphael can know or decide as to whether receipts which may be presented here are genuine or not, nor as to the genuineness or validity of the title, by endorsement or otherwise, under which the parties now hold­ing such receipts may claim to have become assignees of the rights of the persons to whom the receipts were originally given; that the said stock, other than the 60,056 shares, the transfer of which to the names of Heath and Raphael has been and is thus' prevented, is very large in amount, em­bracing many thousands of shares, a large amount of such stock having been sent back to England after the seizure of the 60,056 shares; and that the practical negotiability of the stock certificates therefor has been destroyed, because of the fact, that, when such stock was sent to the United States for transfer and registration, the names of Heath and Raphael were inserted as trans­ferees, in the powers of attorney endorsed on the certificates, so that delivery of such-­stock can no longer be made to a purchaser by giving to him the certificate with a blank power of attorney for transfer.</p>
                <p id="b766-8" pgmap="766">In July last, when this suit was before me in one of its phases, the question was dis­cussed as to the propriety of allowing the real owner of the stock represented by Heath and Raphael to claim it at the hands of this court while it is in the custody of this court. I then remarked [Case No. 4,-­514]: “When such stock shall have been placed in proper condition for its restora­tion to Heath and Raphael, if, then, any person claiming any of the stock through evidence of title issued by Heath and Raphael, shall apply to this court to have his rights in the premises awarded to him out of the res in court, the application will be considered and disposed of.”</p>
                <p id="b766-9" pgmap="766(101) 767(563)">It is quite apparent, that the claim of the petitioner to have delivered to him certifi­cates of stock to the extent of 12,735 shares out of the entire 60,056 shares, but no par­ticular 12,735 shares, cannot be allowed. By the transaction of putting the certificates for the shares into the hands of Heath and Raphael, the owners thereof merely appoint­ed Heath and Raphael their agents to have such stock transferred to ana registered in the names of such agents. Such agency was not a power coupled with an interest, but was a power revocable at the will of its grantor. The petitioner, claiming to stand in the place of original grantors of such powers, (for he does not allege that he was an original depositor of certificates,) claims to revoke such powers. But he can revoke them only in respect to the iden­tical certificates which such original gran­tors put into the hands of Heath and Ra­phael, or in respect to certificates represent­ing, in direct replacement and succession, such original certificates, and not in respect to certificates which were not put into the hands of Heath and Raphael by grantors of •powers to whom receipts were issued which the petitioner claims to own. He explicit­ly states, in his petition, that the certifi­cates represented by the receipts which he owns are either a part of the 60,056 shares, or are a part of the remainder not included in the 60,056 shares, and that he has no means of identifying such certificates. It is true, that the petition states, that such receipts do not represent, and were not in­tended to represent, any particular certifi­cates of stock, and do not designate any of such certificates to which the holders there­of are entitled, but entitle the holders to demand and receive any portion of the cer­tificates of stock held by Heath and Raphael, without discrimination. The receipts do not specify or identify, by numbers or other­wise, the particular certificates received, and do not, on their faces, represent any partic­ular certificates, or designate the certificates received as being the certificates to which the holders of the receipts are entitled. But it by no means follows that the receipts do not in fact represent any particular certifi­cates, or that they entitle the holders there­of to demand and receive any portion of the certificates held by Heath and Raphael, without discrimination. Each receipt bears a number. It is to be supposed that, by such numbers, or otherwise, the particular certificates which each grantor of a power placed in the hands of Heath and Raphael can be identified. Whether this be so or not, any person who can identify the cer­tificates he deposited, is entitled to call upon Heath and Raphael to respond in respect of such particular certificates, and to claim that no one else shall call upon them to re­spond in respect of the same certificates. This view becomes important in connec­tion with the fact that Heath and Raphael hold, under like powers, certificates for a very large number of- shares besides the 60.056 shares. Such other shares have not yet been transferred to, or registered in, the names of Heath and Raphael. This has happened, as appears, through no fault of Heath and Raphael. There is no justice in allowing the petitioner to claim and receive the 12,735 shares in preference to other de­positors who are not parties in court Por aught that appears, it may very well be, that such other depositors deposited all the eer- • tifieates representing the particular 00,050 shares now in the hands of this court The petitioner does not assert that any person under whom he claims title to the receipts, deposited any of such certificates, nor does he assert that such certificates were not’ all of them, deposited by persons to whom the receipts which he claims to own were not issued.</p>
                <p id="b767-5" pgmap="767">This court can, out of the 60,056 shares which are in its custody, deliver certificates for shares to no other person than Heath and Raphael, on a petition of this character, in this suit, unless such person shows him­self affirmatively to be the depositor, or the assignee of the depositor, of particular cer­tificates which have been replaced by, and are directly represented by, particular cer­tificates forming part of such 60,056 shares.</p>
                <p id="b767-6" pgmap="767">I do not dwell upon any of the other views taken in the affidavit presented in opposition to the petition, or urged on the hearing, or express any opinion in regard to them, as the grounds on which I have above put my decision are sufficient to dis­pose of the present application.</p>
                <p id="b767-7" pgmap="767">In connection with the suggestion as to spurious receipts, I observe, in the list of the receipts furnished by the petitioner, as owned by him, there are, of receipts num­bered 15, 18, 59, 191, 329, 438, 460, 812 and 906, two each; of receipts numbered 381, 428 and 475, three each; and of receipt num­bered 349, four. These thirty-one receipts cover 3,700 shares. In the cases of num­bers 15, 329, 460 and 812, the same number of shares is represented by each of the two receipts of the same number. In the cases of numbers 18, 59,_ 191, 438 and 906, a dif­ferent number of shares is represented by each of the two receipts of the same number. In the cases of numbers 428 and 475, the same number of shares is represented by each of two Of the three receipts of the same number, and a different number of shares is represented by the remaining one of the three. In the case of number 381, a differ­ent number of shares is represented by each of the three receipts of the same number. In the case of number 349, the same num­ber of shares is represented by each of two of the four receipts of the same number, and a different number of shares is rep­resented by each of the other two of such four receipts, each of such latter two rep­resenting, also, a different number of shares from the other one of such latter two. 1 allude to these circumstances only for the purpose of saying, that the field of inquiry which they indicate as a necessary one, is one which ought not to be entered upon by a tribunal which has before it only a por­tion of the entire number of shares cov­ered by the transactions with Heath and Raphael, and only a controversy respecting a portion of such entire number, and which has no jurisdiction in this suit to affect the rights of those who ai‘e not before it</p>
                <p id="b767-8" pgmap="767(8) 768(18)">The prayer of the petition is denied, and the order for the suspension of the deliver}' to Heath and Raphael of the 12,735 shares is vacated.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="765" ORDERLABEL="763" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00383_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00383_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00383_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_765.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00383_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="766" ORDERLABEL="764" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00383_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00383_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00383_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_766.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00383_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="767" ORDERLABEL="765" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00384_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00384_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00384_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_767.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00384_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="768" ORDERLABEL="766" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00384_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00384_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00384_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_768.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00384_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b765-13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0395"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_765.15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00383_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b765-16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0395"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_765.21" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00383_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b765-14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0395"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_765.16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00383_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b765-15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0395"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_765.17" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00383_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b767-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0395"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_767.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00384_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b767-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0395"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_767.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00384_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b767-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0395"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_767.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00384_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b765-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0395"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_765.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00383_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b765-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0395"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_765.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00383_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b765-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0395"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_765.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00383_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b765-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0395"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_765.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00383_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b767-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0395"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_767.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00384_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_768.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00384_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b766-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0395"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_766.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00383_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_767.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00384_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_767.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00384_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b766-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0395"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_766.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00383_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b766-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0395"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_766.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00383_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_766.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00383_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b766-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0395"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_766.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00383_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="A6Yc" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0395"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_765.18" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00383_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_765.19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00383_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_765.20" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00383_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_766.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00383_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Az7Y" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0395"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_765.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00383_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
