<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044046873683_0634" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="C.C.S.D.N.Y." jurisdiction="United States">United States Circuit Court for the Southern District of New York</court>
          <name abbreviation="Ferrett v. Atwill">FERRETT et al. v. ATWILL</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 4,747</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">8 F. Cas. 1161</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">1 Blatchf. 151; 4 N. Y. Leg. Obs. 215, 294</citation>
          <decisiondate>1846-04</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-12T19:40:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-26T10:42:09Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-26T10:56:36Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00582_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="165eba31e67232ea26f02508904ace52" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="42922">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00582_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00582_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="8ab7734b3474ca1fdd7dba1ff1f76010" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="73424">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00582_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00583_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="0ee399dc00c7f8e0d3189846ecd05f59" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="112010">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00583_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00583_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="b08cc88316d9aa3e0231117fc980febd" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="36642">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00583_1.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00582_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="a7f3090ff5772dacfbfee99d622a3162" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2134563">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00582_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00582_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="47b42b004182618085aa1de7ab56ad8e" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2733924">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00582_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00583_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="7de3c02c4c38686100c4d655dda22c3a" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3794110">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00583_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00583_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="4855e0642e952a3582b2861ebf33183f" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2027167">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00583_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00582_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="d71f54d210749df2d3f497e0f15bba07" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="80927">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00582_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00582_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="dcdc13cfdd068bb848566abed9ad6b2f" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="145109">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00582_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00583_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="f8403d01f975cab8e8f5e218ea048487" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="243795">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00583_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00583_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="c7b7d9f2b356c03459f9b2907729cdf5" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="70750">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00583_1.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0634" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="1164" firstpage="1161">
              <court id="b1163-10" pgmap="1163">Circuit Court, S. D. New York.</court>
              <docketnumber id="b1163-7" pgmap="1163">Case No. 4,747.</docketnumber>
              <citation id="b1163-9" pgmap="1163">[1 Blatchf. 151;<footnotemark>1</footnotemark> 4 N. Y. Leg. Obs. 215, 294.]</citation>
              <parties id="b1163-8" pgmap="1163">FERRETT et al. v. ATWILL.</parties>
              <decisiondate id="Am-o" pgmap="1163">April Term, 1846.</decisiondate>
              <judges id="b1164-7" pgmap="1164">Before NELSON, Circuit Justice, and BETTS, District Judge.</judges>
              <attorneys id="b1164-5" pgmap="1164">Samuel Sherwood and Randolph W. Town­send, for plaintiffs.</attorneys>
              <attorneys id="b1164-6" pgmap="1164">Marshall S. Bidwell and Samuel Owen, for defendant.</attorneys>
              <footnote label="1">
                <p id="b1163-13" pgmap="1163">1 [Reported by Samuel Blatchford, Esq., and here reprinted by permission.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author id="b1164-8" pgmap="1164">BETTS, District Judge.</author>
                <p id="ARIQ" pgmap="1164">The decision of the court in this case being limited to two points, we do not consider it proper to discuss the other questions involved in the plead­ings, and argued at length by the counsel; and our judgment being peremptory against the action, an attempt now to settle the other points presented by the case, will not, as if an amendment were allowed, tend to abridge litigation or to aid the parties in the disposition of the cause.</p>
                <p id="b1164-11" pgmap="1164">The declaration contains two counts, each of which demands a distinct penalty of $100. The first count charges that the de­fendant, on the first of July, 1845, at New-­York, published a musical composition, called “Alethia Waltz,” and falsely inserted therein and impressed upon the face thereof, the words: “Entered according to act of con­gress, &amp;c.,” without having at the time legally acquired the copy-right of the said musical composition. The second count al­leges that the defendant, at the time and place aforesaid, published a volume of music, called “Alethia Waltz,” and falsely inserted therein and impressed upon the title thereof, the words: “Entered according to act of con­gress, &amp;c.,” without having at the time legal­ly acquired the copy-right of the said volume of music.</p>
                <p id="b1164-12" pgmap="1164">The defendant demurs to the declaration, and, in connection with the general demurrer, assigns various causes of demurrer, only one of which is passed upon by the court; to wit, that the action is brought by two per­sons jointly, for themselves and the United States of' America. Some exceptions were taken to the sufficiency jn form of the special demurrer, but we do not regard the ques­tion as material, the objection to the decla­ration being good on general demurrer; be­cause the right of action, if any, is under the statute, and the declaration must show that the party suing is competent to main­tain the suit. Almy v. Harris, 5 Johns. 175. The decision, accordingly, rests upon this, that the act of congress does not authorize an action in the name of several persons and the United States, for the recovery of the penalties incurred by its violation.</p>
                <p id="b1164-13" pgmap="1164">The provisions governing the question are contained in the eleventh section of the act, which enacts, “that, if any person or persons, from and after the passing of this act, shall print or publish any book, map, chart, music­al composition, print, cut, or engraving, not having legally acquired the copy-right there­of, and shall insert or impress that the same hath been entered according to act of con­gress, or words purporting the same, every person so offending shall forfeit and pay one hundred dollars; one moiety thereof to the person who shall sue for the same, and the other to the use of the United States, to be recovered by action of debt, in any court of record having cognizance thereof.”</p>
                <p id="b1164-14" pgmap="1164(87) 1165(248)">In actions directly upon a statute, or on rights derived from a statute, the party prosecuting must allege, and consequently prove, every fact necessary to make out his title to the thing demanded, and his compe­tency to sue for it. Com. Dig. “Action on Stat.” A 1-3, and “Pleader,” c. 70. An in­former cannot support an action unless there be an express provision in the statute ena­bling him to sue. Rex v. Malland, 2 Strange, 828; Fleming v. Bailey, 5 East, 313. And, if the statute creating the penalty, and bestow­ing it upon the informer, does not give the mode of proceeding, he is bound to set forth the special matter upon which the right of action arises, and allege and prove in what way the penalty vests in him. Cole v. Smith, 4 Johns. 193; Bigelow v. Johnson, 13 Johns, 428; Smith v. Merwin, 15 Wend. 184; Fair­banks v. Antrim, 2 N. H. 105; Ellis v. Hull, 2 Aiken, 41. The doctrine in effect' is ap­plicable ■ to actions founded upon statutes other than for penalties; for, when a statute is made to remedy any mischief or griev­ance, or to bestow any interest or right up­on an individual, the mode of remedy, when one is designated by it, must be exactly fol­lowed. Stowell v. Flagg, 11 Mass. 364; Ste­vens v. Proprietors of Middlesex Canal, 12 Mass. 466. And, if the form of remedy is not pointed out, and the law supplies one by implication, the plaintiff must aver and prove every fact necessary to show the ex­istence of the right in him under the stat­ute. Bigelow v. Cambridge &amp; C. Turnpike Co., 7 Mass. 202; Bigelow v. Johnson, 13 Johns. 428. We think, under these well es­tablished rules of law, that the two plaintiffs prosecuting this action do not come within and satisfy the provisions of the statute giv­ing the penalty “to the person who shall sue for the same.”</p>
                <p id="b1165-3" pgmap="1165">There is a manifest distinction between giving a penalty to a common informer, and imposing one for the benefit of the person ag­grieved by the violation of the statute. In the latter case the term “person” might just­ly be regarded as comprehending every one affected by the injury; because, the design of such enactment must be to give a remedy co-extensive with the mischief or grievance provided against. This consideration has no relation to positive penalties established as sanctions of the law, and not intended to recompense individuals because of their par­ticular injuries.</p>
                <p id="b1165-4" pgmap="1165">The language of the statute is to be partic­ularly adhered to in the construction of penal laws, and, when it has a natural and plain meaning, an artificial or forced one is not to be adopted. 1 Bl. Comm. 88; Dwar. St. 707, 711; Van Valkenburgh v. Torrey, 7 Cow; 252. Courts will not give an equitable construction to a penal law, even for the purpose of embracing cases clearly within the mischief intended to be remedied. U. S. v. Sheldon, 2 Wheat. [15 U. S.] 110; My­ers v. Foster, 6 Cow. 567; Daggett v. State, 4 Conn. 61. They sedulously limit the action of penal statutes to the precise cases de­scribed in them, and reject an interpretation tending to comprehend matters not named by the legislature, although-analogous. The authorities cited are explicit to this point, and are in unison with numerous others, English and American. Cone v. Bowles, 1 Salk. 205; Reniger v. Fogossa, 1 Plowd. 17; Fleming v. Bailey, 5 East. 313.</p>
                <p id="b1165-5" pgmap="1165">The privilege of claiming or enforcing a penalty is one of statutory appointment, and must be construed with like strictness. In an action by husband and wife against exec­utors, to recover a penalty imposed by stat­ute for not proving a will within a fixed pe­riod, one-half of the penalty being given to the plaintiff and the other to the legatees, and the wife being a legatee, it was held by the supreme court of Massachusetts, that the suit could not be maintained in the name of husband and wife, the action being a popular one, and there being no joint interest in the verdict. Hill v. Davis, 4 Mass. 137. The doctrine was still more fully and explicitly declared in a later case in that court, in which it was held that several persons could not unite in a qui tarn action as informers, the right to sue in such case resting upon the express provisions of the statute. Vinton v. Welsh, 9 Pick. 87. When the penalty is given to “any person or persons,” a corpora­tion aggregate cannot sue for it 1 Kyd, Corp. 218; Weavers’ Co. v. Forrest 2 Strange, marg. p. 1241. Hammond, in his treatise on Parties (48), says: “It seems two cannot join as common informers in a penal action, un­less specially allowed by statute.”</p>
                <p id="b1165-8" pgmap="1165">The plain language and sense of the stat­ute under consideration, restrict the right of action to a single person; and we should' not be disposed, on general principles, to en­large its operation, so as to encourage asso­ciations of individuals in instituting and con­ducting penal actions, the nature of those actions in our opinion exacting a rigorous ad­herence to the terms of the law.</p>
                <p id="b1165-9" pgmap="1165">Judgment is accordingly rendered in this case for the demurrant, with costs; and the same judgment is rendered in the ten other suits between the same parties on like plead­ings.</p>
                <p id="b1165-10" pgmap="1165">In taxing the defendant’s costs on the de­murrers in the eleven cases, several ques­tions arose. The costs were taxed by the clerk. There were eleven bills of costs all alike. 1. There were two sets of charges in each bill for putting in special bail, the bail first put in not having justified. 2. Each bill contained charges for a rule to declare, and for services in obtaining security for costs, the attorneys in each suit being the same, and there being but one rule in each matter, and but one set of papers, in which the titles of all the causes were included. 3. Each contained a charge for perusing de­murrer by counsel. 4. Each contained a charge for a rule to join in demurrer, there being a separate rule in each suit. 5. Each contained charges for five demurrer books, and for brief and points, and for attorney and counsel fees on argument, there having been but one argument in fact for all the cases. The plaintiffs appealed to the court from the taxation as to the above items.</p>
                <p id="b1165-11" pgmap="1165(14) 1166(199)">NELSON, Circuit Justice. 1. The second set of charges for putting in special bail should have been stricken out, because they were incurred by the neglect of the defend­ant in not causing the bail first put in to justify, and for his own benefit. 2. The de­fendant’s attorney is not entitled to a sep­arate charge in each suit for the services em­braced in this item. The settled practice is against the allowance. Jackson v. Keller, 18 Johns. 310; Schermerhorn v. Noble, 1 Denio, 682. 3. This item is taxable in each suit Rule 27, Cir. Ct. U. S. 4. It is urged that this item is distinguishable from the second, because there was a separate rule in ■each suit. But the principle is the same, and has been so held since the ease of Jack­son v. Clark, 4 Cow. 532. There can be but one charge for the service, as respects attor­ney’s fees. 5. The demurrer books, and brief and points, are taxable in each case, if they were actually made out in each at the time of the argument. The fact must be shown to the taxing officer, if objection be made to the charge. Attorney and counsel fees on argument are taxable in each case.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="1163" ORDERLABEL="1161" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00582_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00582_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00582_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_1163.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00582_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="1164" ORDERLABEL="1162" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00582_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00582_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00582_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_1164.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00582_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="1165" ORDERLABEL="1163" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00583_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00583_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00583_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_1165.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00583_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="1166" ORDERLABEL="1164" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00583_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00583_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00583_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_1166.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00583_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Am-o" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0634"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1163.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00582_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1163.15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00582_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1165-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0634"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1165.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00583_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1165-11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0634"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1165.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00583_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1166.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00583_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1164-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0634"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1164.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00582_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1165-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0634"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1165.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00583_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1165-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0634"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1165.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00583_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1165-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0634"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1165.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00583_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1165-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0634"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1165.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00583_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1165.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00583_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1164-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0634"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1164.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00582_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1165-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0634"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1165.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00583_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1164-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0634"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1164.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00582_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1164-14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0634"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1164.17" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00582_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1165.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00583_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1164-13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0634"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1164.16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00582_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1164-12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0634"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1164.15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00582_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1164-11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0634"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1164.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00582_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1163-13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0634"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1163.19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00582_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1163-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0634"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1163.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00582_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1164-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0634"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1164.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00582_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="ARIQ" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0634"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1164.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00582_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1164.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00582_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1164.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00582_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1163-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0634"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1163.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00582_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1163-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0634"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1163.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00582_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1163-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0634"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1163.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00582_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
