<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044049817315_0402" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="C.C.D. Md." jurisdiction="United States">United States Circuit Court for the District of Maryland</court>
          <name abbreviation="Johnson v. Onion">JOHNSON v. ONION et al.</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 7,401</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">13 F. Cas. 777</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">3 Hughes, 290; 4 Fish. Pat. Cas. 170; 3 Am. Law T. 285</citation>
          <decisiondate>1870-04</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-10T00:25:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:27:33Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:41:28Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00390_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="74479922a23b53a02659a7a05ee60582" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="88926">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00390_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00390_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="e0c4726c7d146dfc1b7be02cee5e0f6e" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="114212">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00390_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00391_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="4b39c4e0b72d89c44d4f5110a1e4b309" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="76072">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00391_0.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00390_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="eeb4325b805e68474f8f9f6a575b028c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3348930">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00390_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00390_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="0628832940f238fd7d4fad87826db899" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3805433">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00390_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00391_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="b10c72d5f4b0709c966b7dd155638a3d" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2991595">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00391_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00390_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="be8ad08b4558d28f0cd2795e82ee8f34" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="194908">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00390_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00390_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="e51e2da2d45601ecc2f7879da25e60a8" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="251415">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00390_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00391_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="0988812c173cc86ee3a1ae3cf13297e6" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="168967">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00391_0.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0402" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="779" firstpage="777">
              <court pgmap="779" id="ArQ1">Circuit Court, D. Maryland.</court>
              <docketnumber pgmap="779" id="b779-8">Case No. 7,401.</docketnumber>
              <citation pgmap="779" id="ACHF">[3 Hughes, 290;<footnotemark>1</footnotemark> 4 Fish. Pat. Cas. 170; 3 Am. Law T. 285.]</citation>
              <parties pgmap="779" id="AQte">JOHNSON v. ONION et al.</parties>
              <decisiondate pgmap="779" id="A6K">April, 1870.</decisiondate>
              <attorneys pgmap="779" id="b779-18">R. Mason. Wm. Pinkney Whyte, and Chas. JU. Keller, for complainant.</attorneys>
              <attorneys pgmap="779" id="b779-19">F. Nevitt Steele and F. H. B. Latrobe, for defendants.</attorneys>
              <footnote label="1">
                <p pgmap="779" id="b779-21">1 [Reported by Hon. Robert W. Hughes, Dis­trict Judge, and by Samuel S. Fisher. Esq., and here compiled and reprinted by permission. The syllabus and opinion are from 3 Hughes, 290. and the statement is from 4 Fish. Pat. Cas. 170.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author pgmap="779" id="b779-20">GILES. District Judge.</author>
                <p pgmap="779(47) 780(252)" id="AIAd">The bill is filed in this cause for an injunction and an account, etc. It sets forth that on the 15th May. 1S55. Jacob A. Conover, a citizen of the United States, obtained letters patent of the United States, granting to him for the term of four­teen years the full and exclusive right of making, etc., the invention and improvement set forth and described in the specifications annexed to said patent, and that by assign­ments duly executed and recorded, all the rights under said patent in and for the state of Maryland have become vested in the com­plainant, and that he has full authority to sue for and recover for all infringements thereof in the state. That the said patent has been sustained as a valid patent in sev­eral suits in New York; one, a suit at law for damages brought by the patentee against one John H. Rapp, in which Conover recov­ered a verdict, and in which suit it was deter­mined that Conover was the first and orig­inal inventor of the improved wood-splitting machine described in said patent That said patentee subsequently obtained an injunc­tion against John R. Dohrman and John H. .Peipho, to restrain them from infringing said patent. And by the supplemental bill, it appears that since the filing of the original bill in this cause the term of fourteen years for which the said patent was granted has expired; and that the commissioner of pat­ents, upon due application made, and a hear­ing before him, granted an extension of said patent for seven years; and that since the said extension the said patentee has duly as­signed to complainant the same rights which he, complainant, held under the original pat­ent in and for this state.</p>
                <p pgmap="780" id="b780-4">The answer sets up several defences: 1st They deny that Conover was the first and original inventor of the machine described in his patent. 2d. That the verdict of Conover v. Rapp [Case No. 3.124] was a collusive one; that the principal question discussed by Judge Shipman, in the case against Dohrman &amp; Peipho was the question of infringement; and they also, to show that Conover was not the first and original inventor of the machine described in his patent, gave notice of sever­al patents previously granted, which they will rely on in the trial of this case. Dur­ing this litigation, as X have before stated, the patent expired and the extension was granted; and in the answer of the defend­ants to the amended and supplemental bill, the defence set up is that the extension of' the said patent is void, as the application for the same was not filed ninety days before the expiration of the said patent.</p>
                <p pgmap="780" id="b780-5">Now, the first question that presents itself in the consideration of this cause is. was the extension of the patent by the commis­sioner legally granted? or, in other words, was the application for the extension filed “at least ninety days before the expiration of the patent?” Upon this question I have had no difficulty. The patent expired on the last hour of the 15th May, 18CÜ, and the ap­plication for the extension was filed on the 13th February, 1S09. The day on which the application is filed is included, and you have therefore ninety days before the expiration of the patent. In support of the propriety of counting the day upon which the applica­tion is filed in the calculation of the ninety days, I refer to the cases of Griffith v. Bo­gerts, 38 How. [59 U. S.] 163; Sheets v. Sel­den’s Lessee, 2 Wall. [69 U. S.] 190; State v. Schnierle, 5 Rich. Law. 299; Thomas v. Ar­fick, 16 Pa. St. 14; Chiles v. Smith, 13 B. Mon. 461. In [Griffith v. Bogerts] 18 How. [59 U. S.] 165, the supreme court say: “Where the construction of the language is doubtful, courts will always prefer that which will confirm rather than destroy any bona fide transaction or title.” It is clear to me, there­fore, that this application for extension of the letters was in time, under the act of 1861, § 12 [12 Stat. 248].</p>
                <p pgmap="780" id="b780-7">The next question is, what is the true con­struction of Conover's patent? He makes three claims; they are all for combinations. He does not claim, as new, any of the con­stituent elements of his combinations. His first claim is in these words: “What I claim as my invention, and desire to secure by let­ters patent, is the movable bed or carriage for carrying and advancing the blocks of wood in combination with the reciprocating cutters operating at right angles with the surface of the bed or carriage, substantially as and for the purpose specified.”</p>
                <p pgmap="780(326) 781(628)" id="b780-8">Now the counsel for the defendants con­tend that the movable bed or carriage, named in said claim, can only mean a movable bed with flanges on the side, as described in said patent. It is true that Judge Hall, in his able charge to the jury in the case of Cono­ver v. Roach [Case No. 3,125], held that it meant a movable bed or carriage as de­scribed in patentee’s specifications — that is, having flanges on its side to keep the wood firm and in place. Judge Ingersoll does not touch this question in his decision in the case of Conover v. Rapp [supra], and in that case there does not appear to have been any argument made upon the flanges at all. Judge Shipman is very clear in his construc­tion of the patent in the case against Dohr-­man &amp; Peipho. He says: “The construc­tion and operation of the machine described in the patent are substantially as follows: a bed or carriage composed of sections, link­ed together in the form of an endless chain, which is made to travel over a table and around drivers or wheels placed at each end. Blocks of wood of required length of mate­rial for fuel are placed upright on this bed. Over the bed, at the point where the block is to receive the blow which splits it, is a cutter, made in the form of a cross, so that the block may be split into small sticks in-, stead of slabs or boards, as would be the case if the cutter was composed of only ose straight blade. The bed, with the block thereon, is put in motion by an intermittent feed, and the block advanced under the cut­ter at every throw of the feed mechanism, measured by the range at which the feed mechanism is set. The cutter firmly fas­tened above to a stock, as the block passes-­under it, works up and down with a recip­rocating motion, splitting the block as it descends, and then raising from it so that it .may be carried by the bed a step forward, when it descends and splits again. As the blades of the cutter rise they are cleared of any pieces of wood that may be clinging to them, by a clearing plate fixed above, and into which the cutter plays freely as it rises or falls through apertures or mortices in the plate. When the machine is in motion the bed not only carries the blocks to the point where they are split by the cutters, but it also carries off the wood after it is split.” It must be seen that he says nothing about flanges. I incline to the construction which claims a movable bed, with or with­out flanges. While in his specifications the patentee describes his movable bed with flanges, yet he assigns to them no specific function. Other parts have their functions assigned, but these flanges have not. No doubt the bed is better with the flanges, and that may be his preferred mode of making it, but it is no part of his patent. Had it been intended by him to make the flanges a part of his patent he would have referred to them and made them a part of his claims. But he makes no mention of the flanges in his several claims at the close of his specifi­cations, his claim being only “for the mov­able bed or carriage for carrying and ad­vancing the block of wood in combination,” etc. But the wood is held under the knives by the clearing plate as described in the patent I should therefore think that if the wood could be split without the flanges, and I see no reason why it could not, the flanges were not essential parts of the Conover pat­ent, although they would no doubt be an im­provement on it. I admit this is a doubtful point, but it makes no difficulty in this case, because I hold that the machine used by the defendants is an infringement of the plain­tiff’s patent even in this particular. In this case the machine used by the defendants, represented in the model J. H. J., No. 6, clearly infringes the Conover patent. Never was there a clearer case of infringement. Here is thermovable bed or carriage, substan­tially the same as that described in the pat­ent, the reciprocating cutters operating at right angles with the surface of the bed or carriage substantially as described in the patent, and these devices operate substan­tially in the same way as described in the patent. In the machines of the defendants, as it is alleged they are now used, the outside slab or bar of wood has been removed, and a Y knife is used instead of a knife cruci­form in shape, but in my opinion the ma­chine so modified would have in substance the same means of supporting the blocks lat­erally, as the machine described in the pat­ent, for the slab or inner bar of wood, next to the frame, affords the effective lateral support to the block of wood at the moment when such support is most needed. The proof, however, shows that the outer side or slab of wood was upon the machines when this bill was.filed, but I hold that, with or without the sides, it is a clear infringement to use such a machine. Nor is it necessary to resort to the doctrine of equivalents in this case, for the matter is t8o clear for dis­pute. See Winans v. Denmead, 15 How. [56 U. S.] 342.</p>
                <p pgmap="781" id="b781-5">It is maintained also by the counsel for the defendants that George Page invented and made a machine which antedates the Cono-­ver patent.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="779" ORDERLABEL="777" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00390_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00390_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00390_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_779.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00390_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="780" ORDERLABEL="778" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00390_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00390_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00390_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_780.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00390_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="781" ORDERLABEL="779" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00391_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00391_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00391_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_781.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00391_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b779-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0402"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_779.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00390_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="A6K" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0402"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_779.16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00390_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b780-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0402"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_780.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00390_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b780-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0402"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_780.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00390_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b780-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0402"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_780.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00390_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_780.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00390_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b779-21" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0402"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_779.26" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00390_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b779-19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0402"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_779.22" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00390_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="ACHF" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0402"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_779.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00390_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AIAd" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0402"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_779.24" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00390_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_779.25" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00390_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_780.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00390_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="ArQ1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0402"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_779.15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00390_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b781-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0402"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_781.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00391_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b779-18" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0402"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_779.21" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00390_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AQte" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0402"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_779.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00390_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b779-20" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0402"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_779.23" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00390_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b780-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0402"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_780.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00390_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_781.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00391_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_781.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00391_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
