<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044049817315_0169" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="C.C.D.R.I." jurisdiction="United States">United States Circuit Court for the District of Rhode Island</court>
          <name abbreviation="James v. Atlantic Delaine Co.">JAMES v. ATLANTIC DELAINE CO. et al.</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 7,177</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">13 F. Cas. 291</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">3 Cliff. 614</citation>
          <decisiondate>1867-11</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-10T00:25:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:27:33Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:41:27Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00147_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="1b14e54f4a6d2899c4abddbbe9ec2e31" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="86234">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00147_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00147_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="7ddefe30c109cb9f6c5e4da5a6e61302" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="6732">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00147_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00148_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="2b53536a715beafe7ed12983de8f05bc" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="91100">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00148_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00148_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="be6997ded10b68fde07d8ba6e15c8924" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="105140">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00148_1.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00147_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="316bea45a77f23e9d93d0750fabed499" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3368303">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00147_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00147_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="8254f804a0f9083a5c09acd8ddf833ba" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="1065965">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00147_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00148_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="ff397b24411673e71b8a64998d170b3c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3265365">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00148_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00148_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="39f13f0070386f87a77f2b17ebc8f18b" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3731059">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00148_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00147_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="f0d208638ae48cda0a8281804dce7bbd" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="188294">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00147_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00147_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="7dbf88a4303453d7403f9b1d3ede42d3" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="1924">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00147_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00148_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="09165b40e08d7dd9b441106b1451edd1" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="190111">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00148_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00148_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="2d77ea8590a733b7533d86163c025903" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="227546">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00148_1.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0169" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="294" firstpage="291">
              <court pgmap="293" id="AFH6">Circuit Court, D. Rhode Island.</court>
              <docketnumber pgmap="293" id="b293-20">Case No. 7,177.</docketnumber>
              <citation pgmap="293" id="Al2">[3 Cliff. 614.] <footnotemark>2</footnotemark>
              </citation>
              <parties pgmap="293" id="Aoy">JAMES v. ATLANTIC DELAINE CO. et al.</parties>
              <decisiondate pgmap="293" id="AmK">Nov. Term, 1867.</decisiondate>
              <attorneys pgmap="295" id="b295-3">J. H. Parsons, T. A. Jencks, and Caleb Cushing, for complainant.</attorneys>
              <attorneys pgmap="295" id="b295-4">Abraham Payne and R. W. Greene, for re­spondents.</attorneys>
              <footnote label="2">
                <p pgmap="293" id="b293-26">2 [Reported by William Henry Clifford, Esq., and here reprinted by permission.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author pgmap="295" id="b295-5">CLIFFORD, Circuit Justice.</author>
                <p pgmap="295" id="A1G">Before pro­ceeding to' consider the merits of the issue, it becomes necessary to determine the ques­tion as to the competency of certain wit­nesses examined by the respondents. Two depositions, to wit, that of George W. Cha-­pin and that of Lyman B. Frieze, offered by the respondents, are objected to by the complainant, because they are parties to the suit. They were both taken (as now offer­ed) subsequent to the passage of the Act of the 3d of March, 1865, which provides that in actions by or against executors, ad­ministrators, or guardians, in which judg­ment may be rendered for or against them, neither party shall be allowed to testify against the other as to any transaction with or statement by the testator, intestate, or ward, unless called to testify thereto by the opposite party, or required to testify there­to by the court. 13 Stat. 533. The original complainant died in October, . 1862, intes­tate, as appears by the record. Tested by the foregoing provision alone, it is quite clear that the deponents are not competent witnesses to testify against the present com­plainant as to any transaction with or state­ment by her intestate, as they were not called to testify by the opposite party, nor required to testify by the court. Applica­tion for such an order was never made to the court, and none such was ever passed in the case. None of the prior proceedings have any effect to take the two depositions out of the operation of that provision of law. Both of the deponents gave depositions in the case before the first hearing upon the merits. They were taken at that time also by the respondents upon the ground that the prac­tice of the state courts furnished the rule of decision; but they were stricken out by the order of the court before the hearing, because parties, except in certain special cases, were not, under the general rules of equity law, competent witnesses in suits in equity, as previously, decided by this court. Subsequently the parties. were heard, and the case was held under advisement; but the court, at the June term, ordered that the same should be reargued, and thereupon it was ordered, tipon motion and consent of parties, that the time for taking further tes­timony be extended to the 1st of November, in the same year.. In the meantime the complainant died, and the cause being reviv­ed, the time for taking testimony was ex­tended from time to time, until the 1st of April, 1865, as appears in the supplemental record. Suffice it to say, that both of these depositions were taken subsequent to the act of the 3d of March, 1865, and the ques­tion of the competency of the deponents is controlled by that provision.</p>
                <p pgmap="295" id="b295-8">Any restatement of the facts proved, ex­cept to a limited extent, is unnecessary, as they are succinctly stated in the narrative of the case. The execution of the contract and of the mortgage is admitted, and there is no controversy as to the deed of assign­ment and.the appointment of the assignee in insolvency. Satisfactory proof, also, is exhibited that he completed the contract, and that the buildings and machinery were accepted by the other contracting parties. The respondents admit that the mutual re­leases as between the company and. the as-­signee, as set forth in the bill of complaint, were duly executed. The effect of these several instruments was, that the entire in­terest of the original complainant in the company property and in the capital stock, and his entire interest In the mortgaged es­tate, passed into the hands of the respond­ent corporation. Mention is not made of the fact that the mortgage was executed to the treasurer of the company, as it is not controverted that he held it as trustee for the company. The corporation respondents claimed a lien upon the stock held by the original complainant, under the provisions of their charter; and it is fully proved that their treasurer in' February, 1853, advertis­ed the other mortgaged property for sale, and that they were prevented from carry­ing out their intention by the injunction suit prosecuted by . the assignee. They also claimed damages for the delay in comple­tion of the contract, but the' original com­plainant claimed a much larger sum for moneys expended in extra work not includ­ed in the contract.</p>
                <p pgmap="295(30) 296(63)" id="b295-9">Full proof is also exhibited that the treas­urer of the respondent corporation was sev­eral times requested to furnish a true state­ment of the accounts between the parties, and that the only one he ever did present deserving the name is the one he presented, or caused to be presented, to the assignee, and which was used as .the basis of the com­putations at the date of the settlement. Be­yond question, that statement was inaccu­rate in large amounts, and greatly so to the prejudice of the original complainant.</p>
                <p pgmap="296" id="b296-3">Viewed in every aspect, it is the conclu­sion of the court, not only that it was false, but that it was furnished with the intent to deceive and defraud, by promoting a set­tlement prejudicial to the original complainant and more favorable to therespondent corpora­tion than truth and justice would admit. Such being the views of the court, it is clear that the complainant is entitled to a decree, unless some one or more of the de­fenses can be sustained.</p>
                <p pgmap="296" id="b296-4">The settled rule of law is, that the as­signor in such a case is entitled to the res­idue of the estate, after his debts outstanding at the date of the assignment are paid. Halsey v. Fairbanks [Case No. 5,964]; Brash­ear v. West, 7 Pet. [32 U. S.] 608. By the ex-­tinguishment of the debts, the assignee be­came the trustee of the complainant; and the .latter, as the assignor, became clothed with all the rights and powers of a cestui que trust to the same extent as the creditors previously had whose claims he had extin­guished. Lazarus v. Com. Ins. Co., 5 Pick. 81. Consequently the complainant was the proper party to come into a court of equity, and pursue the trust estate, it appearing that it had been fraudulently or improperly part­ed with by the trustee. Story, Eq. Pl. § 221; Oliver v. Piatt, 3 How. [44 U. S.] 400; Lewin, Trusts, 730; Hovenden v. Lord Annesley, 2 Schoales &amp; L. 633. Where the purposes of the trust have been satisfied, equity in a. proper case will compel a conveyance from the trustee to cestui que trust, as he has the sole beneficial interest.</p>
                <p pgmap="296" id="b296-5">The argument for the respondent is that these principles cannot apply in this case, be­cause it' appears that two of the debts of the original complainant have not been paid. Much weight would be given to that objec­tion as between the assignor and assignee, if the estate continued in the latter, and he was still engaged in executing the trust; but when it appears that the trust property has been fraudulently or improperly con­veyed to another, not as a means of execut­ing, but as a means of extinguishing the re-­versionary interest of the assignor, the objec­tion cannot be sustained. The rights of such creditors in such a case will be protected in the deeree granting relief. Want of dili­gence in the institution of the suit is another defense much pressed in the argument. The record shows that the mutual releases were executed on the 2d of March, 1853; and the bill of complaint was filed on the 1st of March, 1859, before the claim was barred by the statute of limitations. But the argument is, that staleness of claim is often admitted in equity as a good answer to a' bill of com­plaint, when the period which has elapsed is less than the time required as a legal bar to a common-law suit, and the proposition is correct, as was held by this court, and has since been affirmed in the supreme court. Badger v. Badger, 2 Wall. [69 U. S.] 94. The correctness of that rule, properly ap­plied, cannot be doubted, but it is equally clear that it should seldom or never be ap­plied in cases of trust, where the means of knowledge are wholly or even chiefly on one side. When the fraud charged and proved consists of misrepresentations and conceal-­ments, courts of equity are reluctant to ap: ply the rule at all, unless it appear that the rights of innocent third parties will be in­juriously affected if that defense is over­ruled. The affairs of the complainant had become much complicated, and the evidence' shows that the mutual releases were execut­ed without his consent and against his wishes. He lost by the arrangement, not only all claim to the possession or control of the property, but all direct means of consult­ing the books and papers containing the evi­dence of his rights. Looking at the circum­stances of the case, I am clearly of the opin­ion that it is one where equity will apply that rule. Provost v. Gratz, 6 Wheat. [19 U. S.] 481; Michoud v. Girod, 4 How. [45 U. S.] 503; Baker v. Whiting [Case No. 787]; 2 Story, Eq. Jur. §§ 15, 20.</p>
                <p pgmap="296" id="b296-8">The details of the evidence have purpose­ly been avoided, as the case is one, if the de­cree be for the complainant, which must go to a master, where further testimony may be taken as to amounts.' The conclusion of the court is, that the complainant is entitled to a decree; that the release of March 2, 1853, given by the assignee to the respondent cor­poration, is void, and that the same be set aside as having been obtained by fraudulent representation and concealment; and also to a decree for an account, including an account of all assigned and mortgaged property, sub­ject to the payment of the debts, if any, due to the creditors of the assignor, as secured in the instrument of assignment, reserving all further orders or decrees as for other specific relief or otherwise, until the true state of the accounts is fully ascertained. Decree ac­cordingly, and the case must be referred to a master, to state the account for the consider­ation of the court.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="293" ORDERLABEL="291" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00147_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00147_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00147_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_293.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00147_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="294" ORDERLABEL="292" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00147_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00147_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00147_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_294.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00147_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="295" ORDERLABEL="293" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00148_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00148_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00148_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_295.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00148_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="296" ORDERLABEL="294" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00148_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00148_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00148_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_296.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00148_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b296-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0169"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_296.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00148_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b295-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0169"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_295.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00148_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b296-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0169"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_296.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00148_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_296.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00148_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="A1G" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0169"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_295.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00148_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_295.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00148_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_295.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00148_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b293-26" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0169"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_293.36" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00147_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b293-20" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0169"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_293.28" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00147_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b296-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0169"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_296.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00148_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AmK" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0169"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_293.32" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00147_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_293.33" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00147_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b295-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0169"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_295.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00148_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_296.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00148_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Al2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0169"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_293.30" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00147_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b296-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0169"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_296.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00148_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b295-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0169"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_295.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00148_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b295-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0169"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_295.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00148_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b295-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0169"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_295.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00148_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AFH6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0169"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_293.31" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00147_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Aoy" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0169"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_293.29" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00147_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
