<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044046873683_0284" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="D.S.C." jurisdiction="United States">United States District Court for the District of South Carolina</court>
          <name abbreviation="Ellison v. The Bellona">ELLISON et al. v. The BELLONA</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 4,407</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">8 F. Cas. 559</citation>
          <decisiondate>1798-09</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-12T19:40:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-26T10:42:09Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-26T10:56:34Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00281_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="a02d0de5f8f10b6a50ed302504f4d437" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="100962">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00281_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00281_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="245ab628f8a7ef43db8f51a8c541e083" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="41478">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00281_1.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00281_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="70c04607c7b4c3391ed97ddf23fc6197" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3620442">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00281_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00281_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="e63ba340e778f9edabcb3ac42e2ccea4" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2061499">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00281_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00281_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="703f435b330377407616630a60ceac35" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="215199">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00281_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00281_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="ebc34f9259f241dd9bf39ec341d889fe" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="85622">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00281_1.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0284" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="560" firstpage="559">
              <court id="b561-6" pgmap="561">District Court, D. South Carolina.</court>
              <docketnumber id="b561-3" pgmap="561">Case No. 4,407.</docketnumber>
              <parties id="b561-4" pgmap="561">ELLISON et al. v. The BELLONA.</parties>
              <decisiondate id="AoU" pgmap="561">Sept., 1798.</decisiondate>
              <judges id="b561-13" pgmap="561">Before BEE, District Judge.</judges>
              <p id="b561-5" pgmap="561">[Bee, 112.]<footnotemark>1</footnotemark>
              </p>
              <footnote label="1">
                <p id="b561-16" pgmap="561">1 [Reported by Hon. Thomas Bee, District Judge.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <p id="b561-14" pgmap="561">In arguing this plea to the jurisdiction of the court, two grounds were taken. 1st. The law of nations. 2d. The 25th article of the treaty between Great Britain and the United States.</p>
                <p id="b561-15" pgmap="561">Under the first head it was contended that, as this is a vessel of war equipped by a foreign power for capturing vessels of its enemy, and furnished with articles peculiar to such vessels and different from the com­mon engagements made by merchant sea­men, the court cannot interfere on this oc­casion. It is undoubtedly true (and so ad­judged in Moitez v. The South Carolina [Case No. 9,697]) that mariners enlisting on board a ship of war or vessel belonging to a sovereign independent state, cannot libel for wages due; and the reason is that sea­men in such case look to the government of their nation, by whom they are employed, and who undertake that they shall be paid. In privateers, whose' commissions are alto­gether of a warlike nature, it is settled by contract between the owners and crew what share of prize each party may claim; and before the seamen become entitled, the valid­ity of every prize must be determined. This can only be ascertained by a court of the nation to which the captors belong; neutral nations have no sort of jurisdiction therein. But the case is materially different with re­spect to letters of marque, which are trading vessels, armed, and commissioned to cruize occasionally. The Bellona is one of these. It appears that she was fitted out at Leith, on a voyage to Jamaica with a cargo of great value, consigned to the captain and another person on board. The crew, con­sisting of about forty men, was shipped un­der articles. The vessel arrived at Jamaica, where this crew quitted her from some mo­tive of dissatisfaction as to the further voy­age; and a new crew’ was shipped under new articles which describe the new voyage, and stipulate what wages should be paid. It appears that part of the cargo on board was on freight to La Vera Cruz, and that, when this should be landed, the vessel was to cruize for six weeks. For the regulation of this cruize another set of articles was signed, by which it was fixed that the own­ers were to have three fourths of all prizes, and the seamen the remainder. The stipu­lated wages are decisive of the commercial character of this vessel, and distinguish her from a privateer.</p>
                <p id="b561-18" pgmap="561">Courts of admiralty have a general juris­diction in causes civil and maritime; and the 9th section of the judiciary act of con­gress vests that power in this court. The case of seamen’s wages comes within this description of causes; and this jurisdiction has been uniformly exercised by me, as re­gards foreigners generally. The consular convention with France formed a single ex­ception in relation to seamen of that nation. If, then, the court is entitled to look into and decide upon the articles of seamen en­gaged on board a merchant vessel, shall that jurisdiction be ousted .merely because the vessel is armed? In cases of bottomry and hypothecation, the power of the court seems to be conceded; why not in the case of wages also? If a vessel arrive here and it appear that the voyage was to end, or the seamen to be discharged, in this port, no objection could be made to the enforcement of the contract It is the daily ' practice of our courts, as well ás those of England; both are guided by the lex loci, and regulate their decisions accordingly. I very lately dis­charged two seamen from a Britirli armed ship, because it appeared by the articles that they had engaged only to come to this port. The 25th article of the treaty with Great Britain has been relied on in the second place. But this evidently relates merely to prizes. It is found in all our treaties, and generally in those between commercial na­tions possessed of a naval power. It pro­vides that the neutral power shall not take cognizance of prizes, and permits the captor to have an asylum in our ports till he shall see fit to proceed, with his prize, to the ports of his own nation. But this by no means excludes jurisdiction as to incidental mat­ters not connected with the question of prize. Before this provision by treaty, neutral courts were frequently induced to restore prizes brought within their jurisdictional limits; that practice is effectually restrained by the clause relied on.</p>
                <p id="b561-19" pgmap="561">Yet there are cases even of prize where this court will interfere. It will restore Ameri­can vessels brought as prize into this port. It will divest a French- privateer of his Brit­ish or Dutch prize taken within our juris­dictional limits, or by a vessel fitted out in our harbours. French prizes, under similar circumstances would be restored, without re­gard to the claim of a British or other captor. Each of these cases has occurred, been de­cided, and confirmed in every stage of ap­peal. The law is therefore, fixed.</p>
                <p id="b561-20" pgmap="561(9) 562(241)">But it is said that this power of discliarg-­ing the crew of an armed vessel amounts to a power of laying her under embargo, for that she is prohibited by our laws from re­cruiting in our ports. In support of this ar­gument, the act of congress of June, 1794 [1 Stat. SSI], was quoted. That act is de­claratory of the law of nations, confirms all tue doctrine cited from Vattel, and provides, inter alia, that no foreign armed vessel shall add to her force, within our ports, by aug­menting the number of her guns or other equipment solely applicable to war, nor en­list men for the service of a foreign state. But it has been determined, under this clause, that repairs necessary to put a vessel in statu quo, alterations in the manner of her equipment (without adding to her force) and the shipping of men to the amount of the original number that composed the crew, are not such infractions of the treaty as call for the interference of the court. If every man in the Bellona were changed, I should decide that our neutrality was not commit­ted, provided the ship carried out the same number, and no more, that she brought in. I should willingly have got rid of the trouble that must attend an investigation of the merits of this cause. But I hold myself bound by law to retain the suit, and to direct that the claimant answer over.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="561" ORDERLABEL="559" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00281_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00281_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00281_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_561.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00281_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="562" ORDERLABEL="560" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00281_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00281_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00281_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_562.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00281_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b561-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0284"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_561.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00281_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b561-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0284"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_561.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00281_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b561-20" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0284"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_561.21" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00281_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_562.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00281_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b561-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0284"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_561.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00281_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b561-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0284"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_561.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00281_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AoU" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0284"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_561.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00281_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b561-18" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0284"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_561.19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00281_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b561-19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0284"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_561.20" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00281_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b561-13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0284"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_561.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00281_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b561-14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0284"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_561.15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00281_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b561-15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0284"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_561.16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00281_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_561.17" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00281_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b561-16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0284"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_561.18" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00281_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
