<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044049817315_0270" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="N.D. Ill." jurisdiction="United States">United States District Court for the Northern District of Illinois</court>
          <name abbreviation="Jenkins v. Mayer">JENKINS v. MAYER</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 7,272</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">13 F. Cas. 529</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">2 Biss. 303; 3 N. B. R. 776</citation>
          <decisiondate>1870-05</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-10T00:25:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:27:33Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:41:27Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00266_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="09c2a48c372ad718ca09839a91bc7f28" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="89194">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00266_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00266_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="71a241ca589f0d77ede7b0556289cdc6" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="108522">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00266_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00267_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="5053e0688cd60c44a940b421d53f95e5" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="64664">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00267_0.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00266_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="172fc080436cb2b182d5b17cb7f1dfb4" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3791555">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00266_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00266_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="3f4274a2a231fcca728168dd35d741fd" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3714968">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00266_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00267_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="d947cf3bbd0aecc290ff61c27126b9c6" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3141077">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00267_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00266_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="3c3af5eb49cb5db563bd291b7e9064a2" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="195556">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00266_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00266_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="71710d15028bb1e4bd8e567d95c604d8" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="239854">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00266_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00267_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="b4bd43ea0c02a8d702b2767b19eaf020" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="134663">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00267_0.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0270" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="531" firstpage="529">
              <court pgmap="531" id="ATJ">District Court, N. D. Illinois.</court>
              <docketnumber pgmap="531" id="b531-3">Case No. 7,272.</docketnumber>
              <citation pgmap="531" id="b531-5">[2 Biss. 303: <footnotemark>1</footnotemark> 3 N. B. R. 776 (Quarto. 189).]</citation>
              <parties pgmap="531" id="b531-4">JENKINS v. MAYER.</parties>
              <decisiondate pgmap="531" id="AHV">May Term, 1870.</decisiondate>
              <attorneys pgmap="531" id="b531-14">Rich &amp; Noble, for assignee.</attorneys>
              <attorneys pgmap="531" id="b531-15">Hoyne, Horton &amp; Hoyne, for defendant.</attorneys>
              <footnote label="1">
                <p pgmap="531" id="b531-18">1 [Reported by Josiah H. Bissell, Esq., and here reprinted by permission.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author pgmap="531" id="b531-16">BLODGETT, District Judge.</author>
                <p pgmap="531" id="ApO">The facts elicited in the evidence are substantially these: Up to some time in August. 1809, the bankrupt Heffron and one A. H. Hovey were in partnership as seedsmen and flo­rists, and also as dealers in statuary, pic­tures and works of art. For the better transaction of the latter branch of their business, they had a “fine art gallery.” where articles in that line were exhibited and remained for sale on commission. In the course of this business Constant Mayer, one of the respondents, had forwarded to them a valuable picture, entitled “Good "Words.” to be sold on commission.</p>
                <p pgmap="531(668) 532(199)" id="b531-17">In August the co-partnership was dis­solved. and the business of the firm contin­ued by Heffron. In September or October this picture was sold for $3.000, to be paid for about the 1st of November. Some time in September Heffron left Chicago for the East, and entrusted the general manage­ment of his business to his former partner, Mr. A. H. Hovey, who had power to sign checks and notes. In the latter part of Oc­tober a note of Heffron’s came due at one of the banks in this city, and Hovey. hav­ing no other available resources, collected the amount due on the picture sold for May­er. and used the proceeds for the payment of the note. Heffron. who was at the time at Utica, N. Y., on business, on being ad­vised of this act on the part of his agent, wrote to Mayer, apologizing for the .use of his money, and enclosing his draft at thirty days for the amount. On the receipt of this letter, Mayer at once wrote to Messrs. Hoyne, Horton &amp; Hoyne. his attorneys here, directing them to proceed to collect the mon­ey at once by attachment, and denouncing Heffron for this unauthorized use of his money. When this letter came to the hands of Mayer's attorneys here, Heffron was still absent, and Hovey in the general charge of his business. The attorneys called upon Hovey for a settlement of their client’s de­mand, and informed him of their instruc­tions in the premises. Hovey assured the attorneys that Heffron was abundantly sol­vent and able to pay his debts, but that he was unavoidably detained at the. East by the illness of his wife, and that when he returned, which they expected would be in a few days, the money would certainly be paid, and proffered them security if they would not commence suit. The result of the interview was that Hovey. as attorney and agent for Heffron. made and executed a bill of sale under seal, absolute on its face, to Mayer for a lot of pictures, works of art, and other property, the value of which was about $5.400, as stated in the schedule there­of, but the real purpose of which was to make Mayer secure for the amount of his funds thus appropriated to Heffron’s use by Hovey. At the same time this bill of sale was executed by Hovey the property de­scribed therein was nominally turned over to J. Albert Hovey, a young man who seems to have been partially employed about the premises, to hold for Mayer; but the goods were not removed from the store, nor their visible possession and ownership changed. It is conceded that A. H. Hovey had no au­thority under seal to execute the bill of sale, his sole authority in writing resting on a letter from Heffron, authorizing him to sign checks and notes, and attend to his, Heff-­ron’s. business. About the 1st of December Heffron returned, and resumed the control of his affairs. He was informed of this transaction between Hovey. as his agent, and Hoyne, Horton &amp; Hoyne, as attorneys for Mayer, and replied, “he should not have done so, if here; yet, as it was done, the ar­rangement had better be carried out;” or words to that effect. Soon after his return a proposition was made by some customer to change a picture ho had for one of those conveyed by the bill of sale, and pay the sum of $000 difference; and. after consulta­tion with Hoyne. Horton &amp; Hoyne. this ex­change was effected, and the $000 was paid directly over to Messrs. Hoyne. Horton &amp; Hoyne by the purchaser, and by them cred­ited to Heffron on the amount due Mayer. Subsequently Heffron placed a large portion of his works of art in the hands of an auc­tioneer for sale at auction, among which were a part of the goods included in the bill of sale, and a portion, about $600 or $800 wortb of the goods mentioned in the bill of sale were sold. And on or about the 20th of December last, Heffron paid to said at­torneys, for Mayer, $1,000 more. Since the commencement of the proceeding in bank­ruptcy against Heffron, another picture in­cluded in the bill of sale has been sold for $150, and the proceeds of which are in the hands of E. I. Tinkham, provisional as-­signee, subject to the decision of the ques­tions involved in this cause. It is also agreed that a lot of potatoes included in the bill of sale have been sold for $240, and the proceeds are held subject to this decision. It is objected that this transaction is fraud­ulent as against the assignee of Heffron, be­cause: First. It gave Mayer, a creditor, an undue preference over the other creditors of Heffron. Second. Hovey. the agent of Heff-­ron, who executed the bill of sale, had no sufficient authority for his acts in that re­gard. Third. Said goods were suffered to remain in the control of the bankrupt with­out visible change, of control, or possession.</p>
                <p pgmap="532" id="b532-4">In support of the first point numerous de­cisions by my predecessor and other district courts have been cited, all tending to estab­lish the conceded point that any act in­tended to give a preference is void under the bankrupt act. The reason and authority of these decisions is not denied, but the ques­tion is, was this a case where a preference, such as is prohibited by the act, was intend­ed. Heffron, by his agent had unlawfully used the funds of Mayer coming into his hands, and had offered his draft, due in thirty days, for the money thus appropriat­ed. Mayer refuses to accept the draft, but directs his attorneys to commence suit by attachment at once; and Hovey, who had acted for Heffron in the use of the funds, and who was still acting for him, proposed to turn over the goods in question to secure the payment of the money, saying he had no doubt it would be adjusted immediately on Heffron’s return, which was daily expected. And the attorneys of Mayer took the respon­sibility of accepting the security, instead of commencing suit as their client had direct­ed. These facts seem to me clearly to take the case out of the class of cases cited. There is no pretense that Mayer or his at­torneys had any actual knowledge of Heff-­ron’s insolvency at the time this transaction took place, although there is evidence going to show that he was, in fact, insolvent at the time, but was not himself aware of the fact, nor was Hovey, his general agent, so aware. But it is claimed that the eases cit­ed show that “insolvency consists in present inability to pay debts,” and that Mayer, through his attorneys, knew that he could not pay this debt, and was therefore insol­vent. This rule might apply if Heffron had been present and the negotiations had been with him. But he was absent, and that ab­sence was alleged as the sole reason for non­payment, and the reasons given for such ab­sence were not such as would excite any sus­picion of insolvency or present inability to pay. Clerks and agents are not supposed to have entire control of the resources of their principal to such an extent as to make their failure to meet an obligation of their princi­pal an act of bankruptcy against him.</p>
                <p pgmap="532" id="b532-6">And. in this case the proof is ample that no suspicion of insolvency had entered the mind of Heffron or his agent. Hovey. The bill of sale was executed as a temporary ex­pedient to indemnify the attorneys for the responsibility they took in disregarding the instructions of their client, by withholding the suit he had instructed them to com­mence. I do not think, therefore, that the evidence shows this to be a case of fraudu­lent preference of a creditor within the bankrupt act, and the cases cited which have arisen under it.</p>
                <p pgmap="532" id="b532-7">In regard to the second point, that Hovey had no authority to execute the bill of sale, I deem it sufficient .to say that it did not re­quire a written authority, and that Mr. Heff-­ron, before the proceedings in bankruptcy, and immediately on his return, ratified the act of Hovey and acquiesced in the same. It is objected that the bill of sale being un­der seal, the ratification must be by as sol­emn an instrument; but this, I apprehend, only applies when it is necessary that the original should have been under seal. As to the other objection, that the goods should have been separated, the evidence shows they were placed in charge of J. Albert Ho-­vey, and that Mr. Heffron acquiesced in his assumed custody; and as there is no evi­dence that any creditor or purchaser was deceived or misled, I shall deem it good be­tween the parties, and only concede to the assignee the assertion of such rights in re­gard to the property as Heffron might have asserted at the time proceedings in bank­ruptcy were commenced.</p>
                <p pgmap="532" id="b532-8">As to that part of the petition which claims a refunding to the assignee of the money received from Heffron since the bill of sale was executed, this depends upon the question whether the transaction between Heffron, through Hovey, his agent, and Mayer, through his attorney, was valid, and whether that, although an absolute sale on its face, was, in fact, only a pledge. Hav­ing come to the conclusion that this was a valid pledge of the goods, it seems to me that money paid to redeem the goods from that pledge cannot be recovered back. It seems clearly for the interest of the estate that the goods thus pledged, being of much greater value than the debt, should be re­deemed. in order that the creditors may have the benefit of the excess in value over the debt secured by them.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="531" ORDERLABEL="529" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00266_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00266_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00266_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_531.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00266_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="532" ORDERLABEL="530" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00266_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00266_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00266_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_532.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00266_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="533" ORDERLABEL="531" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00267_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00267_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00267_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_533.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00267_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b532-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0270"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_532.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00266_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b532-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0270"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_532.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00266_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b532-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0270"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_532.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00266_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_532.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00266_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b531-14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0270"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_531.15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00266_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="ApO" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0270"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_531.18" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00266_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_531.19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00266_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b531-16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0270"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_531.17" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00266_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b531-17" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0270"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_531.20" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00266_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_531.21" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00266_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_532.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00266_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b531-18" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0270"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_531.22" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00266_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b531-15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0270"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_531.16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00266_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="ATJ" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0270"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_531.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00266_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b531-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0270"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_531.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00266_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b531-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0270"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_531.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00266_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b532-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0270"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_532.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00266_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AHV" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0270"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_531.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00266_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b531-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0270"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_531.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00266_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
