<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044046873683_0467" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="C.C.E.D. Pa." jurisdiction="United States">United States Circuit Court for the Eastern District of Pennsylvania</court>
          <name abbreviation="Ewer v. Coxe">EWER et al. v. COXE et al.</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 4,584</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">8 F. Cas. 917</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">4 Wash. C. C. 487</citation>
          <decisiondate>1824-10</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-12T19:40:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-26T10:42:09Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-26T10:56:35Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00460_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="0cf131a28eb27dea0e86e0ed96697686" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="76978">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00460_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00460_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="76691ca3d9302c55af71771c6c930728" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="34484">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00460_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00461_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="c8f244ec66e68caa000796eb80c06ba5" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="113922">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00461_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00461_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="ca81727ef16c38a7e1664725ec810196" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="40850">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00461_1.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00460_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="63aacad2645ab7cd4cb0a1bbe8423a3d" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3104394">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00460_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00460_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="aff48c08f8b6f94a0abb1e395eb7aa14" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="1753756">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00460_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00461_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="43ebeb32a7bebdb0ba35a6c4378d5cc6" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3828914">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00461_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00461_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="8d3d711711fa6e8e1c622ce66d503afa" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2011359">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00461_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00460_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="fcf422033fa6b25a3842c8dd14f25fbd" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="159253">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00460_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00460_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="2d77e0bddedd5de68a608782cc4aa029" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="67643">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00460_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00461_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="8bd7abd014677ccddbb8440bc0c91e1d" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="261151">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00461_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00461_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="f91f56d82f8e2821d1998d20e81accb7" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="81264">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00461_1.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0467" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="920" firstpage="917">
              <court id="b919-12" pgmap="919">Circuit Court, E. D. Pennsylvania.</court>
              <docketnumber id="b919-10" pgmap="919">Case No. 4,584.</docketnumber>
              <citation id="Agy" pgmap="919">[4 Wash. C. C. 487.] <footnotemark>1</footnotemark>
              </citation>
              <parties id="b919-11" pgmap="919">EWER et al. v. COXE et al.</parties>
              <decisiondate id="A1jT" pgmap="919">Oct. Term, 1824.</decisiondate>
              <attorneys id="b920-10" pgmap="920">Mr. Ingraham, for plaintiffs.</attorneys>
              <attorneys id="b920-11" pgmap="920">Mr. Binney, for defendants.</attorneys>
              <footnote label="1">
                <p id="b919-22" pgmap="919">1 [Originally published from the MSS. of Hon. Bushrod Washington, Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States, under the supervision of Richard Peters, Jr., Esq.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author id="b920-12" pgmap="920">WASHINGTON, Circuit Justice.</author>
                <p id="A6L" pgmap="920">The first question is, whether the plaintiffs, not hav­ing published a copy of the record of the title of the Pharmacopaeia, within the period, and for the length of time prescribed by the third section of the act of 1790, have enti­tled themselves to a copyright in that work? If they have not, it will be unnecessary to inquire whether “The American Dispensa-­tory” is a copy or an illegal imitation of the former work, as I hold it to be beyond contro­versy, that, if the plaintiff has no copyright in the work of which he claims to be the owner, a court of equity will not grant him an injunction. This was formerly the doc­trine of the English court of chancery, and still is as I conceive; notwithstanding lord Eldon has, in some instances, granted an in­junction, and continued it to the hearing, un­der circumstances which rendered the title doubtful, if the plaintiff had possession under a colour of title. But surely if he has no title at all, or such a one as would enable him to recover at law, even that judge would, I pre­sume, refuse an injunction. 1 Vern. 120; 6 Ves. 710, 707, 689, 699; 1 W. Bl. 105, 370; 2 Burrows, 661; 2 Eden, 327; Millar v. Taylor, 4 Burrows, 2303, and the cases there cited; Greirson v. Jackson, R. Term R. 304; 8 Ves. 505; 7 Ves. 1; 19 Ves. 447; Coop. Eq. Pl. 303.</p>
                <p id="b920-13" pgmap="920(16) 921(429)">In deciding this first question, it is material to settle, whether the requisitions of the third and fourth sections of the act of the 31st of May 1790, c. 42, are merely' directory, or whether their performance is essential to the vesting of a title to the copyright secured by the law? The first section enacts, in sub­stance, that the author of any book, being a citizen of the United States, or resident there­in, his executors or assigns, shall have the sole right and liberty of printing, publishing, and vending such book, for the term of four­teen years from the time of recording the title thereof in the clerk’s office, as thereafter directed. And if, at the expiration of the said term, the author be living, and a citi­zen or resident as aforesaid, the same exclu­sive right shall be continued to him for the further term of fourteen years, provided he or they shall cause the title thereof to be a second time recorded, and published in the same manner as is hereafter directed; and that within six months before the expi­ration of the first term of fourteen years aforesaid. The second section enacts, that, if any person from and after the recording of the title, and publishing the same as afore­said, and within the times limited and grant­ed by the act, shall print, &amp;c. any copy of such book without the consent of the author or pro­prietor first obtained in writing, &amp;c. such of­fender shall forfeit every such copy, &amp;c. to the author or proprietor, &amp;e. and shall fur­ther pay fifty cents for every sheet, &amp;c. one moiety thereof to the proprietor, who shall sue for the same, and the other to the United States. The third section declares, that no person shall be entitled to the benefit of this act, unless he shall, before publication, de­posit a printed copy of the title of such book in the clerk’s office of the district court, where the author or proprietor shall reside, which record the clerk is required to make f and then follows the form of the record. The sec­tion then proceeds as follows: “and such au­thor or proprietor shall, within two months from the date thereof, cause a copy of the said record to be published in one or more of the newspapers printed in the United States, for the space of four weeks.” The fourth section enacts, that the proprietor shall, within six months after the publishing of the said book, deliver to the secretary of state a copy of the same, to be preserved in his office.</p>
                <p id="b921-3" pgmap="921">It would seem from the phraseology of the first section of this act, as if the recording of the ütle a second time in the clerk’s office, and the publication of the same as directed in the third section were made essential to the vesting of the copyright for a second term of fourteen years in the author or pro­prietor; and it is perfectly clear from the language of the second section, that the proprietor can acquire no title to the copy­right for the term of the first fourteen years, unless he shall deposit in the clerk’s office a printed copy of the title of the book; for the section declares that he shall not be en­titled to the benefit of the act, unless he shall make such deposit. But the condition upon which the proprietor is to be entitled to the benefit of the act, cannot, upon, any gram­matical construction, be extended to the re­quisition contained in the last sentence of this section, to publish a copy of the record of the title within the time and the period pre­scribed. It is entirely a new sentence, and is as much disconnected from the' condition expressed in the preceding part of the sec­tion, as if it had been contained in the fourth section, to which there is clearly no condition annexed. If, then, the title of an author to a copyright, depended altogether upon this act, I should be of opinion that it would be complete, provided he had deposited a print­ed copy of the title of the book in the clerk’s office, as directed by the second section, and that the publication of a copy of the same would only be necessary to enable him to sue for the forfeitures created by the second sec­tion. In this respect, the act corresponds, and was probably intended to correspond with St 8 Anne, c. 19; which, and the construc­tion given to it in the cases of Blackwell v. Harper, 2, Atk. 93; Beckford v. Hood, 7 Term R. 620, and some others, were no doubt within the view of the legislature which ¡passed this act.</p>
                <p id="b921-6" pgmap="921">But a subsequent act was passed on the 29th of April 1802 (chapter 36), as a supple­ment to the before mentioned act which de­clares, that every person who shall, after a certain day, claim to be the author or proprie­tor of any book, and shall thereafter seek to obtain a copyright of the same, agreeably to the rules prescribed by law, before he shall be entitled to the benefit of the act to which this is a supplement, he shall, in addition to the requisites enjoined in the third and fourth sections of the said act, give information, by causing the copy of the record, which, by said act, he is required to publish in one or more newspapers, to be inserted at full length in the title page, or in the page immediately following the title. With respect to this new and additional requisite, it is most obvious that the proprietor can acquire no title to the copyright, unless it is complied with. He must cause the copy to be inserted as di­rected, before he can be entitled to the ben­efit of the act of 1790. What was the benefit conferred by that act? The answer is appa­rent, — a copyright for a certain number of years, with all the privileges, advantages and remedies which that act confers upon the pro­prietor of such copyright. If he has not that right, he can have no remedy of any kind.</p>
                <p id="b921-7" pgmap="921(84) 922(223)">But the supplemental act declares that the person seeking to obtain this right, shall per­form this new requisition, in addition to those prescribed in the third and fourth sections of the act of 1793, and that he must per­form the whole, before he shall be entitled to the benefit of that act. It seems to me that the act will admit of no other construction. The meaning could not, I think, have been more clear and intelligible if the act had de-­dared that “the proprietor, before he should be entitled to the benefit of the act of 1790, should cause a copy of the record of the title to be published; and shall deliver a copy of the book to the secretary of state, as di­rected by the third and fourth sections of that act; and shall also cause a copy of the said record to be inserted at full length in the title page, &amp;e.” That this was the in­tention of the legislature is strongly illustrat­ed by the second section of this act, which secures to persons who shall invent, &amp;c. any historical or other print, the sole right of printing, publishing, &amp;c. the same, provided he shall perform all the requisitions in re­lation thereto, as are directed in relation to maps, charts, and books, by the third and fourth sections of the act of 1790, and shall moreover cause the same entry to be en­graved on such plate, with the name of the proprietor, and printed on every such print, as herein before required to be made on maps or charts. I am therefore of opinion that the plaintiffs are not entitled to a copy­right in the Pharmacopoeia, of which they claim to be the proprietors, and that the in­junction ought not to be granted.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="919" ORDERLABEL="917" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00460_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00460_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00460_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_919.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00460_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="920" ORDERLABEL="918" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00460_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00460_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00460_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_920.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00460_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="921" ORDERLABEL="919" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00461_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00461_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00461_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_921.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00461_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="922" ORDERLABEL="920" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00461_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00461_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00461_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_922.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00461_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b920-13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0467"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_920.16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00460_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_921.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00461_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b920-12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0467"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_920.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00460_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b921-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0467"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_921.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00461_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_921.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00461_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b920-11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0467"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_920.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00460_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b920-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0467"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_920.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00460_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b919-22" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0467"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_919.27" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00460_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="A1jT" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0467"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_919.19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00460_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_919.20" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00460_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b919-12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0467"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_919.18" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00460_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b919-11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0467"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_919.16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00460_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b919-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0467"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_919.15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00460_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b921-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0467"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_921.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00461_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_922.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00461_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b921-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0467"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_921.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00461_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Agy" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0467"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_919.17" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00460_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="A6L" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0467"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_920.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00460_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_920.15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00460_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
