<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044049817315_0114" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="E.D. Wis." jurisdiction="United States">United States District Court for the Eastern District of Wisconsin</court>
          <name abbreviation="In re Jackson">In re JACKSON et al.</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 7,123</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">13 F. Cas. 191</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">7 Biss. 280; 14 N. B. R. 449</citation>
          <decisiondate>1876-09-04</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-10T00:25:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:27:33Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:41:26Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00097_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="71118863f91911baaded4d51b58eca7e" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="10970">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00097_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00097_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="0bdcb14011be40e3924b572295a22ec3" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="113670">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00097_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00098_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="dee77f8d752a13467eda583143abb2ba" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="112794">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00098_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00098_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="a136cf02b508ab3e4b8e52433d100043" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="91576">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00098_1.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00097_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="b3d9df3e17158b77ea03027c01330d8f" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="1181396">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00097_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00097_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="4804e1cce6847d6b284ba4549181a1b6" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3776199">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00097_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00098_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="990c0d5e9c6bcfcfa22f763f153905c1" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3770084">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00098_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00098_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="bfc13be0c7f61be8a11031375a5bce45" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3319433">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00098_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00097_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="61f557627f53fe549c6d77528a883d64" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="11840">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00097_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00097_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="4e4b5511d895700e9fd6f851fca7ca67" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="235629">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00097_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00098_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="354c2c4f2c20074fefbcf65d93e63076" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="238879">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00098_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00098_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="3aae8166756f59dcf2a97291f0db508a" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="190632">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00098_1.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0114" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="194" firstpage="191">
              <court pgmap="193" id="AhJh">District Court, E. D. Wisconsin.</court>
              <docketnumber pgmap="193" id="b193-3">Case No. 7,123.</docketnumber>
              <citation pgmap="193" id="b193-5">[7 Biss. 280; <footnotemark>1</footnotemark> 14 N. B. R. 449.]</citation>
              <parties pgmap="193" id="b193-4">In re JACKSON et al.</parties>
              <decisiondate pgmap="193" id="A_n">Sept. 4, 1876.</decisiondate>
              <attorneys pgmap="194" id="b194-2">John B. Winslow, for creditors petitioning to set aside appointment of assignee.</attorneys>
              <attorneys pgmap="194" id="b194-3">Jenkins, Elliott &amp; Winkler, for creditors opposed.</attorneys>
              <footnote label="1">
                <p pgmap="193" id="b193-18">1 [Reported by Josiah H. Bissell, Esq., and here reprinted by permission.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author pgmap="194" id="b194-4">DYER, District Judge.</author>
                <p pgmap="194" id="Auj">Section 50S3 of Re­vised Statutes provides, that “when a claim is presented for proof before the election of the assignee, and the judge or register en­tertains doubts of its validity, or of the right of the creditor to prove it, and is of opinion that such validity or right ought to be in­vestigated by the assignee, he may postpone the proof of the claim until the assignee is chosen.”</p>
                <p pgmap="194" id="b194-5">Obviously, under this language of the stat­ute, it is not required, in order to justify the postponement of proof of a claim until after the election of an assignee, that the regis­ter should be satisfied, or have before him positive evidence, that the claim is invalid, or that the creditor has no right to prove it. Upon facts or circumstances being laid before him, which create in his mind a sub­stantial doubt upon the question of validity or of the creditor’s right, it is his duty to postpone the claim for investigation. The necessity for a prompt election or appoint­ment of an assignee being usually impera­tive, the theory of the law seems to be, that such election or appointment shall not await an investigation — in many instances necessa­rily protracted — of all the facts touching the validity of the claim. It therefore not in­frequently occurs that a claim is postponed and “is not permitted to be represented in the choice of an assignee, which is subsequent­ly admitted to proof upon full showing made.</p>
                <p pgmap="194" id="b194-6">I. The doubt in the mind of the register should be a reasonable, substantial doubt, re­sulting from a judicial consideration of the question. Such investigation is therefore re­quired as will influence the mind to a con­clusion as to whether there is such doubt of the validity of the claim or of the creditor’s right to prove it. The register cannot post­pone claims on mere objections. If bare ob­jections are made and the register never­theless regards the claims as valid and ad­missible, the court should be at once applied to, if the objections are insisted on, since “the register has not the power to proceed to a choice of assignee without the votes of all the creditors who wish to vote, if their votes can influence the result, unless the register himself considers their claims doubtful.” In re Bartusch [Case No. 1,086].</p>
                <p pgmap="194" id="b194-7">There is no doubt, that where the power of postponement is erroneously exercised by the register, the creditors prejudiced may have the judgment of the court on the question, and it then becomes the duty of the court to consider whether the facts or circumstances laid before the register warranted a judicial determination that the claim in question was of such doubtful validity as to justify an opinion that the claim or the creditor’s right should be investigated by an assignee. In re Lake Superior Ship Canal, Railroad &amp; Iron Co. [Case No. 7,997].</p>
                <p pgmap="194" id="b194-10">The register has certified in this case, that he had such doubts as to the validity of the claims in question, and as to the right of the alleged creditors to prove them, that he was of opinion that such validity or right should be investigated. The fact of rela­tionship of the parties whose «.‘¡aims were-­postponed, to the bankrupts, would not alone justify the register’s action. Nor would the single fact of discrepancies between these claims as scheduled by the bankrupts and as offered for proof, because those discrepancies might arise from computations of interest, but with these circumstances, he had the sworn statement of other creditors, that in their belief, the claims were to some extent fictitious and were proved for the purpose of controlling the election of assignee, in the interest of the bankrupts. And added to-­these, was the circumstance that these de­mands did not appear upon the books of the bankrupts, nor in any bills payable account kept by them. This must have been in the mind of the register, and is a material fact; since it is regarded as a matter of high im­portance, by the terms of the law, that mer­chants shall keep books of account from which creditors may learn their actual finan­cial condition. I do not mean that the cir­cumstance referred to would necessarily have weight against these claims upon further in­vestigation, because it is a circumstance sus­ceptible of explanation, but, at this stage of the case, the question is, whether it was not a fact, which, in connection with the other circumstances, might not create a reasona­able, substantial doubt as the basis for an opinion, that the claims should be investi­gated by an assignee. I am not prepared to say it was not, or that the register erroneous­ly entertained the doubts upon which he acted in postponing these claims.</p>
                <p pgmap="194" id="b194-11">Further, I take occasion to suggest where a review by the district judge of the action of the register in such cases is sought, the better practice on the part of creditors who object to the postponement of claims, is, to at once have the objection entered, obtain a stay of proceedings, and have the case cer­tified, before any further action before the register transpires.</p>
                <p pgmap="194" id="b194-12">Inasmuch as without such objection being thus made in this case, the vote for assignee proceeded as if in submission to the ruling of the register, even creditors who now seek this review joining in the attempted elec­tion, I doubt whether the point under con­sideration could be now available to the con­testing creditors. I make these suggestions because of the importance of having the practice in the particular referred to, well settled and understood, as it may not have heretofore been in this court.</p>
                <p pgmap="194(6) 195(95)" id="b194-13">The bankrupt law contemplates as little delay as possible in the choice of an as-­signee and in his assumption of the care and management of the estate; and in this case after the appointment of the assignee, and after he had given bond and taken an assignment of the estate, and several days before the court was advised of any of the alleged irregularities in the proceedings, li­cense was granted to him to sell property, upon the supposition that he had been reg­ularly chosen, a circumstance which I think illustrates the propriety of the practice I have suggested.</p>
                <p pgmap="195" id="b195-4">2. The objection to the proof of debt of­fered at the creditors’ meeting in behalf of .Elam Beardsley, is, I think, well taken. Section 5078 of the United States Revised Statutes provides that such proof shall be made “by the claimant, testifying of his own knowledge, unless he is absent from the United States, or prevented by some other good cause from testifying, in which case the demand may be verified by the attorney or authorized agent, etc.” The proof of this claim stated, as a reason why it was made by an agent, that the principal was traveling and was supposed to -be in Colorado; and the register held that under the words “some other good cause,” in the section cited, such absence of the claimant as was shown in this proof of his demand, justified proof by an agent I do not concur in this construc­tion of the law. As the statute when it mentions absence of the claimant as ground for verification of the claim by an agent, speaks particularly, and only, of absence from the United States, it must be held I think, that mere absence from the state or the locality where the proof is made, is not to be regarded as alone cause for proof by an agent. The words “some other good cause,” means some sufficient cause other than or in addition to mere absence from the state. I concur in the ruling made in Re Whyte [Case No. 17,606], in which case it was held that the absence of a claimant, which will render a proof of debt by an agent admissible, must be “from the United States.” But the objection to this claim is immaterial, since it did not, and could not affect the choice or appointment of an as-­signee. The disallowance of it by the reg­ister would still leave the case, so far as the choice of an assignee by vote of creditors was concerned, as it was, provided his rul­ings and action on the other points were right.</p>
                <p pgmap="195" id="b195-5">The result would not be changed by the exclusion of the claim. This being so, the court ought not to set aside proceedings oth­erwise regular, because of irregularity in ad­mitting this claim. In re Lake Superior Ship Canal, Railroad &amp; Iron Co. [supra].</p>
                <p pgmap="195" id="b195-6">8. It is claimed that the action of the reg­ister in appointing an assignee was irregu­lar, that there was an opposing interest, and Therefore that the register could not appoint. Section 5034 of Revised Statutes provides, that at the meeting of creditors for election of an assignee, if no choice be made, the judge, or if there be no opposing interest, the register shall appoint one or more as­signees.</p>
                <p pgmap="195" id="AqF">By “opposing interest” is meant not merely an interest contending by vote for the elee­tion of a particular person, but an interest in opposition to the exercise of the power of appointment by the register. Upon failure to elect an assignee by creditors, it becomes the duty of the register to state that the duty devolves upon the judge to appoint, un­less there be no opposing interest. If there be no such interest, then the register may appoint. Some misunderstanding appears to exist between counsel, and between one of the counsel and the register, as to what transpired at the creditors’ meeting. In jus­tice to all parties I permitted in addition to the register’s certificate, oral statements as to what then transpired to be made at the hearing. The register’s certificate states that when the result of the vote showed that there had been no choice of assignee, he so announced to the creditors,-• and advised them that it became the duty of the judge to appoint the assignee, unless there were no opposing interests, when the register was au­thorized to make the appointment; that up­on inquiry of the attorney for some of the creditors, he stated that the term “opposing interest” meant opposition or objection to an appointment by the register, and that no ob­jection being made, he appointed the as-­signee. The recollection of counsel for cred­itors now opposing the register's appoint­ment, differs somewhat from the statements of the register’s certificate, but from the statements made by counsel on both sides and by one of the contesting creditors, I must conclude that the controversy before the register, was essentially upon the person to be chosen.</p>
                <p pgmap="195" id="Ari">A creditor states that he thinks the regis­ter made to the meeting the statement em­bodied in his certificate, and adds that ac­cording to his recollection, the attorney rep­resenting himself and other creditors now contesting the appointment made by the reg­ister, requested or suggested the appoint­ment of a person voted for by him, though this does not accord with counsel’s under­standing of what transpired.</p>
                <p pgmap="195(106) 196(21)" id="b195-10">From all the statements made, I think it a necessary inference, that specific objection was not made to an appointment by the reg­ister. In cases where there is no choice of an assignee by creditors, distinct disclosure should be made of any opposing interest, and the register should not appoint unless it appears beyond doubt that there is no such interest. In view of all the facts, and as no objection is made to the qualifications or integrity of the present assignee, I must confirm his appointment and set aside the stay of proceedings heretofore granted. If there should at any time arise any ground of complaint against him or his administra­tion of the estate, creditors will have the right and opportunity to be heard.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="193" ORDERLABEL="191" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00097_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00097_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00097_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_193.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00097_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="194" ORDERLABEL="192" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00097_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00097_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00097_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_194.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00097_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="195" ORDERLABEL="193" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00098_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00098_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00098_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_195.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00098_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="196" ORDERLABEL="194" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00098_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00098_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00098_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_196.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00098_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b194-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0114"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_194.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00097_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b194-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0114"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_194.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00097_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b194-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0114"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_194.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00097_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b194-2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0114"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_194.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00097_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b194-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0114"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_194.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00097_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b193-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0114"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_193.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00097_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b193-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0114"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_193.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00097_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b193-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0114"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_193.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00097_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b193-18" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0114"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_193.21" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00097_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AqF" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0114"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_195.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00098_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Ari" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0114"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_195.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00098_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b194-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0114"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_194.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00097_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_194.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00097_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AhJh" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0114"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_193.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00097_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b195-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0114"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_195.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00098_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_195.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00098_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b195-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0114"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_195.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00098_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b194-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0114"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_194.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00097_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="A_n" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0114"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_193.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00097_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b195-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0114"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_195.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00098_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Auj" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0114"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_194.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00097_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_194.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00097_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b195-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0114"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_195.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00098_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_196.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00098_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b194-11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0114"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_194.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00097_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b194-13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0114"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_194.16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00097_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_195.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00098_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b194-12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0114"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_194.15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00097_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
