<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044046873683_0571" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="C.C.E.D. Mich." jurisdiction="United States">United States Circuit Court for the Eastern District of Michigan</court>
          <name abbreviation="Farrington v. Board of Water Com’rs">FARRINGTON et al. v. BOARD OF WATER COM’RS OF DETROIT</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 4,687</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">8 F. Cas. 1086</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">4 Fish. Pat. Cas. 216</citation>
          <decisiondate>1870-09</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-12T19:40:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-26T10:42:09Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-26T10:56:35Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00544_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="88010a3d60d503acb9ec85cb3ffb1a58" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="62134">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00544_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00545_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="b5b1d7474f3db8b26c1bb662167ef874" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="98398">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00545_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00545_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="c8721c7e1ff26bbd7b8bf682f2c2a44c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="71754">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00545_1.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00544_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="df0f32448e114d095af52820e040acfb" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2524116">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00544_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00545_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="209ddddf1b668a5e0ff3e0fec5e45864" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3507872">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00545_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00545_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="d78c61a91d727411c4e30fdf41b0d40b" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2887038">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00545_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00544_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="ee9c58ac6da3593c0502034f451667e0" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="126570">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00544_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00545_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="b81dc81724bec2cb1ffe3f8c89512d6d" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="234707">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00545_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00545_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="a4ae7ca1d59ab8de2f46b847da6651fe" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="159727">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00545_1.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0571" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="1088" firstpage="1086">
              <court id="AqIC" pgmap="1088">Circuit Court, E. D. Michigan.</court>
              <docketnumber id="b1088-8" pgmap="1088">Case No. 4,687.</docketnumber>
              <citation id="b1088-10" pgmap="1088">[4 Fish. Pat. Cas. 216.]<footnotemark>1</footnotemark>
              </citation>
              <parties id="b1088-9" pgmap="1088">FARRINGTON et al. v. BOARD OF WATER COM’RS OF DETROIT.</parties>
              <decisiondate id="AGJ" pgmap="1088">Sept., 1870.</decisiondate>
              <attorneys id="b1089-6" pgmap="1089">A. Russell, for complainants.</attorneys>
              <attorneys id="b1089-7" pgmap="1089">A. D. Frazer and Moore &amp; Griffin, for de­fendants.</attorneys>
              <footnote label="1">
                <p id="b1088-16" pgmap="1088">1 [Reported by Samuel S. Fisher, Esq., and here reprinted by permission.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author id="b1089-8" pgmap="1089">LONGXEAR, District Judge.</author>
                <p id="AX11" pgmap="1089">On the ar­gument, the first point was abandoned, and it was conceded that, by the provisions of section 18, act of July 4,1836 (5 Stat. 125), the •extension of the patent inured to the benefit •of the defendants, as purchasers of a ma­chine, and conferred upon them the right to continue the use of the same.</p>
                <p id="b1089-9" pgmap="1089">But the second point is insisted on, and it is claimed, on the part of complainants, that the right of defendants to continue the use •of the machine in use by them at the time of the extension of the patent, includes the right to repair merely, and does not include the right to renew any portion of the ma­chine, or any of its parts, especially the tubu­lar or hollow auger, or bit, used in the ma­chine, for the reason that it constitutes the -valuable or novel thing patented.</p>
                <p id="b1089-10" pgmap="1089">' The thing patented is described and de­fined in the specifications, as follows: “A new and improved machine, intended chiefly for boring pump logs. * * * The nature ■of my invention consists in, first, the em­ployment or use of a tubular or hollow auger -or bit, constructed and arranged as will be presently shown; and also in the combina­tion of the tubular or hollow auger or bit, with a screw’ or worm-rod, arranged and •operating, as will be hereafter described. * * * The bits or cutting portion (b) of the auger are attached to its outer end, and .are placed over the bore of the auger, the points of the bits just passing the center of the bore, so as to cut a clear hole without leaving a core. * * * I do not use any screw on the end of my bit. or auger, as I •find that a screw has a tendency to follow the grain of the wood. * * * Within the hollow or tubular auger D. there is placed a screw or worm-rod J. This screw or worm-rod represents the screw portion of an ordinary screw auger, and extends the w’hole length of the auger D, its outer end nearly touching the bits, C, of the auger. •* * * The auger or bit and worm, J, are detached, and revolve independent of each other, by which means I am able to run the wrorm, J, at a much greater speed than the bit or auger, and which serves to clear the chips from the bit as fast as they are made, .and prevents the same from choking. * * * I am aware that the tubular or hollow auger, as such, is not new; nor do I claim it as new, but what I claim as new, and desire to secure by letters patent, is:</p>
                <blockquote id="b1089-16" pgmap="1089">“1. The tubular or hollow auger or bit D, as constructed having the lips of the bits ap­proach the centre, and yet separated from each other, doing without the use of a screw on the end of the bit, for the purpose of pre­venting the bit from following the grain of the wood.</blockquote>
                <blockquote id="b1089-17" pgmap="1089">“2. I claim the worm J, operating on its own axle, and independent of the revolutions of the auger or bits D, for the purpose of clearing away the chips as set forth.”</blockquote>
                <p id="b1089-18" pgmap="1089">As appears by affidavits, presented on be­half of defendants in opposition to the mo­tion for a temporary injunction, these lips of the auger or bit will wear out by constant use in about forty days, so that they can not be longer repaired or made of any use whatever for the purpose intended, and un­less replaced by new ones the machine could not be longer used. It is the replacing of such old worn-out lips by new ones that is complained of as an infringement and to restrain which an injunction is asked.</p>
                <p id="b1089-19" pgmap="1089">It further appeared, upon the hearing of the motion, that for convenience in taking off and putting on these lips of the auger or bit for the purpose of sharpening or re­pairing, the auger or bit is so constructed that a small portion of the outer end of it to which the lips are attached may be screwed off and on at pleasure, and it is by this means that the new lips are attached in place of the old ones. Although this device for taking off and putting on the lips is no part of the invention, yet it is a circumstance necessary to be stated in order to a full un­derstanding of the questions presented.</p>
                <p id="b1089-20" pgmap="1089">The questions presented are:</p>
                <p id="b1089-21" pgmap="1089">1. Did the purchase of the defendants of the right to the use of the machine in ques­tion, invest them with the right to supply new lips to the hollow auger or bit whenever the old ones should become useless and ir­reparable by ordinary wear or by breaking?</p>
                <p id="b1089-22" pgmap="1089">2. How did the renewal of the patent after the purchase affect that right?</p>
                <p id="b1089-23" pgmap="1089">First. It is clear, from the specification above quoted, that the patent covers the fol­lowing items:</p>
                <p id="b1089-24" pgmap="1089">1. The lips of the auger or bit, in question.</p>
                <p id="b1089-25" pgmap="1089">2. Tile combination of the hollow auger or bit with the new lips attached, with the screw or worm for removing the chips as fast as made, as described.</p>
                <p id="b1089-26" pgmap="1089(73) 1090(495)">The “lips,” and the “combination,” are the only things that were new, or claimed as new, and of course were the only things pat­ented. The “combination” included the “lips,” and it is the combination, together with the ordinary machinery for giving its different parts the requisite motion, that con­stitutes the “machine,” as a whole, which is mentioned in the first sentence of the specifi­cations above quoted, which was covered by the patent, which was sold to the defendants, and which they had the right to use. In this combination, the lips of the auger or bit constitute the effective element; but the inventor has so arranged them in the com­bination that the machine could-not be con­tinued in use without a complete renewal of them at short intervals. From the na­ture of the case, these lips could be but tem­porary in their relations to the use of the whole machine, and it must have been so understood by the inventor in selling and the purchaser in buying the machine. It has been held, by the supreme court, that in such a case the purchaser has the right to replace such temporary parts. See Wilson v. Simpson, 9 How. [50 U. S.] 109. This case is so nearly analogous to that one, that I quote from it at laifee. The question there was as to the right of an assignee of a Wood-­worth patent planing machine to replace the cutter knives when worn out or broken, and Hr. Justice Wayne, in delivering the opin­ion of the court, at page 125, says: “The right of the assignee to replace the cutter knives is not because they are of perishable materials, but because the inventor of the machine has so arranged them as a part of its combination, that the machine could not be continued in use without a succession of knives at short intervals. Unless they were replaced the invention would have been of but little use to the inventor or to others. The other constituent parts of this inven­tion, though liable to be worn out, are not made with reference to any use of them which will require them to be replaced. These, without having a definite duration, are contemplated by the inventor to last so long as the materials of which they are formed can hold together in use in such combination. No replacement of them at in­termediate intervals is meant or is neces­sary. They may be repaired as the use may require. With such intentions they are put into the structure — so it is understood by a purchaser, and beyond the duration of them the purchaser of a machine has not a longer use. But if another constituent part of a combination is meant to be only temporary in the use of the whole, and to be frequently replaced, because it will not last so long as the other parts of the combination, its in­ventor can not complain if he sells the use of his machine, that the purchaser uses it in the way the inventor meant it to be used, and in the only way in which the ma­chine can be used. Such replacement of temporary parts does not alter the identity of the machine, but preserves it, though there may not be in it every part of its origi­nal material.”</p>
                <p id="b1090-3" pgmap="1090">I think the case of Wilson v. Simpson clear­ly decides this one. It matters not that in that case the cutter knives were not a part of the invention, and that in this case the lips of the auger or bit are. The only question is, are they, from the nature of things, tem­porary in their relation to the use of the whole combination? Being such, the right to replace them clearly exists.</p>
                <p id="b1090-6" pgmap="1090">Second. The extension of the patent does not in any manner affect or impair the right. The right to replace, as has been seen, de­pends upon the right to use the machine. The continued right to use the machine is clearly guarantied by section 18 of the act of July 4, 1S3G, above cited, and was con-, ceded upon the argument</p>
                <p id="b1090-7" pgmap="1090">The motion for a preliminary injunction is denied.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="1088" ORDERLABEL="1086" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00544_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00544_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00544_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_1088.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00544_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="1089" ORDERLABEL="1087" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00545_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00545_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00545_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_1089.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00545_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="1090" ORDERLABEL="1088" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00545_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00545_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00545_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_1090.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00545_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1089-17" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0571"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1089.17" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00545_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1088-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0571"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1088.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00544_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1089-22" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0571"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1089.22" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00545_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1089-23" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0571"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1089.23" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00545_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1089-24" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0571"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1089.24" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00545_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1089-26" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0571"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1089.26" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00545_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1090.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00545_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1089-20" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0571"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1089.20" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00545_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1088-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0571"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1088.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00544_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AX11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0571"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1089.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00545_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1089.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00545_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1089-16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0571"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1089.16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00545_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1089-19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0571"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1089.19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00545_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1089-18" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0571"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1089.18" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00545_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1088-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0571"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1088.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00544_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AqIC" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0571"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1088.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00544_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1089-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0571"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1089.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00545_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1089.15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00545_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AGJ" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0571"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1088.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00544_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1090-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0571"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1090.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00545_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1089-21" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0571"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1089.21" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00545_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1090-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0571"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1090.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00545_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1090.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00545_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1090-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0571"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1090.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00545_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1089-25" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0571"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1089.25" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00545_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1089-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0571"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1089.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00545_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1089-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0571"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1089.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00545_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1088-16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0571"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1088.21" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00544_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1089-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0571"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1089.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00545_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1089-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0571"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1089.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00545_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
