<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044049817315_0115" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="C.C.S.D.N.Y." jurisdiction="United States">United States Circuit Court for the Southern District of New York</court>
          <name abbreviation="In re Jackson">In re JACKSON</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 7,124</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">13 F. Cas. 194</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">14 Blatchf. 245</citation>
          <decisiondate>1877-06-09</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-10T00:25:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:27:33Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:41:26Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00098_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="a136cf02b508ab3e4b8e52433d100043" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="91576">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00098_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00099_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="58b63d5ca63f5365b617b6368ed1d0ea" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="112060">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00099_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00099_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="90961134ac483e297e1917b1f9af6e3c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="119344">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00099_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00100_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="47e67b2c44cc7176b018f3cdec739de4" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="69118">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00100_0.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00098_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="bfc13be0c7f61be8a11031375a5bce45" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3319433">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00098_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00099_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="3d0a7b98f021e91dbd8fae7be6393acd" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3773370">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00099_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00099_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="8989df8685cb3b415eb4d8081c4814d9" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3852069">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00099_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00100_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="7083b0f7c4265afa6dde2776b6a7bcb5" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2854872">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00100_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00098_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="3aae8166756f59dcf2a97291f0db508a" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="190632">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00098_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00099_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="b1a0b4596c1fed94d2c9cde83bc86521" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="243291">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00099_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00099_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="72caef092d527f2508d74ee4a2daac8e" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="241986">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00099_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00100_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="0d09d313ea52c259db71f2de010b7fa9" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="151647">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00100_0.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0115" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="197" firstpage="194">
              <court pgmap="196" id="b196-7">Circuit Court, S. D. New York.</court>
              <docketnumber pgmap="196" id="b196-4">Case No. 7,124.</docketnumber>
              <citation pgmap="196" id="b196-6">[14 Blatchf. 245.] <footnotemark>1</footnotemark>
              </citation>
              <parties pgmap="196" id="b196-5">In re JACKSON.</parties>
              <decisiondate pgmap="196" id="AIU">June 9, 1877.</decisiondate>
              <attorneys pgmap="196" id="b196-16">Abram J. Dittenhoefer, for relator.</attorneys>
              <attorneys pgmap="196" id="b196-17">Benjamin B. Foster, Asst. Dist. Atty., for the United States.</attorneys>
              <footnote label="1">
                <p pgmap="196" id="b196-19">1 [Reported by Hon. Samuel Blatchford. Cir­•cuit Judge, and here reprinted by permission.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author pgmap="196" id="b196-18">BBATCHFORD, District Judge.</author>
                <p pgmap="196" id="AXa">On the 8th of March, 1877, a United States commis­sioner for this district issued a warrant to the marshal, which recited, that complaint on oath had been made to him, charging that A. Orlando Jackson did, on or about the 23d of February, 1S77, “at the Southern district of New York, unlawfully, wilfully and knowingly deposit and cause to be de­posited, in the post-office and mails of the United States, then and there, for mailing and delivery, certain circulars concerning lotteries," and commanded him to apprehend said Jackson. Jackson was arrested under this warrant, and brought before the com­missioner on the 13th of March, and was identified as the party charged, and dis­charged on bail to await trial. Subsequent-­lj- he was surrendered by his surety, and he demanded an examination before the com­missioner on the charge, and it was had, and the commissioner, on the 2d of May, de­cided that there was probable cause to be­lieve that Jackson committed the offence charged, and he committed him to the cus­tody of the marshal, to await the action of the grand jury, in default of 8500 bail. Thereupon he has- been brought before this court on a writ of habeas corpus issued to inquire into the cause of his imprisonment, and the proceedings which took place before the commissioner have been brought before this court by a writ of certiorari. It ap­peared before the commissioner, that Jack­son, on the 23d of February. 1877, deposited in the post-office at New York City, to be conveyed by mail, a sealed letter envelope, addressed as follows: “J. Ivetcham, Lock Drawer 1G4, Gloversville, N. Y.,” and which contained circulars concerning a lottery de­scribed as “The Kentucky State Lottery, Simmons and Dickinson, Managers,” and also circulars concerning Louisiana and Ha­vana lotteries, the postage on which was duly prepaid by stamps, and that the above named lotteries were authorised by the laws of the respective states of Louisiana and Kentucky and of the kingdom of Spain.</p>
                <p pgmap="196(383) 197(14)" id="b196-21">.The prosecution in this case is founded on section 3894 of the Revised Statutes, which, as amended by section 2 of the act of July 12. 1870 (19 Stat. 90), provides, that “no letter or circular concerning lotteries, so called gift concerts, or other similar enter­prises. offering prizes, or concerning schemes devised and intended to deceive and de­fraud the public, for the purpose of obtain­ing money under false pretences, shall be carried in the mail;” and that “any person' who shall knowingly deposit or send any thing to be conveyed by mail, in violation of this section, shall be punishable by a fine of not more than five hundred dollars, nor less than one hundred dollars, with costs of prosecution.” The amendment of 1876, con­sisted in striking out the word “illegal” before the word “lotteries” from the section as originally enacted in the Revised Statutes. A part of the statutory provision embodied in section 3894 of the Revised Statutes was originally enacted July 27, 1868, as section 13 of the act of that date (15 Stat. 190), in these words: “It shall not be lawful to de­posit in a post-office, to be sent by mail, any letters or circulars concerning lotteries, so called gift concerts, or other similar en­terprises, offering prizes of any kind, on any pretext whatever.” No specific penalty or punishment was imposed for a violation of this provision. On the 8th of June. 1872, it was enacted as follows, by section 179 of the act of that date (17 Stat. 302): “It shall not be lawful to convey by mail, nor to de­posit in a post-office to be sent by mail, any letters or circulars concerning illegal lot­teries, so called gift concerts, or other sim­ilar enterprises, offering prizes, or concern­ing schemes devised and intended to deceive and defraud the public, for the purpose of obtaining money under false pretences, and a penalty of not more than five hundred dol­lars. nor less than one hundred dollars, with costs of prosecution, is hereby imposed, up­on conviction, in any federal court, of the violation of this section." It is to be noted, that the word “illegal” was not in the act of 1868, but was inserted in the act of 1872, and continued in the Revised Statutes, and stricken out by tbe act of 1876.</p>
                <p pgmap="197" id="b197-4">Congress has, at various times, exercised the power of excluding from the mails vari­ous articles, capable of being conveyed in scaled letter envelopes, and of declaring it to be a punishable offence to deposit sueii articles in the mail. By section 148 of the act of June 8, 1872 (17 Stat. 302), it was ■enacted, that no obscene book, pamphlet, picture, print, or other publication of a vui-­gar or indecent character, shall be carried in the mail, and that any person who shall knowingly deposit for mail or for delivery any such obscene publication, shall be deem­ed guilty of a misdemeanor, and, on convic­tion thereof, shall, for every such offence, be fined not more than $500, or imprisoned not more than one year, or both, according to the circumstances and aggravation of the offence. By section 2 of the act of March 3, 1S73 (17 Stat. 599), such inhibition was extended to every “obscene, lewd, or lascivi­ous book, pamphlet, picture, paper, print, or •other publication of an indecent character,” and to every “article or thing designed or intended for the prevention of conception or procuring of abortion,” and to every “arti­cle or thing intended or adapted for any in­decent or immoral use or nature,” and to every “written or printed card, circular, book, pamphlet, advertisement or notice of ■any kind, giving information, directly or in­directly, where, or how, or of whom, or by what means, either of the things before mentioned may be obtained or made;” and It was enacted, that any person who shall knowingly deposit, or' cause to be deposited, for mail or delivery, any of said-articles or things, or any notice or paper containing .any advertisement relating to said articles or things, and any person who, in pursuance of any plan or scheme for disposing of any of said articles or things, shall take, or cause to be taken, from the mail, any such letter or package, shall be deemed guilty of a mis­,demeanor, and, on conviction thereof, shall, for every offence, be fined not less than $100, nor more than $5,000. or imprisoned at hard labor not less than one year, nor more than ten years, or both, in the discretion of the judge. These provisions were re-enacted in section 3S93 of the Revised Statutes, and by section 1 of the act of July 12, 1S76 (19 Stat. •90).</p>
                <p pgmap="197" id="b197-5">It is contended for the relator, that, if sec­tion 3894 can be construed to cover sealed letters, it is void, as not within any power ■conferred on congress by the constitution. 'The argument is, that, prior to the adoption of the constitution, which conferred on con­gress (article 1, § 8) the power “to establish post-offices and post-roads.” the states and the people had enjoyed for many years the right of having conveyed by post all sealed letters, -without reference to their contents, •(unless such contents were liable to destroy, ■deface, or otherwise injure the contents of the mail-bag, or the persons of those engaged in the postal service, such as liquids, poisons, glass or explosive materials); and that such grant of power must be construed as not authorizing congress to exclude from the mail what was legitimate mail matter at the time of the adoption of the constitution. It is further said, that congress is bound to provide for carrying by mail everything which it prohibits from being carried other­wise than by mail; and that it has made it a punishable offence to carry letters for hire outside of the mail. It is further said, that the exercise of a power absolutely to prohibit the carrying in the mail of sealed letters containing information of a certain charac­ter, is not the exercise of a power which is either proper or necessary for carrying into execution the power of establishing post-­offices and post-roads; that a power of ex-­elusion, based upon the contents of sealed letters, is an arbitrary power, and may be extended to the exclusion of matters which depend on caprice or whim; and that the ex­clusion, in the present case, extends to mat­ters which are lawful under the laws of -some of the states of the Union, and to mat­ters over which the federal government has no jurisdiction.</p>
                <p pgmap="197" id="ANek">On the part of the United States it is ■ con­tended, that it is within the constitutional power of congress to determine what shall be mail matter; and that, in pursuance of such power, it may lawfully exclude certain articles and things from the mail, although such articles and things are contained in sealed envelopes, and may declare it to be an offence to deposit such articles and things In the mail.</p>
                <p pgmap="197(234) 198(46)" id="Amp">The meaning of the clause in the constitu­tion (article 2, § 8). that congress shall have power “to make all laws which shall be nec­essary and proper to carry into execution the foregoing powers.” has been settled by ju­dicial construction. It does not mean that no law is authorized which is not indispen-­.sabl.v necessary to give effect to a specified power. Congress possesses the choice of means, and is empowered to use any means which are in fact conducive to the exercise of a power granted by the constitution. U. S. v. Fisher, 2 Cranch [6 U. S.] 358, 396. The necessity spoken of in the clause is not to be understood as an absolute one, but congress is to be allowed that discretion with respect to the means by which the powers conferred on it are to be earned into execution, which will enable it to discharge the high duties assigned to it in the manner most beneficial to the people. If the end is legitimate and within the scope of the constitution, then all means which are appropriate, and are plain­ly adapted to that end. and are not prohib­ited, but consist with the letter and spirit of the constitution, are constitutional: and. if a particular law is not prohibited, and is really calculated to effect any of the objects entrusted to the government, an inquiry by a court into the degree of its necessity, would be to pass the line which circum­scribes the judicial department, and to tread on legislative ground. McCulloch v. Mary­land, 4 Wheat [17 U. S.] 421, 423; Legal Tender Cases, 12 Wall. [79 U. S.] 539.</p>
                <p pgmap="198" id="AA5">The principal argument on the part of the relator is, that inasmuch as the exclusive power is given to congress to establish post-­offices and post-roads, it is not authorized to refuse to carry in the mail anything which was lawful mail matter at the time the con­stitution was adopted. This, line of reason­ing has been sought to be applied to other matters of federal cognizance, but has not met with favor. Thus, congress is author­ized to establish uniform laws on the sub­ject of bankruptcies throughout the United States; and it has been contended, in respect to laws on that subject which have been en­acted by congress, that.the power of congress is limited to the principle on which the Eng­lish bankruptcy system was founded when the constitution was adopted, and cannot ex­tend to authorizing voluntary bankruptcies, or to putting into involuntary bankruptcy others than traders, or to granting dischar­ges without the consent of creditors, or to authorizing such compositions as are now provided for. But the view has prevailed, that congress, in passing laws on the subject of bankruptcies, is not restricted to laws with such scope only as the English bank­ruptcy laws had when the constitution was adopted, and that it is sufficient if the stat­ute relates to the subject of bankruptcies. In re Klein, 1 How. [42 U. S.] 278; In re Silverman [Case No. 12,855]; U. S. v. Pusey [Id. 16,098]; In re Reiman [Cases Nos. 11,673, 11,675]. So, also, in respect to admiralty and maritime jurisdiction. The constitution de-­dares (article 3, § 2) that the judicial power of the United States shall extend to all cases of admiralty and maritime jurisdiction. Pri- or to the decision in the case of The Genesee Chief v. Fitzhugh, 12 How. [53 U. S.] 443, it had always been understood and held, that, under the constitution, such jurisdiction was confined to tide-waters. In that case it was held, that, according to the true construction of the grant in the constitution, the admi­ralty jurisdiction extended to all public nav­igable waters, whether influenced by the tide or not. In England, in the text-writers and the decisions, the jurisdiction of the admi­ralty had always been spoken of as confined to tide-water, tide-water and navigable wa­ter being, in England, synonymous terms, and “tide-water” meaning, in England, noth­ing more than public rivers, as contradistin-­guished from private ones. At the time the constitution was adopted, and our courts of admiralty went into operation, the English definition of the jurisdiction, that it was confined to the ebb and flow of the tide, was adopted here, by the courts. But it after-­wards became evident, that a definition which would limit public rivers in this coun­try to tide-water rivers was utterly inadmis­sible, and it was held that the lakes and the waters connecting them were public waters and within the grant of admiralty and mari­time jurisdiction in the constitution.</p>
                <p pgmap="198" id="b198-6">These illustrations serve to show, that, in construing a grant of power in the constitu­tion, it is to be construed according to the fair and reasonable import of its terms, and its construction is not necessarily to be con­trolled by a reference to what existed when the constitution was adopted. A power to establish post-offices and post-roads is exe­cuted by the single act of making the es­tablishment; but, under such power, it has always been held to be lawful to carry the mail along the post-road, from one post-office to another, and to punish those who steal letters from the post-office or rob the mail. So, under the power to establish post-offices and post-roads, it must be held, that con­gress has the right to prescribe what it will carry along the post-road as part of the mail, and what it will not carry, and to render its enactments efficient by punishing as an offence the violation of them. Wheth­er certain things shall be excluded or not is a matter for the sound discretion of congress, and the discretion of a court can­not be substituted for the discretion of congress. The discretion of congress can­not be fettered by the consideration that a given thing was generally or even univer­sally allowed to be carried in the mail when the constitution was adopted. To argue against the existence of such discretion be­cause it is possible for congress to abuse its exercise, by excluding from the mail letters, containing matter of a given character, through caprice or from partisan prejudice, is to argue against the existence of all dis­cretion in congress in the exercise of any of the powers conferred on it. All such discre­tion may be abused, but the correction of the abuse must be left, under our form of gov­ernment, to the expression of the will of the people by means of the elective franchise. The existence of the abuse is no argument against the existence of the power. Because an individual judge might not. if a legislator, have thought it wise to exclude from the mail a sealed letter containing matter of a given character, it is not for him, in the ex­ercise of his judicial functions, to hold that such exclusion is not within the constitution­al authority of congress. Whether the pro­visions of law which forbid and punish the carrying of letters outside of the mail will be construed as applying to letters which-­congress forbids to be carried in the mail, is a question which does not arise in this case.</p>
                <p pgmap="198(49) 199(57)" id="b198-7">It is, undoubtedly, not indispensably nec­essary to the exercise of the power of estab­lishing post-offices and post-roads, that let­ters or circulars concerning lotteries should be excluded from the mails. But congress is not prohibited from excluding them, and, if congress regards it as most beneficial to the people, and as calculated to effect in the most proper manner the objects of establish­ing post-offices and of carrying the mail, to exclude from the mail letters concerning lot­teries, whether legal ones or illegal ones, it is for congress, and not for a court, to judge of the degree of necessity for such exclusion.</p>
                <p pgmap="199" id="b199-3">It is also contended, for the relator, that section 3894 of the Revised Statutes does not create any crime or offence against the Unit­ed States. This is not so. The word “pun­ishable,” and the fact that the amount of the fine imposed is discretionary, indicate that a crime is intended and not a pecuniary pen­alty to be recovered by a civil action.</p>
                <p pgmap="199" id="b199-4">It is further urged, that, because the only punishment is a fine, and there can be no imprisonment except for the nonpayment of the fine, the relator cannot be arrested and deprived of his liberty in the first instance. But section 1014 of the Revised Statutes pro­vides, that, for any crime or offence against the United States, the offender may be ar­rested, and imprisoned or bailed, for trial. If there be a'crime or offence, an arrest for trial may be made, to be followed by impris­onment if no bail is taken, or by bail, even though the punishment, on conviction, be a fine alone. The arrest is made to secure a trial for the offence.</p>
                <p pgmap="199" id="b199-5">The writ is dismissed, and the relator is remanded to the custody of the marshal un­der the process of commitment by which he was held.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="196" ORDERLABEL="194" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00098_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00098_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00098_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_196.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00098_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="197" ORDERLABEL="195" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00099_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00099_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00099_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_197.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00099_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="198" ORDERLABEL="196" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00099_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00099_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00099_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_198.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00099_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="199" ORDERLABEL="197" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00100_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00100_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00100_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_199.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00100_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b196-21" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0115"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_196.25" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00098_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_197.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00099_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Amp" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0115"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_197.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00099_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_198.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00099_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b196-19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0115"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_196.24" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00098_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b196-18" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0115"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_196.20" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00098_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b197-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0115"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_197.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00099_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b196-17" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0115"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_196.19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00098_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b196-16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0115"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_196.18" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00098_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b199-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0115"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_199.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00100_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b196-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0115"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_196.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00098_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b196-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0115"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_196.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00098_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b196-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0115"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_196.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00098_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b196-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0115"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_196.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00098_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b197-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0115"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_197.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00099_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_197.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00099_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b198-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0115"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_198.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00099_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_199.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00100_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b198-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0115"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_198.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00099_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="ANek" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0115"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_197.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00099_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AA5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0115"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_198.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00099_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_198.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00099_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b199-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0115"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_199.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00100_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AXa" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0115"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_196.21" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00098_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_196.22" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00098_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_196.23" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00098_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AIU" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0115"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_196.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00098_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b199-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0115"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_199.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00100_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
