<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044046873683_0466" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="C.C.D. Conn." jurisdiction="United States">United States Circuit Court for the District of Connecticut</court>
          <name abbreviation="Evory v. Candee">EVORY et al. v. CANDEE</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 4,583</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">8 F. Cas. 915</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">17 Blatchf. 200; 4 Ban. &amp; A. 545</citation>
          <decisiondate>1879-10-06</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-12T19:40:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-26T10:42:09Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-26T10:56:35Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00459_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="4272affba1eb5f0ad968512d25bba4f6" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="61360">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00459_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00459_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="7c1ce54fd49365ce04bb405b4aaf8b4b" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="118894">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00459_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00460_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="0cf131a28eb27dea0e86e0ed96697686" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="76978">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00460_0.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00459_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="9617f90da3209cbaec5517fcade6de89" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2936927">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00459_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00459_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="0ca9b4b127487d3dfa90fd547a7b8066" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3818613">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00459_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00460_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="63aacad2645ab7cd4cb0a1bbe8423a3d" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3104394">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00460_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00459_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="55bae420db7cf753d9a78207e530f39a" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="125224">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00459_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00459_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="539912acb87934eca49541fe85758b59" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="246293">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00459_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00460_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="fcf422033fa6b25a3842c8dd14f25fbd" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="159253">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00460_0.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0466" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="917" firstpage="915">
              <court id="ADzA" pgmap="917">Circuit Court, D. Connecticut.</court>
              <docketnumber id="b917-17" pgmap="917">Case No. 4,583.</docketnumber>
              <citation id="b917-19" pgmap="917">[17 Blatchf. 200; 4 Ban. &amp; A. 545.] <footnotemark>1</footnotemark>
              </citation>
              <parties id="b917-18" pgmap="917">EVORY et al. v. CANDEE.</parties>
              <decisiondate id="AdCj" pgmap="917">Oct. 6, 1879.</decisiondate>
              <attorneys id="b917-27" pgmap="917">Frederic H. Betts, for plaintiffs.</attorneys>
              <attorneys id="b917-28" pgmap="917">Charles P. Blake, for defendant.</attorneys>
              <footnote label="1">
                <p id="b917-30" pgmap="917">1 [Reported by Hon. Samuel Blatchford,- Cir­cuit Judge; reprinted in 4 Ban. &amp; A. 545, and here republished by permission.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author id="b917-29" pgmap="917">SHIPMAN, District Judge.</author>
                <p id="AGlO" pgmap="917(195) 918(183)">This is a bill in equity for an account, and is brought to recover from the defendant the license fees which are claimed to be due to the pin in tiffs by virtue of a written agreement between said parties, dated July 10th, 1877, whereby the defendant was licensed, upon an estab­lished royalty, to use letters patent dated. November Oth, 1866, for a “double expansi­ble gore flap,” in the manufacture of boots and shoes. The plaintiffs are citizens of the states of New York and of Michigan. The defendant is a citizen of the state of Con­necticut. The bill alleges, upon information and belief, a manufacture and sale by the de­fendant, between July 10th, 1S77, and Oc­tober 9th, 1878, of a large number of boots and shoes containing the invention described in the. letters patent, and prays for an ac­count of the number manufactured or sold between said dates. The license was re­voked by the plaintiffs on October 9th, 1878. The agreement, which is made part of the bill, recites as follows: “Whereas, letters patent of the United States, dated the Otli day of November, 1866, numbered 59,370, were lawfully granted unto Alexander F. Ev-­ory and Alonzo Heston, for a new and useful invention, consisting of a double expansible gore flap used in the manufacture of boots and shoes; * * * and whereas L. Candee &amp; Co., of New Haven, Conn., manufacturers ■of rubber boots and shoes, are desirous of ac­quiring the privilege and license of Using said invention in the manufacture and sale of shoes.” The agreement, after authorizing the licensors to revoke the license upon non­payment of the royalty, provides, that such revocation should not impair “the effect of the admission of the validity of said letters patent or re-issue, or of the novelty, utility and practicability of the said invention.” A royalty of three cents per pair on all shoes while the licensee should manufacture or sell was established. The licensee further agreed to pay at least five dollars, as a license fee, .upon the first days of each quarter, “even though they should not make enough of said patented shoes to amount to that sum, at the royalty of three cents per pair.”</p>
                <p id="b918-4" pgmap="918">The answer denies that the patentees were the original and first inventors of the al­leged improvement, and, admitting that an agreement of July 10th, 1877, was entered into, denies that the defendant, in said agree­ment, admitted the validity of the patent, but avers, that, "‘before the said license was granted to the defendants herein, the com­plainant Belcher presented to these defendants a printed form of license, in which was print­ed an admission of the validity of the said letters patent here in suit; that these de­fendants had- grave doubts whether said let­ters patent were good and valid, and re­fused to sign the said printed form, because of ■ said admission, and expressly stated to the said Belcher that they did not admit the validity of the said patent, but were willing to take a license thereunder at the stated royalty of three cents per pair for all shoes made by them, which embodied the alleged invention set forth and claimed in said pat­ent, but that they reserved unto themselves the right to deny the validity of said patent and to contest the same, and to refuse to pay said license money, and to continue to use said invention without paymentof saidlicense money, if they should thereafter conclude that said' letters patent were void;” that there­after an agreement or license was prepared, omitting the said admission, which was then, and on July 10th, 1S77, executed by the de­fendant herein; and that the defendant has never, nor has any one for it, paid any roy­alties under the said alleged' license, and has always refused to pay royalties under said license, on the ground of the invalidity of the petters patent; and that the license was revoked by the plaintiffs on October 9th, 1878. The answer alleges the invalidity of the patent for want of novelty , and of pat­entable subject-matter, and that the license is void for want of consideration, and that the “defendants do not know how many, if any, boots and shoes, containing the alleged invention, they have manufactured and sold between July 10th, 1877, and October 9th, 1878, and they refuse to ascertain and state the same.”</p>
                <p id="b918-6" pgmap="918">In this state of the pleadings, the case was set for hearing upon the bill and answer, and the plaintiffs moved for a decree pursuant to the prayer of the bill, “upon the bill and an­swer filed herein and the annexed affidavit and the papers therein referred to,” and filed an affidavit tending to show that the de­fendant, in its answer in another case in this court, had relied upon the validity of the li­censed patent. The defendant filed counter affidavits.</p>
                <p id="b918-7" pgmap="918">The plaintiff's motion is in accordance with the comparatively recent English chancery practice which was authorized by an act of 15 &amp; 16 Viet, and by the orders of court passed in August, 1852. 1 Daniell, Oh. Pr. 822-826. The 90th equity rule of the su­preme court provides, that, in all cases where the prescribed rules do not apply, the prac­tice of the circuit court shall be regulated by the “present” practice of the high court of chancery in England, “not as positive rules, but as furnishing just analogies to regulate the practice.” That rule adopts the English practice, as it was known and understood in 1842, at the time the rule was ordained. Consequently, the practice of,this court re­mains unaffected by the new orders, so called, which the courts of that country have since incorporated into their practice. Badg­er v. Badger [Case No. 717]; Goodyear v. Providence Rubber Co. [Id. 5,583]. This mo­tion, in the form in which it was made, coupled with affidavits, does not seem to be in accordance with the practice of the feder­al courts, but I shall regard the hearing as a hearing upon bill and answer, without ref­erence to the affidavit of the plaintiffs.</p>
                <p id="b918-8" pgmap="918">The question in the case is, whether the answer sets up a legal defence against the admitted facts which are alleged in the bill. “If an answer is insufficient in its responses to the charges and statements in the bill, the objections are to be taken to it by exceptions filed. If it is in substance bad as a defence, and no further proofs are required by the plaintiff, the case can be set down for hear­ing upon the bill and answer, and will be ad­judged accordingly.” Story, Eq. PI. § 456.</p>
                <p id="b918-9" pgmap="918">Two questions are presented by the an­swer: (1) Is the licensee estopped, by the terms of the license, from setting up the in­validity of the patent, as a defence in an action for license fees due prior to the revo­cation of the license? (2) Is a parol agree­ment, made prior to the license, that the licensee shall be at liberty to attack the pat­ent, to be admitted, in view of the recitals and provisions of the license, there being no allegation or claim that anything was in­serted, or was omitted, in the written agree­ment, through fraud, mistake, or accident?</p>
                <p id="b918-10" pgmap="918(8) 919(171)">It is not necessary to consider, upon the first point, the question whether, in an action to recover overdue license fees, the licensee Is estopped from contesting the validity of the patent, by a naked license, and by an unmolested exercise of the right which the license purported to convey, for, in this case, the licensee expressly admitted the validity of the patent, in the recitals of the agree­ment. It is admitted that the agreement ■which is set out in the bill is the one which was executed by both parties. The defend­ant asserts in the license, that the letters patent were lawfully granted to the pat-­entees for a new and useful invention, and has thereby tersely admitted the novelty and utility of the invention specified in the pat­ent, and the validity of the grant to the pat-­entees. It is not permissible to the licensee, unless the recitals were introduced by fraud, imposition, mistake, or accident, to deny their truth, in an action for license fees which accrued before the revocation of the license.</p>
                <p id="b919-3" pgmap="919">The defendant next relies upon a parol agreement, made prior to the execution of the license, whereby it reserved to itself the right to deny the validity of the patent. It appears, from the answer and from the de­fendant’s affidavit, that a license was sent to the defendant, which contained an express .admission of “the validity of said letters pat­ent, and the novelty, utility, and practicabil­ity of the invention therein described and claimed, or that may, or can be, described und claimed in any re-issue thereof.” This agreement the defendant declined to sign. The parties subsequently met, and the de­fendant informed the plaintiffs that it would sign a license, but reserved the right to de­fend on the ground that the patent was not valid, if it should so cortclude, and to use the alleged invention described in the patent without royalty, if it became satisfied that the patent was void. Thereupon, the plain­tiff requested the defendant to draw up a license in the form which it would sign. 'The license set forth in the bill was drawn by the defendant, and was signed by the parties.</p>
                <p id="b919-4" pgmap="919">The defendant suggests that the parol res­ervation was a valid collateral agreement, which should be enforced. It is true, that, oftentimes, a collateral parol agreement has been permitted to be proved, “which does not interfere with the terms of the written con­tract, though it may relate to the same sub­ject-matter.” 2 Tayl. Ev. § 1049. This parol .agreement, reserving a right to use the li­censed invention without royalty, if it be­came satisfied that the patent was void, is substantially inconsistent with the written agreement which the defendant subsequently drew, wherein it promises to pay a royalty •during the unexpired term of the patent, re­serves no right of revocation, twice admits the validity of the patent, and declares that a revocation by the licensors, for non-pay­ment of royalty, shall not impair the effect of the admissions. The parol agreement is in the teeth of the subsequent written con­tract</p>
                <p id="b919-7" pgmap="919">The bill avers a use of the patented inven­tion by the licensees prior to October 9th, 1S7S, which, though not denied, is not admit­ted in the answer. Brown v. Pierce, 7 Wall. [74 U. S.] 205. But the license also provided for a quarterly payment of five dollars, al­though no shoes containing the patented in­vention had been made. The execution of the license having been admitted, it is ap­parent, from the pleadings, that something is due the plaintiffs. Bet there be a decree for an account, in accordance with the prayer of the bill.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="917" ORDERLABEL="915" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00459_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00459_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00459_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_917.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00459_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="918" ORDERLABEL="916" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00459_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00459_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00459_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_918.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00459_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="919" ORDERLABEL="917" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00460_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00460_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00460_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_919.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00460_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b919-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0466"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_919.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00460_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_919.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00460_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b917-27" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0466"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_917.31" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00459_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AGlO" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0466"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_917.34" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00459_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_917.35" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00459_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_918.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00459_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b917-28" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0466"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_917.32" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00459_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b917-29" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0466"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_917.33" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00459_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b918-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0466"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_918.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00459_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_919.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00460_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AdCj" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0466"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_917.25" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00459_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b917-19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0466"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_917.23" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00459_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b917-18" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0466"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_917.22" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00459_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b917-17" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0466"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_917.21" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00459_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b917-30" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0466"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_917.36" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00459_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b919-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0466"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_919.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00460_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="ADzA" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0466"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_917.24" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00459_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b918-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0466"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_918.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00459_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b918-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0466"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_918.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00459_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b918-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0466"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_918.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00459_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_918.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00459_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b919-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0466"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_919.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00460_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b918-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0466"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_918.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00459_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b918-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0466"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_918.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00459_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
