<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044046873683_0021" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="C.C.N.D. Ill." jurisdiction="United States">United States Circuit Court for the Northern District of Illinois</court>
          <name abbreviation="Dunham v. Indianapolis &amp; St. L. R.">DUNHAM v. INDIANAPOLIS &amp; ST. L. R. CO.</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 4,151</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">8 F. Cas. 44</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">7 Biss. 223; 2 Ban. &amp; A. 327; 9 Chi. Leg. News, 50</citation>
          <decisiondate>1876-06</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-12T19:40:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-26T10:42:09Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-26T10:56:33Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00023_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="5c698effb945258f42ea81d77d46d6f6" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="95752">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00023_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00024_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="5f1ada3d571bd86ae2ab316fafd61173" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="99088">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00024_0.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00023_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="c07c6963c555625dd4df9b013731df0a" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3424624">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00023_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00024_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="4bbc4498514120f27a37b43175d3b607" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3667513">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00024_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00023_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="8695009652831a878ada07bdd759630e" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="205791">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00023_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00024_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="9e735d07da1c810e91a8abdfdb1584e7" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="234409">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00024_0.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0021" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="45" firstpage="44">
              <court id="b46-12" pgmap="46">Circuit Court, N. D. Illinois.</court>
              <docketnumber id="b46-7" pgmap="46">Case No. 4,151.</docketnumber>
              <citation id="b46-10" pgmap="46">[7 Biss. 223;<footnotemark>1</footnotemark> 2 Ban. &amp; A. 327; 9 Chi. Leg. News, 50.]</citation>
              <parties id="b46-8" pgmap="46">DUNHAM v. INDIANAPOLIS &amp; ST. L. R. CO.</parties>
              <decisiondate id="AG6" pgmap="46">June, 1876.</decisiondate>
              <attorneys id="b46-18" pgmap="46">Banning &amp; Banning, for plaintiff.</attorneys>
              <attorneys id="b46-19" pgmap="46">Baldwin &amp; Hanna, for defendant</attorneys>
              <footnote label="1">
                <p id="b46-22" pgmap="46">1 [Reported by Josinh H. Bissell, Esq., anti here reprinted by permission.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author id="b46-20" pgmap="46">DRUMMOND, Circuit Judge.</author>
                <p id="AFlh" pgmap="46(227) 47(222)">The facts in this case are, that three persons were pat-­entees for an improvement in car-brake shoes, and that the plaintiff, being one of them, made a contract with the defendant for a li­cense to use the invention described in the patent; the price to be paid for the license was a thousand dollars. The plaintiff exe­cuted and offered to deliver to the defend­ant the license signed by himself, but not by the two other patentees, and the defendant refused to comply with the terms of the con­tract and pay the money, because the license was not signed by all of the patentees. The patentees did not own the right in equal shares; one of them owned a half, and the other two a quarter each, the plaintiff only owning a quarter; and the question in the case is, whether this constitutes a good de­fense to a suit, brought upon the contract made between the plaintiff and the defend­ant; and I am of opinion that it does not The material point is, who is to answer, if any one, to the other patentees for the use of the part which does not belong to them when a joint owner uses the improvement, or makes a contract with another person for its use. What is the position of patentees with refer­ence to tlieir right to use the thing patented? The patentees are tenants in common of the right. One of them has no superiority of right over the other. One of them can manu­facture and use the article patented without the consent of the others; that is, each has the same right, although one may own a greater share of the thing patented than the other. Tiie grant was, in this case, to the three to use and vend the improved car-brake shoes, and while it is clear that one of the patentees can not grant what does not belong to him, and if he gives a license or makes a contract for the use of the thing patented, he can only grant that which he has himself, and not the rights of the other patentees, still he can clothe his grantee or his licensee with the same right that he has himself, namely, the right to sell or use the thing pat­ented. And it seems to me the better rule is to hold, if there is a liability at all, that where a party owning less than the whole of a thing patented, makes a grant or a license, he shall be answerable to the others, rather than that the other patentees shall look to the grantee or licensee.</p>
                <p id="b47-3" pgmap="47">There were three cases particularly referred to on the argument. One was the case di Pitts v. Hall [Case No. 11,193], decided by Judge Hall, of the northern district of New York. 1-Ie seems to hold that if one joint owner of a patent uses or sells his right with­out the authority of his co-owner, he is lia­ble to an action by such co-owner for an in­fringement of the patent; and the conclusion, perhaps, to be drawn from his decision is, that if the party to whom he sells uses the thing patented, an action could be maintained and an injunction issued against the grantee or licensee of the co-owner.</p>
                <p id="b47-4" pgmap="47">Judge Curtis, in the case of Clum v. Brew­er [Id. 2,909], seems to hold, and I think that is the true rule upon the subject, that where one of the joint patentees uses or sells the thing patented, or any portion of it, the oth­ers can not sue him as for an infringement of the patent.</p>
                <p id="b47-5" pgmap="47">Tiie most that can be claimed is, that if one uses or sells it to the detriment of the oth­ers, he may be held responsible. For exam­ple, if he obtains more than his share of the profits from the use of the article, or in issu­ing licenses he obtains more than his share of the license money, he possibly may be held responsible by the other joint patentees; but Judge Curtis, in that case, held that an in­junction should not issue against the use, by one of the joint patentees, of the thing pat­ented, and the principle decided by him is, that one tenant in common of letters patent has the same rights as the others to make, use and sell the thing patented, and a licensee under one tenant in common cannot be en­joined, on a bill by aother tenant in common.</p>
                <p id="b47-8" pgmap="47">A case has been decided in England bear­ing on this question, Mathers v. Green, 1 Ch.­App. 29, and the opinion is given by Lord Chancellor Cranworth. That was a case of letters patent granted to three individuals. The chancellor says:</p>
                <blockquote id="b47-9" pgmap="47">“The right conferred is a right to exclude all the world, other than the grantees, from using the invention. But there is no ex­clusion in the letters patent of any one of the patentees. The inability of any one of the patentees to use the invention, if any such in­ability exists, must be sought elsewhere than in the letters patent. But there is no princi­ple, in the absence of contract, which can prevent any persons not prohibited by stat­ute, from using any invention whatever. Is there any implied contract where two or more persons jointly obtain letters patent, that no one of them shall use the invention without the consent of the others, or, if he does, that he shall use it for their joint ben­efit? I can discover no principle for such a doctrine. It would enable one of two pat-­entees either to prevent the use of the inven­tion altogether, or else to comped the other patentee to risk his skill and capital in the use of the invention on the terms of being accountable for half the profit, if profit should be made, without being able to call on his co-patentee for contribution if there should be loss.”</blockquote>
                <p id="b47-10" pgmap="47">Now while this is the principle announced by the chancellor, it perhaps should be with this qualification: that if one of the patentees obtains more than his share of the profits, he might be held liable under certain circum­stances to the others. Certainly I do not wish to be understood as affirming that there is never such liability. Of course we must take into consideration any risk which he may run; any outlay of money which he may make in the manufacture or sale of the ar­ticle; but if, looking at it upon equitable prin­ciples. he has obtained more than his share of the profits arising from the tiling patent­ed, either in the use or sale of it, or of licenses, it seems to me he might in certain eases be held accountable to the other joint patentees. But it is not necessary in this case to decide that point. My conclusion there­fore is, that the fact that one of the patentees has given a license to the defendant to use the thing patented, clothes him with the right to use it. and having that right, he is liable under his contract for the payment of the one thousand dollars which he agreed to pay for the license.</p>
                <p id="b47-11" pgmap="47">Judgment will accordingly be entered for the plaintiff.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="46" ORDERLABEL="44" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00023_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00023_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00023_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_46.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00023_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="47" ORDERLABEL="45" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00024_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00024_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00024_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_47.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00024_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b46-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0021"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_46.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00023_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AFlh" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0021"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_46.22" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00023_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_46.23" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00023_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_47.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00024_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b46-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0021"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_46.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00023_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b46-12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0021"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_46.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00023_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b46-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0021"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_46.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00023_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b47-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0021"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_47.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00024_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b46-19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0021"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_46.20" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00023_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b46-18" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0021"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_46.19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00023_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b46-22" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0021"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_46.24" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00023_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b47-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0021"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_47.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00024_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b47-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0021"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_47.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00024_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_47.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00024_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b47-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0021"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_47.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00024_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b47-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0021"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_47.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00024_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b47-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0021"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_47.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00024_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b46-20" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0021"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_46.21" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00023_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AG6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0021"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_46.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00023_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b47-11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0021"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_47.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00024_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
