<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044046873683_0625" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="E.D. Va." jurisdiction="United States">United States District Court for the Eastern District of Virginia</court>
          <name abbreviation="In re Ferguson">In re FERGUSON</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 4,738</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">8 F. Cas. 1149</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">2 Hughes, 286; 16 N. B. R. 530</citation>
          <decisiondate>1875-03-30</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-12T19:40:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-26T10:42:09Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-26T10:56:35Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00576_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="d805486131456e6b7976fd718135d80c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="99426">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00576_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00576_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="79bc5ed84e63e7b938e44ee1a182f4f3" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="116078">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00576_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00577_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="8c630abe724a16367d5c22d95e3ccd2b" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="87118">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00577_0.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00576_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="57a0cf7dddcd26a44d4a4643c08ab901" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3508903">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00576_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00576_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="a38c9ac04f3af1bbad8186667ac22190" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3788223">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00576_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00577_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="2c0c5ad2dfcde1535b9558d5c67294ef" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3312756">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00577_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00576_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="a0796401109f3553d31c337a448315f2" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="213033">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00576_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00576_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="05ef98c9de6a22d661be91234b5c33c7" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="252643">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00576_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00577_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="6bf9d07892de9cf520065988499b5875" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="182029">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00577_0.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0625" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="1151" firstpage="1149">
              <court id="Adn_" pgmap="1151">District Court, E. D. Virginia.</court>
              <docketnumber id="b1151-4" pgmap="1151">Case No. 4,738.</docketnumber>
              <citation id="b1151-6" pgmap="1151">[2 Hughes, 286;<footnotemark>1</footnotemark> 16 N. B. R. 530.]</citation>
              <parties id="b1151-5" pgmap="1151">In re FERGUSON.</parties>
              <decisiondate id="Apcu" pgmap="1151">March 30, 1875.</decisiondate>
              <footnote label="1">
                <p id="b1151-12" pgmap="1151">1 [Reported by Hon. Robert W. Hughes, Dis­trict Judge, and here reprinted by permission.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author id="b1151-14" pgmap="1151">HUGHES, District Judge.</author>
                <p id="A8Y" pgmap="1151">John A. Fergu­son filed his petition here, on the 27th Octo­ber, 1874, setting forth that he had received a discharge from his debts as a bankrupt on the 25th day of March, 1870; that after the issu­ing of said discharge a suit was brought against him, upon a debt contracted before his adjudication, in the circuit court of the i county of Pittsylvania; that after being sued ! he placed his certificate of discharge in the • hands of the attorney employed by him, to wit, R. H. Tredway, to be used in his defence; that the discharge was not filed (pleaded) by reason of the neglect of his said counsel, and judgment was in consequence obtained against him, at the May term of the said cir­cuit court in 1874; that execution was issued thereon; that an injunction was applied for and obtained from the said circuit court, to stay proceedings; that with his bill praying for said injunction his discharge was filed as an exhibit; that the judge of the said circuit court of Pittsylvania, at the succeeding term of said court, dissolved the said injunction; and that execution again issued and was in the hands of the sheriff of Pittsylvania at the filing of this petition.</p>
                <p id="b1151-15" pgmap="1151">On the filing of the petition here, this, the court of bankruptcy which granted the dis­charge, granted a restraining order against all proceedings by the said sheriff until the further order of court; and a rule was given against the plaintiff in the said suit in the circuit court of Pittsylvania and the said sheriff, to show cause why the injunction should not be made perpetual. The parties are now before this court on the rule awarded as aforesaid, and on the answer of the said sheriff, who as administrator was also the plaintiff in the suit on which the executions issued. I should not have granted the re­straining order upon the Pittsylvania sheriff, but for the frequency with which this ques­tion of the bankrupt’s liability when he fails to plead his discharge, arises. The only ques­tion presented is, whether this court has juris­diction to relieve against a judgment ob­tained against a bankrupt in a suit brought against him after his adjudication, in which, for any cause, he has failed to plead his dis­charge. Clearly it has not. The discharge in bankruptcy must-be pleaded in suits upon debts existing before the bankruptcy, just as payment, or the statute of limitations, should be pleaded in proceedings where those pleas constitute the proper defences. If the bank­rupt fails, from any cause, to interpose che discharge in bankruptcy, in the suit against him in the state court, this court will not re­lieve against the consequences of his own neglect His proper recourse is in the court of law in which the suit was pending; or else by appeal from that court to one having ap­pellate jurisdiction over it, which, in the pres­ent case, this court of course has not; or else by a bill of injunction in a state court of chancery.</p>
                <p id="b1151-16" pgmap="1151(9) 1152(83)">There is but one view of the matter in which this court could consider the question' of relief against such a judgment as that com­plained of. By virtue of the district court of the United States, as a court of equity, hav­ing jurisdiction of matters connected with and growing out of bankruptcy proceedings, it might exercise the same jurisdiction to relieve from a judgment at law in a matter connected with bankruptcy which a state court of equi­ty would have if the matter were not connect­ed with bankruptcy.</p>
                <p id="b1152-4" pgmap="1152">Although not required in the present case to pass upon that question of jurisdiction, which is a very important one, I will as­sume for the sake of argument that this court would enjoin against the judgment at law complained of, if the facts of this case were ■ such as to warrant it in doing so. In deter­mining whether they are of that character my safest and most proper guide are the decisions of the court of highest resort of this common­wealth. The rulings of that court are so strongly against the exercise of such a juris­diction, that I should feel bound to refuse to interfere if I were passing upon a bill of in­junction brought on the chancery side of this court, rather than a petition in bankruptcy on its bankruptcy side.</p>
                <p id="b1152-5" pgmap="1152">The following are extracts from some of •the decisions of the Virginia court of ap­peals on this subject In Tapp’s Adm’r v.' Rankin, 9 Leigh, 478, that court said: “Al­though it may be manifest that’great in­justice has been done a defendant at law by the verdict and judgment against him, yet if this injustice had not been produced by any fraud, or surprise on the part of the plain­tiff, but is the result either of the defendant’s own negligence or of his counsel’s ignorance or bad management, a court of equity can give him no relief.”</p>
                <p id="b1152-6" pgmap="1152">In Meem v. Rucker, 10 Grat 506, that .court decided that an injunction to a judg­ment at law will not be sustained where the defendant at law has failed to make his de-­fence at law, from ignorance of the nature of the proceeding against him, and a mis­taken apprehension of the steps it was nec­essary to take in his defence, remarking: “Now, that a party to whom a day and an opportunity have been allowed to make his defence against a demand set up against him in a court of law, but who has wholly failed to avail himself of them, will not be enter­tained in a court of chancery on a bill seek­ing relief against the judgment which has been rendered against him in consequence of his default, upon grounds which might have been successfully taken in the court of law, unless some reason founded on fraud, acci­dent, surprise, or some other adventitious circumstance beyond the control of the party, be shown why the defence was not made in that court, is a proposition which has been so repeatedly affirmed that it has become a principle and maxim of equity as well settled as any other whatever. It has been recognized and acted upon in very •numerous cases in this court as well' of ancient as of recent date. The rule has its foundation in wisdom and sound policy. It springs out of the future necessity fOr pre­scribing some period at which litigation must cease; and I am utterly unable to appreciate the force or justness of the complaints, which, in view of its supposed harsh opera­tion in particular cases, have sometimes been made against it. I think that private right and public interest alike require that it should be adhered to. So numerous indeed and so familiar are the cases in which this court has recognized the doctrine, that I deem it entirely unnecessary to cite them here.”</p>
                <p id="b1152-8" pgmap="1152">Lee, J, in Meem v. Rucker, 10 Grat. 509, 510. In another case that court said: “A defendant upon whom process has been served, who wholly neglects his defence, or contents himself with employing a lawyer who practices in the court to defend him. without giving him any information about his defence, or inquiring whether he is at­tending to the case, is not entitled to relief on the ground of surprise, however grossly unjust the decree may appear to be.” Hill v. Bowyer, 18 Grat. 382-386.</p>
                <p id="b1152-9" pgmap="1152">In another case, however, that court de­cided that where a defendant at law has been prevented from making his defence by the assurances or promises of the counsel of the.plaintiff, equity will relieve him. 22 Grat 136. For the grounds on which equity will or will not relieve against judg­ment at law, see Holland v. Trotter, Id. 136.</p>
                <p id="b1152-10" pgmap="1152(275) 1153(194)">In Wallace v. Richmond, decided by the court of appeals of Virginia, as late as the 25th March, 1875, reported in 26 Grat 67, which was on a bill in chancery to enjoin a judgment at law. that court again said: “It is true that after the writ was served on him he retained counsel to defend the suit, and informed him of the grounds of his defence, to wit, that he was sued as a partner of Black &amp; Co., and was not and never was a partner or member of said linn, in any way liable for said debt. But he gave no further attention to the suit. It does not appear that he even spoke to his counsel on the subject or made any preparation for his defence; though he was probably at the place where the court was held during the term. His counsel en­tered no plea to set aside the office judgment, and made no defence whatever, and judg­ment went against him by default. His counsel says he examined the docket and saw no case upon it of ‘Richmond, Assignee, v. Wallace.’ He saw the case of Richmond, assignee, against Black &amp; Co., but it never occurred to him that the appellant was sued in that case, and he did not look into the papers to see. Yet he had been informed bj the appellant that he was sued as a member of that firm, and that his ground of defence was, that he was not and never had been a member of it; and he thinks he showed him a copy of the summons which had been served on him. His counsel says he did not remember to have been shown a copy of the summons, and was not aware that the appel-­lee was interested in that suit, else he would have looked into the papers and en­tered a plea. But a plea- denying the part­nership could not have availed for his de-­fence unless verified by affidavit; but the de­fendant was not there to make affidavit to it. It seems to the court a plain case of negligence on the part of the appellant’s at­torney, not unmixed with fault or negligence on his part. And without deciding that mere inadvertence or forgetfulness on the part of the attorney would deprive a party of his right to relief in equity, where the de­fendant himself had used proper diligence and was chargeable with no laches, the court is of opinion that a court of equity could not interfere by injunction in this case, to re­strain the execution of the judgment, and to give the appellant another trial, who has al­ready had his day in court, without overturn­ing the well-established rule in such cases.”</p>
                <p id="b1153-4" pgmap="1153">Such are the decisions of the court of the highest resort in this state on the question of opening judgments obtained through the negligence of defendants or their attorneys. Even, therefore, if the court of bankruptcy had the right of a court of equity in such a case as that of this bankrupt, it would not interfere to relieve him against the laches of his counsel and himself.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="1151" ORDERLABEL="1149" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00576_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00576_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00576_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_1151.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00576_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="1152" ORDERLABEL="1150" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00576_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00576_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00576_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_1152.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00576_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="1153" ORDERLABEL="1151" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00577_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00577_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00577_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_1153.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00577_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1152-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0625"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1152.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00576_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1152-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0625"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1152.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00576_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="A8Y" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0625"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1151.18" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00576_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1151.19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00576_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1151-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0625"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1151.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00576_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1151-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0625"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1151.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00576_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1151-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0625"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1151.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00576_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1152-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0625"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1152.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00576_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1152-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0625"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1152.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00576_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1152.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00576_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1152-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0625"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1152.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00576_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Apcu" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0625"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1151.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00576_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1151-12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0625"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1151.16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00576_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1151-16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0625"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1151.21" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00576_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1152.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00576_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1151-15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0625"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1151.20" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00576_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1151-14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0625"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1151.17" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00576_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Adn_" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0625"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1151.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00576_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1153-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0625"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1153.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00577_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1152-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0625"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1152.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00576_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1153.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00577_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
