<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044049817315_0011" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="S.D.N.Y." jurisdiction="United States">United States District Court for the Southern District of New York</court>
          <name abbreviation="The Indiana">The INDIANA</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 7,020</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">13 F. Cas. 22</citation>
          <decisiondate>1848-11</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-10T00:25:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:27:33Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:41:25Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00012_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="97922849087df4b55ced3e60eb1c8bcc" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="68602">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00012_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00013_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="172e80fce160fba2e80c403889031b5e" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="109818">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00013_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00013_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="35a848fa695ef10c02657e0a1078f9b2" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="96968">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00013_1.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00012_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="9998a777c207ed34aba1c2d73a4d4262" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2786543">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00012_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00013_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="dcee80383df13cb168330532e869983c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3713902">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00013_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00013_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="ba9616c9bea70978078aca63cb510331" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3442426">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00013_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00012_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="973032809fb267526ca63419e3447ca9" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="144687">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00012_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00013_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="0b4350c38c9896f2546f0b7b9224c703" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="241797">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00013_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00013_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="c06e51a37d8d3c5caca3815211d50a56" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="203251">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00013_1.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0011" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="24" firstpage="22">
              <court pgmap="24" id="b24-7">District Court, S. D. New York.</court>
              <docketnumber pgmap="24" id="b24-4">Case No. 7,020.</docketnumber>
              <parties pgmap="24" id="b24-5">The INDIANA.</parties>
              <decisiondate pgmap="24" id="AQ">Nov., 1848.</decisiondate>
              <attorneys pgmap="24" id="b24-19">E. O. Benedict, for libellants.</attorneys>
              <attorneys pgmap="24" id="b24-20">O. Van Santvoordt, for claimant.</attorneys>
              <p pgmap="24" id="b24-6">[Abb. Adm. 330.] <footnotemark>1</footnotemark>
              </p>
              <footnote label="1">
                <p pgmap="24" id="b24-16">1 [Reported by Abbott Brothers.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author pgmap="24" id="b24-21">BETTS, District Judge.</author>
                <p pgmap="24" id="Anc">The libellants having established a right, primfi facie, to compensation for the injuries received in the collision articled upon, the case rests upon the sufficiency of the “defence made on behalf of the claimant. That defence speci­fies three acts of the libellants which, it is contended, were wrongful under the cir­cumstances, and operated to cause the col­lision, without fault or negligence on the part of the claimant.</p>
                <p pgmap="24" id="b24-22">Those facts are the following: (1) That the schooner wras anchored, in a thick, dark night, nearly in the middle of the river, in the ordinary route and channel of steam vessels passing up and down the river. (2) That no light, proper and sufficient to warn approaching vessels of the position of the schooner, was exhibited upon her at the time of the collision. (3) That no watch was kept on her deck at the time.</p>
                <p pgmap="24(249) 25(13)" id="b24-23">It is contended, that owing to these acts of culpable negligence, those in charge of the steamboat were prevented from discern­ing the schooner until so near her as to render it impossible to avoid the collision. So far as respects the character of the weather and the position of the schooner, the evidence upon both sides is in substan­tial harmony. For although some of the testimony introduced on behalf of the libel-­lant charges that the night was so dark that no vessel could be safely navigated, yet the weight of evidence on that side, in concur­rence with all the testimony offered for the claimant, is to the effect that it was proper and safe, on the night in question, for steam vessels to run, inasmuch as the land on each side of the river could be seen. And although there was a slight disagreement amongst the witnesses as to the position of the schooner — the claimant’s witnesses stat­ing that she lay “in the middle of the riv­er,” and the witnesses for the libellant say­ing that she was “a third or more of the width of the river from the east shore,”— yet the discrepancy is too slight to embar­rass the court in applying to the case the rules of law governing cases of a similar kind. For the assertion of the pilot of the Indiana, that the position taken up by the schooner was an unusual one for vessels to anchor in, is not contradicted by any evi­dence upon the other side.</p>
                <p pgmap="25" id="b25-3">These facts, then, are established by the pleadings and proofs. That the wind was northeast, and the tide a strong ebb. That the'schooner lay at anchor wide oft in the river. That the night was so thick and dark, that an object of the size and color of the schooner could not, without the aid of a light on board of her, be discovered by those on board of a steamboat running on the same track, at a distance of more than ten or fifteen rods oft. That the position thus taken up by the schooner was one far out in the river, there a mile or more in width, and at a place where steamboats were not bound to exercise extraordinary circumspection or precaution in expectation of coming upon vessels at anchor.</p>
                <p pgmap="25" id="b25-4">In respect to that charge of negligence on the part of libellants, which is based on the position selected by the schooner for an­choring, the rule applicable to such cases requires the promovent to show that there was positive fault or negligence on the part of the colliding vessel, and thgt there was no blamable conduct in the one injured, conducing to the collision. The utmost that is made out by the claimant is, that the choice of the place where the schooner an­chored might possibly have led to the ac­cident. There is no evidence that any fixed understanding exists amongst navigators on the Hudson river, to the effect that vessels will not anchor out towards the middle of the river, even at points where it is of such great breadth; nor any proof that it is the invariable or even the most usual course for steamboats to hold a course directly midway the river during the night time. I do not think, therefore, that this case can be ranged with those where vessels are guilty of cul­pable negligence in anchoring in the common passages of great thoroughfares. After leav­ing the immediate harbor of New York, and particularly in those parts of the North river where there is a navigable channel of a mile or more in width, there does not seem to be any rule, or any necessity, com­pelling vessels to coniine their anchorage within any particular limit, or excusing those under way in one part of the channel from exercising the ordinary precaution and vigi­lance which might be required from them in another part.</p>
                <p pgmap="25" id="b25-5">The charge of negligence, in not keeping a light conspicuously suspended on the schooner, is better founded. Both the stat­ute law of the state and the equally strin­gent rule of the maritime law, require a ves­sel at anchor, under such circumstances as are shown in this ease, to maintain a good and sufficient light throughout the night, so placed as to be visible to other vessels ap­proaching her from any direction. Com­pare, also, The Santa Claus [Case No. 12,-­327]. 1 Rev. St. 685, § 2; Thain v. The North America [Case No. 13,853]; Simpson v. Hand, 6 Wheat. 324; Bullock v. The Lamar [Case No. 2,129]; Waring v. Clarke, 5 How. [40 U. S.] 441. And the testimony on the part of the claimants is full and satisfactory to show that no light on the schooner was discernible from the steam­boat, either before or at the time of the col­lision.</p>
                <p pgmap="25" id="b25-9">This evidence is given not by the pilot and other persons on board the steamboat alone, but by others on the canal boats in tow alongside her. The witnesses all assert that they were on a vigilant look-out, — the alarm-bell of the steamer having been rung, —and that they saw a few rods ahead a dark object on the water, but no appearance of a light -upon any part of it.</p>
                <p pgmap="25" id="b25-10">It is proved, by those on board of the schooner, that a globe lamp was trimmed and lighted, and properly set, at about eleven o’clock that night, and that at the time of the collision it remained in the same place, still lighted, and was taken down and used in searching for the damages she might have received. The pilot, however, adds that the wick was found crusted thickly, ..and he picked the wick before hanging it up again.</p>
                <p pgmap="25" id="b25-11">' After the two vessels were separated, the steamer passed down the river, but return­ed a short time subsequently to put back upon the schooner one of her crew, who had got on board the steamer during the col­lision. On that occasion the light of the lamp was plainly seen by those on board the steamer, in season to give them notice of her proximity in ample time to avoid a collision. This circumstance is urged, on the part of the libellants, to show that the lamp had all the time given sufficient light to warn the steam­er where the schooner lay; while it is, on the other hand, invoked by the claimant, as evidence that the re-trimming of the lamp was necessary to render it of any service to other vessels approaching her.</p>
                <p pgmap="25" id="Aqs">I think this particular is not sufficient to countervail the strong proofs furnished by the claimant of the absence of any light ex­hibited on the schooner at the time of the col­lision, competent to afford warning to the steamer of her position. The light prob­ably continued feebly kindled and burning too obscurely to give more light than enough to show the men. as they came on deck, that the wick was still ignited; and even that effect might well be produced from the jar of the two vessels in the collision, shaking up or resuscitating slightly the flame.</p>
                <p pgmap="25" id="b25-13">The weight of evidence, in my opinion, is against the libellants upon this point, and fastens the fault on them of having failed to keep up, burning during the night, a clear light, placed conspicuously on the ves­sel.</p>
                <p pgmap="25(36) 26(146)" id="b25-14">The omission of the libellants to maintain a competent watch on deck throughout the night is clearly proved. That was an act of gross negligence on their part. Com­pare, also, The Rebecca [Case No. 11,618]. All hands on board the schooner turned in at about eleven o’clock in the evening. A look-out, doing his duty on deck, could have secured the schooner from the accident. He could have given the steamer timely warn­ing, by hailing or by waving a light, and especially would have acquitted the schoon­er of fault in respect to a standing light on the vessel, by seeing that the lamp was kept in proper condition, and furnished the light required by law. Aside from the posi­tive duty to maintain such a light, enjoined by the local statute, these acts of omission •are made by the maritime law evidence of culpable inattention and want of precaution, which bar the schooner of all claim to dam­ages she may have suffered in consequence of the neglect. The libel must therefore be dismissed, with costs to be taxed.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="24" ORDERLABEL="22" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00012_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00012_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00012_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_24.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00012_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="25" ORDERLABEL="23" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00013_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00013_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00013_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_25.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00013_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="26" ORDERLABEL="24" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00013_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00013_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00013_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_26.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00013_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b24-16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_24.27" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00012_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b24-23" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_24.26" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00012_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_25.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00013_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b24-22" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_24.25" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00012_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b24-21" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_24.22" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00012_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b24-19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_24.20" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00012_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Aqs" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_25.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00013_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b25-11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_25.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00013_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b25-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_25.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00013_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b25-13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_25.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00013_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b25-14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_25.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00013_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_26.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00013_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b25-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_25.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00013_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_25.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00013_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b25-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_25.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00013_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b25-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_25.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00013_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b24-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_24.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00012_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b25-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_25.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00013_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Anc" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_24.23" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00012_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_24.24" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00012_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AQ" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_24.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00012_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b24-20" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_24.21" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00012_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b24-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_24.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00012_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b24-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_24.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00012_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b24-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_24.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00012_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
