<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044049817315_0268" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="C.C.S.D. Ohio" jurisdiction="United States">United States Circuit Court for the Southern District of Ohio</court>
          <name abbreviation="Jenkins v. Greenwald">JENKINS v. GREENWALD</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 7,270</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">13 F. Cas. 519</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">2 Fish. Pat. Cas. 37; 1 Bond, 126</citation>
          <decisiondate>1857-04</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-10T00:25:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:27:33Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:41:27Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00261_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="805f60121c610d5236844b81e85d30d9" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="101014">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00261_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00261_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="9dbde30e709b68ed420f8694caa7de1e" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="64530">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00261_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00262_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="5a176df7e0ff367ebacc73dfeb2ff344" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="108746">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00262_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00262_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="fe76a007041780a40f7978c9832561cc" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="113458">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00262_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00263_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="997d378eefd63ba4d16bfb85ed2cc90b" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="112860">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00263_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00263_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="5a3cb5ea7a26f9533ab1d9e22e8cf2a2" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="113214">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00263_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00264_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="b1686c23013c32a06ae3a52a152de04f" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="73618">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00264_0.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00261_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="5423b91ec4b53eabf683d50e177c79f8" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3519836">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00261_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00261_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="71f10b71389ae7e4f540aa503c6c23ea" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2600308">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00261_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00262_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="d109b8374fcbb13e8cdc514b3b682614" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3756976">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00262_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00262_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="160dcd95f4ec3e8be77ba005ae4afb27" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3815154">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00262_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00263_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="6316bff113e262a66613797c2a308850" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3860125">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00263_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00263_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="4746da8a4ae4bc1ce829146db084a253" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3813924">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00263_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00264_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="c560107587ecced83f22956c0aa06574" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2885931">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00264_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00261_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="34193efa2475c2e27bb7bcdb52ec7186" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="217173">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00261_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00261_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="188ff3cf6175687d32c810ad59b6fcc1" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="136308">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00261_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00262_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="8ad35d3931b93109b3c2d0521c8f4ed4" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="239483">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00262_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00262_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="409ca06e54714d47c455c8bfaada1c7f" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="240933">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00262_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00263_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="5fbf4dc68c36098ae1de1a75b13da627" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="239919">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00263_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00263_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="4eed8ba32ed05af3b482f56717a4e95f" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="238548">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00263_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00264_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="77e284122024da804f7358ae8a63d716" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="157271">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00264_0.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0268" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="525" firstpage="519">
              <court pgmap="521" id="b521-11">Circuit Court, S. D. Ohio.</court>
              <docketnumber pgmap="521" id="b521-8">Case No. 7,270.</docketnumber>
              <citation pgmap="521" id="b521-10">[2 Fish. Pat. Cas. 37; 1 Bond, 126.] <footnotemark>1</footnotemark>
              </citation>
              <parties pgmap="521" id="b521-9">JENKINS v. GREENWALD.</parties>
              <decisiondate pgmap="521" id="Av0f">April Term, 1857.</decisiondate>
              <attorneys pgmap="522" id="b522-14">Coffin &amp; Mitchell, for complainant.</attorneys>
              <attorneys pgmap="522" id="b522-15">R. D. &amp; J. H. Handy, for defendant.</attorneys>
              <footnote label="1">
                <p pgmap="521" id="b521-15">1 [Reported by Samuel S. Fisher, Esq.; re­printed in 1 Bond, 126, and here republished by permission.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author pgmap="522" id="b522-16">LEAVITT, District Judge..</author>
                <p pgmap="522" id="AGxG">This case is before the court on a motion by the com­plainant for a decree to perpetuate the in­junction heretofore allowed by Judge Mc­Lean, and for the profits arising from an al­leged infringement, by the defendant, of the complainant’s exclusive right to construct Woodworth’s patented planing machine within certain territorial limits, which will be hereafter noticed. This motion is resist­ed on several grounds, which will be advert­ed to.</p>
                <p pgmap="522(479) 523(167)" id="b522-19">Before proceeding to the consideration of the points arising in the case, it will be proper to state the material facts involved. This I shall do without presenting even an analysis of the allegations of the parties, as set forth in their pleadings. On April 21, 184G, James G. Wilson, in whom was vested, by assignment, the title to the Woodworth patent, entered into a contract with the com­plainant and one Benjamin Bicknell. by which, on the conditions specified. Wilson sold and granted them “the exclusive right to make, use, and vend to others to con­struct and use, during the full term of said letters patent, from this day until Decem­ber 27. 1S5G, machines for planing, tongue-­ing. and grooving, upon the principle, plan, and description of the said renewed patent, and amended specifications, within the ter­ritory of Hamilton county, in the state of Ohio, and so much of the adjacent territory in the state of Kentucky as lies along and adjoining said Hamilton county, and within five miles of the Ohio river.” After reserv­ing the right of Hudson and Hughes to the use of one machine in the city of Cincinnati, previously granted by Wilson, the contract recites that several other licenses had been granted within Hamilton county on certain conditions stated. Wilson also reserves the right to license the use of other machines within the territory designated in the con­tract, upon the condition “that the aggre­gate machines allowed by sale or license, executed by him, or his former assignees, Brooks and Morris, licensed to be used in that territory, do not exceed thirteen,” etc. It is then provided that “Bicknell and Jen­kins shall not erect for use, or directly or indirectly authorize to be used, within the said territory, any machines, until the num­ber is, or shall be, reduced to eight, and when any right of any person to use any of the said thirteen machines shall cease, Bick-­nell and Jenkins shall not put in operation a machine or machines in lieu thereof, until the whole number of machines in said terri­tory shall be reduced below eight, and when so reduced, the number of machines shall be kept at eight.” It is also agreed that, in the licenses to be granted, it shall be stipu­lated that the licensees shall not work lum­ber, by said machines, at a less rate than seven dollars per 1,000 feet of board meas­ure, and that they shall render full accounts of their earnings, etc. Bicknell and Jenkins agree to pay for the rights granted at the rate of $2.500 a year, with the condition, that if their receipts from licenses do not amount in any year to that sum, they are to pay or account to Wilson at the rate of $1.25 per thousand, etc. Wilson binds him­self, “on due notice to institute and prose­cute all actions necessary to secure the mo­nopoly granted by said patent, within said, territory, at his own expense, and expressly reserves to himself all damages which may accrue therein, and the exclusive right to prosecute for piracies.” Bicknell and Jen­kins reserve the right, on giving three months’ notice of their intention, to surren­der the agreement, at the end of any year. Wilson, after the assignment to Jenkins and Bicknell above mentioned, assigned whatev­er remaining interest he had in said letters patent within said territory to Elisha Bloomer. On August 25, 1847, Bicknell as­signed to Elisha Bloomer an undivided half of his right to build machines under said contract; and on September 1. 1849, Bloom­er assigned his interest to Bicknell. On De­cember 2, 1853, Bicknell assigned all his right to build and sell machines, all claims for damages for infringements, and for prof­its of making the machine, to the complain­ant.</p>
                <p pgmap="523" id="b523-3">It is among the averments of the bill, that the defendant had made a number of ma­chines, at Cincinnati, upon the plan of the Woodworth patent, without license therefor from Wilson, in violation of the complain­ant’s exclusive right; and that then, on Au­gust 29, 1854, he was engaged in making one at his shop in Cincinnati. The bill - prays for an injunction restraining the de­fendant from the further construction of the machines, and for an account of the profits, and for general relief. The defend­ant, in his answer, admits, in substance, that he had constructed several planing ma­chines on the Woodworth plan, at Cincin­nati, without a license from Wilson, and that at the time of the filing of the bill, he had one in his shop. He denies that he has infringed any right of the1 complainant, and avers that the complainant has no ex­clusive right to build the machines for use or sale, outside of the limits of the territory designated in the contract with Wilson.</p>
                <p pgmap="523" id="b523-4">This case has been referred to a master, to take testimony as to the number of ma­chines constructed by the defendant, and the profit derived therefrom. The report of the master shows the number of machines made by the defendant; and that either at the time the notice of the application for the injunction was served, or at the time of filing the bill, there was one in his shop. But it appears from the evidence, that all the machines made by the defendant were sold, to be used at places not within the lim­its of the territory described in the contract referred to.</p>
                <p pgmap="523" id="b523-5">The first objection to the decree asked for by the complainant is, that this court has not jurisdiction. By section 37 of the pat­ent act of 1836 [5 Stat. 124], jurisdiction is given to the circuit courts of the United States, in all cases arising under any law of the United States, granting or confirming to inventors the exclusive right to their inven­tions or discoveries; and they are author­ized, “upon a bill in equity filed by any par­ty aggrieved in any such case, to grant in­junctions, according to the course and prin­ciple of courts of equity, to prevent the vio­lation of the rights of any inventor as se­cured to him, by any law of the United States, on such terms and conditions as said courts may deem reasonable.” Although inventors only are named as entitled to the benefits of this statute, no doubt can be en­tertained that it extends to and includes the assignees of such inventors. Ogle v. Ege [Case No. 10,462]; [Woodworth v. Wilson] 4 How. [45 U. S.] 712. Such was clearly the view of Judge McLean in granting the in­junction in this case. The statute limits the discretion of the court to the granting of in­junctions, “according to the course and prin­ciple of courts of equity,” etc. And it is in­sisted by counsel, that, as the case before the court shows that, at the time the writ of injunction issued, the defendant was not in the act of infringing the complainant’s exclusive right, and has denied any inten­tion of doing so in future, there is nothing on which the injunction can operate, and that, therefore! it should be dissolved, and the bill dismissed. It is true, if there was sufficient ground for the allowance of the injunction, and the case is to be viewed as a mere proceeding to recover compensation for an infringement of the complainant’s ex­clusive right, there would be great force in the objection now urged to the jurisdiction of this court. In the case supposed, there would seem to be an adequate remedy at law, which would render the interposition of a court of equity improper.</p>
                <p pgmap="523(207) 524(71)" id="b523-8">The allegations of the bill, and the ad­missions of the defendant, in his answer, as to the fact of infringement, have been before noticed. Upon the point now under consideration, the only inquiry is, whether it is necessary to justify an order for an injunction, or for its continuance when al­lowed, that the defendant should have been in the act of infringing the complainant's exclusive rights at the time of its allow­ance. The argument of the counsel for the defendant is based on the supposition that this is necessary. But, it seems clear, the position of counsel is not sustained, either by reason or authority. In his treatise on Patents (section 335) Mr. Curtis says: “If the plaintiff shows the necessary posses­sion, and an infringement has actually been committed by the defendant, the injunction will be granted, notwithstanding the de­fendant admits the infringement, and prom­ises not to repeat it.” The writer refers to the case of Losh v. Hague, Webst. Pat. Cas. 200, as sustaining his position. In that case, the vice-chancellor is reported as saying: “Now. it seems to me that there can be no question but that the wheels complained of as having been made by the defendant, do answer the description of the plaintiff’s wheels, and I do not think it enough, on a question of injunction, for the defendant to say that he has done the thing complained of, but will not do it again.” And further, “But if once the thing complained of has been done, I apprehend this court inter­feres, notwithstanding any promise the de­fendant may make not to do the same thing again.”</p>
                <p pgmap="524" id="b524-4">I think the supreme court of the United States, in the case of Woodworth v. Wilson, 4 How. [45 U. S.] 712, decided the point under consideration, though not expressly referred to, in the opinion given. That was a proceeding in chancery for an infringe­ment of the Woodworth patent. An injunc­tion had been granted to restrain the de­fendant from the use of the machine; and in the progress of the case, a rule for the attachment against him, for violating the injunction, had been issued. In the state­ment in the proceedings in the court below, it appears that the defendant showed cause against the rule, by an affidavit in which he stated that immediately on the service of the injunction he ceased to use the ma­chine. The report further states that the case was heard on the merits and upon the rule granted; and the court dissolved the injunction, dismissed the bill, and dischar­ged the rule. The case was appealed to the supreme court of the United States, where the decree of the circuit court was reversed. Although not specially noticed by the judge in delivering the opinion of the court, it is obvious the point under consideration was decided. For, if the fact stated in the de­fendant’s affidavit, that he had ceased to use the machine upon the service of the in­junction, had been viewed by the supreme court as a sufficient ground for the decree in the court below, dissolving the injunc­tion and dismissing the bill, it is clear there would have been no sufficient ground for reversing that decree. In the opinion of the court, it is remarked that “some oth­er objections were taken to the maintenance of the suit on the argument, which it is not material to notice particularly. They have all been considered; and, in the judgment of the court, afford no sufficient ground for the dismissal of the bill, and the dissolving the injunction." These authorities seem de­cisive on the point referred to. They es­tablish the position, that if the party pro­ceeded against as an infringer of the ex­clusive right of the person having the title to the patent, admits the infringement, but asserts that after notice or service of the injunction, he had refrained from the use of the thing patented, and asserts that he will not afterward infringe, it is no reason why an injunction should not issue, and bo made perpetual. The complainant in 3uch a case is not obliged to rest his interests on the mere asseveration of the party, that he will not repeat the act of infringement. Having once been a wrong-doer, the law supposes the possibility of his being so again, and will impose the proper restraint to prevent the repetition of the wrongful act. This view sufficiently explains the reason why the court has declined to make an order for a further reference of this case to the master, and. for leave to amend the answer, in accordance with the motion of counsel, filed since the argument on the hearing. The principal ground of the mo­tion was, that there was an error committed by the master in taking the testimony in relation to the day on which the last ma­chine made by the defendant was taken from his shop, and a similar error by the defendant in his answer on the same point. It is obvious, that if the conclusion of the court, as indicated, is correct, there could be no necessity for the reference moved for, as the legal aspect of the question would not be affected by thé admission that the facts were as claimed by the defendant.</p>
                <p pgmap="524" id="b524-6">It is further insisted in argument, by the counsel for the defendant, that the com­plainant has precluded himself from taking a decree, in his favor, by allowing the de­fendant to be examined as a witness before the master, on the reference to him, and numerous authorities are cited, to the effect that if a complainant in chancery examines a defendant as a witness, it is a waiver of his right to a decree against him. Such, under ordinary circumstances, is, without doubt, the rule in chancery. But it is not applicable to the present case. In the first place, there is no evidence before the court that the defendant was examined as a wit­ness before the master, at the suggestion or request, or with the knowledge of the complainant. There is, however, anotner answer to this objection. By the seventy-­seventh rule of the rules adopted by the supreme court of the United States, regu­lating the chancery practice of the circuit courts, it is provided, that “the master shall regulate all the proceedings in every hear­ing before him, upon every such reference; and he shall have full authority to examine the parties in the cause, upon oath, touch­ing all matters contained in the reference," etc. These rules were adopted by the su­preme court, under the authority of an act of congress, and are, of course, obligatory on the circuit courts. And the eighth rule of this court, declaring that “interest in the event of a suit shall not render a witness incompetent, unless he be a party to the suit,” neither conflicts with, nor abrogates, the seventy-seventh rule of the chancery practice. The circuit court has not the au­thority to rescind a rule adopted by the su­preme court for the government of its prac­tice in chancery. And the eighth rule, above quoted, excluding, by implication, a party from being a witness, was obviously Intend­ed to apply to cases at law.</p>
                <p pgmap="524(8) 525(278)" id="b524-7">It is also contended in argument, that the complainant is not entitled to a decree for profits in- this suit, if an infringement is proved, for the reason that the right to sue for and recover damages for piracies has not vested in him, by the assignments of Wilson to Bloomer, and of Bloomer to Bick-­nell. It is claimed by counsel that the lat­ter assignment is only of the right of Bloom­er to “build machines in. Hamilton county, and can not be held to imply a right in the assignee to sue for damages accruing from infringements.” These assignments have been before noticed. Wilson’s assignment to Bloomer was, “of all his remaining inter­est in the patent” within the territory des­ignated, and Bloomer assigned his right to build the machines, without any reservation of a right to any damages that may have accrued from infringements, or of a right to sue for them. It was, without doubt, competent for him to have reserved this right; but not having done so, and now as­serting no claim, there is no reason, per­ceptible to the court, why the complain­ant, as the assignee of Bicknell, being vest­ed with the entire interest in the patent, should not protect his rights by suit in his own name. Bloomer certainly has no inter­est in the patent, nor could he be compelled to join in any proceeding, having for its object the establishment of the rights of the complainant under the patent. Besides, there is no allegation or proof to the effect that any of the infringements complained of, in this suit, transpired during the pe­riod that Bloomer held his interest in the patent.</p>
                <p pgmap="525" id="b525-3">It is further insisted by counsel, that if there has been an assignment, which trans­fers to the complainant the right to sue for infringements of the patent, it is void, for the reason that, in its legal effect, it is an assignment of a right to unliquidated dam­ages. This view is clearly not sustainable. The profits recoverable in an action for a violation of an exclusive right, under a pat­ent, are not regarded in the light of un-­liquidated damages. The right to recover rests upon the principle that the party com­plained of has unlawfully appropriated to himself the benefits of an improvement or discovery which belongs exclusively to an­other; and that, so far as he has made profit by such appropriation, he is liable to the party injured. This profit is ascertaina­ble by evidence; and does not, like the claim for damages in an action for a tort, rest in the mere discretion • of a court or jury.</p>
                <p pgmap="525" id="b525-4">The remaining inquiry relates to the con­struction of the contract between Wilson and Bicknell and Jenkins. The counsel for the complainant insists that the clause granting the exclusive right “to make, use, and vend to others to construct and use” the Woodworth planing machine within the territorial limits designated, imports a right in the grantee to construct for sale or. use elsewhere, and wherever a market can be found; and that, consequently the construc­tion of the machine, within those limits, by the defendant, though sold for use outside such limits, is an infringement of the exclu­sive right of the complainant, and that he is entitled to a decree for the profits derived from such infringement,' as proved by the testimony in the case. On the other hand, it is contended that the limitation as to ter­ritory applies alike to the right of making, and to the right of vending and using; and that the complainant can not claim, under the contract, any exclusive right to make the machines for sale or use, except within the territory described. And it is argued that, as. a necessary result, if machines are made by one having no license or authority, within those limits, for sale or use else­where, it is merely a technical infringe­ment of the complainant’s right, and does not afford a basis for a decree for an ac­count of profits on the sales of the machines so made and sold.</p>
                <p pgmap="525(337) 526(549)" id="b525-7">As before noticed, the proof is clear that the defendant has made no machines which have been sold or used within the territory mentioned in the contract He asserts in his answer a right to sell them elsewhere, without the license or consent of the com­plainant and without being answerable for the profits. If this construction of the con­tract is sustained, it is clear the complain­ant is entitled only to nominal damages for the infringement. In that case he would have no right to invoke the aid of a court of chancery, as the law would afford a plain and adequate remedy. It is obvious, there­fore, that the construction of the contract referred to, presents a material question for the decision of the court. In the case of Bicknell v. Todd [Case No. 1,389], which was an application to Judge McLean for an injunction, the learned judge, after giving a synopsis of the contract, says: “Under this contract, Bicknell and Jenkins have a right to make for use, within the district speci­fied, the planing machines, under the re­strictions named; and they have also a right to all the receipts under the thirteen licenses granted, they paying to Wilson the sum stipulated.” The question arising in this case, whether Bicknell and Jenkins, un­der the contract, had the exclusive right, within the territory defined, to make ma­chines for sale and usé outside of it, did not arise in the case referred to, and was not decided by Judge McLean. It is, therefore, an open question in this court, and, perhaps, not wholly free from difficulty. I will state briefly the conclusions to which I have been brought on the point stated; and, in doing so, may properly express my regrets that I can not have the aid of my brother judge in its consideration and decision. This con­tract, in its terms, grants to Bicknell and Jenkins “the exclusive right to make, use, and vend to others to construct and use” the Woodworth planing machine, for the full term of the patent, within the limits specified. It does not, in express words, ex­tend the grant to the right of constructing machines, within those limits, for sale or use elsewhere. It is equally clear there is nothing in the contract which expressly neg­atives such a right. The intention of the parties must, therefore, be sought for; and if that can be ascertained by reference to the entire instrument, it will furnish a guide in giving it a construction, in reference to the point under consideration. And here it is material to notice, that the person having the title to a patent for a new or improved mechanical structure, has three distinct rights, which he may dispose of separately to different individuals. These are: the right to mate the machine, the right to use, and the right to vend. In the case of Bick-­nell v. Todd, before referred to, Judge Mc­Lean distinctly recognizes this doetiine, as applicable to the contract now in question. He remarks, that “these rights have been treated as distinct by the parties to this contract;” and adds: “This is clear from the words of the contract, and especially from that part of it which reserves the right of Hudson and Hughes to make a machine, which had been granted to them by Wil­son.” At the date of this contract, Wilson held the entire interest in the Woodworth patent, including the territory named, ex­cept so far as he had previously granted certain rights within it. By his contract with Bicknell and Jenkins, he transferred his in­terest to them, subject to the restrictions and limitations specified. In this transfer, it seems clear he intended to distinguish be­tween the right to make the machine gen­erally, and the right to make for use, with­in the limits designated. While there is no limitation as to the former, the latter right is cautiously guarded and restricted. Wil­son, prior to the date of the contract, had granted several licenses to use the machine in Hamilton county, and, in his contract with Bicknell and Jenkins, reserved the right of licensing other machines in the dis­trict mentioned, upon the condition that the number should not exceed thirteen. Bick-­nell and Jenkins bound themselves not to “erect for use. use, or directly or indirectly authorize to be used, within said territory, any machines, until the number is or shall be reduced to eight.” Under this restric­tion, it is obvious they could expect but little profit from the right granted them within the district described, except what they might realize, from the receipts to which they were entitled, from the machines li­censed by Wilson. • They could build and use no new machine within the district till the number licensed was reduced from thir­teen to eight. And as to making machines, their right was only that of replacing such of the number licensed as might become un­fit for use. This would seem to be an in­adequate consideration for the 52,500 which they were to pay, yearly, for the rights granted to them; and would justify the con­clusion that the right to make the machines was intended to have a wider meaning.</p>
                <p pgmap="526" id="b526-5">In the argument of the counsel for the complainant, it is contended that the right to make and the right to use the machine, in the contract under consideration, are dis­tinct and independent, and that the parties intended to separate them. It is insisted, therefore, that while Bicknell and Jenkins are restricted in their right to make, for use, within the territory named, there is no lim­itation to their right to make, for sale, with­out that territory. This is probably the true construction of the contract. But then the inquiry arises, does the grant of the naked right to construct, import a right to Bicknell and Jenkins to sell for use, outside of the territory named? The right to make carries with it the right to sell; but does it necessarily imply the right to use the ma­chine when made and sold? According to the argument of the complainant’s counsel, the mere right to make, with the right to sell, may be vested in one person, while the right to grant a license for the use of the machine may be in another. Has Wilson, in his contract, parted with the right to au­thorize the use of the machines, to be made by Bicknell and Jenkins, for sale outside of Hamilton county, and the adjacent terri­tory, in Kentucky? Upon the supposition that he had granted the right, Bicknell and Jenkins were authorized to make and li­cense for use anywhere within the United States. I can not perceive anything in the terms of this contract justifying the conclu­sion that a right so immensely valuable was transferred by Wilson. The consideration named in the contract would certainly be no' equivalent for such a right But, on the supposition that Wilson transferred, with­out limitation as to any territory outside of that named in the contract, the mere right to construct the machines for sale, reserv­ing the right to license such machines for use, the contract becomes intelligible, and the intention of the parties obvious. In this view, it excites no surprise that Wilson should have granted, without restriction or limitation, the right to manufacture the ma­chines for sale anywhere, beyond the lim­its of the district specified. His policy was to encourage the making of the machines, since his profits from licenses would be in­creased in proportion to the number made and sold. The city of Cincinnati, being one of the principal centers of business in the West, and of easy access from various points, would be a desirable place for the manufacture of the machines. From thence, they would readily find their way into the smaller towns and villages.</p>
                <p pgmap="526(22) 527(180)" id="b526-6">If this view of the contract is correct, it follows that the defendant has infringed the complainant’s exclusive right to make .the machine, by constructing machines within the district defined, and selling -them else­where, and must account for the profits ac­cruing to. him from such violation of the right of the complainant And the question is presented, upon what principle shall these profits be estimated? Counsel assume that the complainant occupies the position, and is entitled to all the rights of an assignee of the entire interest in the Woodworth pat­ent, and as such is entitled to an account for all profits, including the price charged as the profit of the assignee, on the sale of his rights under the patent. But I am unable to perceive the justice of a decree in this case on that basis. If the right granted to Bieknell and Jenkins, as to all territory out­side of that described in the contract, was the naked right to construct the machine, with a right to sell, but not to license for use, the rule of damages must be their actual profit from the manufacture of the machine, ex­cluding any profit as a patentee.</p>
                <p pgmap="527" id="b527-3">I am aware that, in his treatise on Pat­ents, Mr. Curtis asserts a principle that may seem to be in conflict with that on which it is proposed to place the decree in this case. He says: “When a patentee sells to another a patented machine made by himself, or permits such person to make the machine, the party thus authorized becomes a licen­see, with the right of selling the machine, which carries with it the right of using it” Section 195. Without controverting this doctrine, I doubt its applicability to the case before the court. This case must be dis­posed of with reference to the contract be­tween the parties. As before stated, this contract was made and so regarded by the parties, with reference to the rights of the patentee, or his assignee, of making, of vending, and of using a patented machine, as distinct and separable, and as capable of being vested in different persons; as before noticed, this principle was expressly sanc­tioned by Judge McLean, in the case refer­red to, and he held that the parties to this contract seemed so to have understood it. • The doctrine laid down by the writer just mentioned, does not therefore apply to this contract. If the right of Bieknell and Jenk­ins was a mere right to construct the ma­chine within certain limits, implying a right to sell outside of such limits, but without any right to. use, or authorize others to use, the machine, the injury sustained by the complainant, as the result of the defend­ant’s infringement of his exclusive right, is to be measured by the profit, which, as a manufacturer and not as a patentee, he real­ized from making it</p>
                <p pgmap="527" id="b527-4">The report of the master shows that the defendant, on his own account and in con­nection with his partner, Bonsall, construct­ed and sold nine machines; and that the amount usually paid to the patentee, for the right to make machines, is $225 each. It does not appear, from the report, whether this is inclusive or exclusive of the profit made by the manufacturer. This profit, as it seems to the court, furnishes the rule for fixing the amount of the decree. For the purpose of ascertaining this, there must be a further reference to the master, unless the parties can agree on the amount. Case referred back to the master for the purpose of stat­ing an account, in accordance with the prin­ciples stated.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="521" ORDERLABEL="519" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00261_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00261_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00261_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_521.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00261_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="522" ORDERLABEL="520" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00261_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00261_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00261_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_522.21" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00261_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="523" ORDERLABEL="521" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00262_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00262_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00262_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_523.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00262_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="524" ORDERLABEL="522" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00262_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00262_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00262_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_524.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00262_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="525" ORDERLABEL="523" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00263_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00263_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00263_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_525.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00263_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="526" ORDERLABEL="524" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00263_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00263_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00263_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_526.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00263_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="527" ORDERLABEL="525" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00264_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00264_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00264_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_527.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00264_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b521-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0268"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_521.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00261_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b521-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0268"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_521.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00261_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b523-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0268"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_523.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00262_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_524.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00262_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b522-19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0268"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_522.22" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00261_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_523.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00262_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b523-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0268"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_523.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00262_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b527-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0268"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_527.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00264_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_527.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00264_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b523-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0268"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_523.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00262_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_523.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00262_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b521-11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0268"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_521.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00261_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b521-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0268"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_521.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00261_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b521-15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0268"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_521.18" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00261_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b523-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0268"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_523.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00262_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b524-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0268"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_524.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00262_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_524.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00262_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b525-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0268"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_525.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00263_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_526.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00263_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_526.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00263_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b527-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0268"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_527.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00264_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b525-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0268"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_525.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00263_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_525.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00263_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b525-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0268"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_525.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00263_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b526-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0268"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_526.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00263_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_527.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00264_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Av0f" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0268"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_521.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00261_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b522-14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0268"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_522.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00261_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b522-15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0268"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_522.15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00261_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b522-16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0268"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_522.16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00261_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b526-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0268"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_526.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00263_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b524-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0268"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_524.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00262_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AGxG" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0268"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_522.17" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00261_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_522.18" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00261_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_522.19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00261_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b524-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0268"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_524.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00262_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_525.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00263_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
