<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044049817315_0290" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="D.N.J." jurisdiction="United States">United States District Court for the District of New Jersey</court>
          <name abbreviation="In re Jersey City Window Glass Co.">In re JERSEY CITY WINDOW GLASS CO.</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 7,292</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">13 F. Cas. 557</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">1 N. B. R. 426 (Quarto, 113); 7 Am. Law Reg. (N. S.) 419: 1 Am. Law T. Rep. Bankr. 61</citation>
          <decisiondate>1868-04-08</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-10T00:25:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:27:33Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:41:28Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00280_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="968f50aac0886e9508bc0dca7869f4ea" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="66928">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00280_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00280_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="b8a68b2c663221bbc229f42033adc5f9" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="98102">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00280_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00281_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="48db37fff238cfee284b8444a7b75218" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="86020">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00281_0.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00280_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="d9c9e01e8541aa60c8ff7cf691b28ec9" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3087341">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00280_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00280_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="9ecfcda0a33a30c462e00ba0541074de" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3452761">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00280_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00281_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="8685e8e19673b9a9dc08346a1c46b078" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3267594">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00281_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00280_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="1cccc65e6028b67b3ebd6e77f8eccdf3" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="150645">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00280_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00280_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="784231e1789195225b6f6fca7518c5db" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="215576">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00280_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00281_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="d81343addf9e3b123e17c144a6d4fb61" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="184587">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00281_0.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0290" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="559" firstpage="557">
              <court pgmap="559" id="b559-24">District Court, D. New Jersey.</court>
              <docketnumber pgmap="559" id="b559-21">Case No. 7,292.</docketnumber>
              <citation pgmap="559" id="b559-23">[1 N. B. R. 426 (Quarto, 113);<footnotemark>1</footnotemark> 7 Am. Law Reg. (N. S.) 419: 1 Am. Law T. Rep. Bankr. 61.]</citation>
              <parties pgmap="559" id="b559-22">In re JERSEY CITY WINDOW GLASS CO.</parties>
              <decisiondate pgmap="559" id="Asa">April 8, 1868.</decisiondate>
              <attorneys pgmap="560" id="b560-4">J. Dixon, for petitioner.</attorneys>
              <attorneys pgmap="560" id="b560-5">J. F. Randolph, for defendant.</attorneys>
              <footnote label="1">
                <p pgmap="559" id="b559-32">1 [Reprinted from 1 N. B. R. 426 (Quarto, 113), by permission.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author pgmap="560" id="b560-6">FIELD, District Judge.</author>
                <p pgmap="560(903) 561(112)" id="ALl">The only act of bankruptcy alleged in the petition is that the •Jersey City Window Glass Company sus­pended payment of their commercial paper, and did not resume within a period of four­teen days. There is no allegation that this suspension and non-resumption were fraudu­lent. This, it is contended, is an act of bankruptcy within the meaning of the thirty-­ninth section of the bankrupt act [of 1SC7 •(14 Stat. 530)]. I am aware that this con­struction has been sanctioned and adopted by the judges of several of the district courts. My attention has been more than once called to the opinion of Judge Hall of the Northern district of New York; but with all my respect for his learning and ability, I have never been able to bring my mind to the conclusion which he has reached. The language of the clause under consideration is: “Who being a banker, merchant, or trader, has fraudulently stopped or suspend­ed, and not resumed payment of his com­mercial paper, within a period of fourteen •days.” It is insisted that here are two dis­tinct acts of bankruptcy created and de­scribed; the first, a fraudulent stopping, which is in itself an act of bankruptcy, and upon which proceedings may at once be in­stituted; and the second, a mere suspension of payment, without any fraud, and which only becomes an act of bankruptcy by being continued for a period of fourteen days. It is possible, I admit, to read this clause in such a way as to make it seem to bear such a construction. But it can only be done by making a distinct pause after the -word ■“stopped,” and then reading in one breath the remaining part of the sentence. But is that the way in which any one would ever think of reading it? Is it the natural and ordinary way? Would not such a construc­tion, to say the least, be a strained one? Would it not be doing violence to the lan­guage, and wresting it from its obvious sense and meaning? And would it not make the whole sentence, not only very awkward, but a very ungrammatical one? In this re­spect. it would be in striking contrast with the rest of the act, in which, as it seems to me, much more attention has been paid to clearness of expression, the correct use of language, and the rules of grammar, than is usual in acts either of our national or state legislatures. But why depart from the plain and obvious meaning of the language em­ployed, and resort to a construction so forced and unnatural? For the purpose, it is said, of carrying out the general intentions of congress in the passage of the bankrupt law. Nowit is very well known that this law is in a great measure based upon the English statutes of bankruptcy. Almost every act of bankruptcy enumerated in the thirty-ninth section is to be found in the English stat­utes. where they are described in substan­tially the same terms. If, then, the fraudu­lent stopping of payment by a banker, mer­chant, or trader of his commercial paper, and the suspension without fraud for a pe­riod of fourteen days, were two distinct and well known acts of bankruptcy under the English law, we might naturally expect to find them in our own act, and might very well imagine that we had found them, in the clause referred to, although certainly nor very clearly expressed. But it so happens that there are no such acts of bankruptcy known in the .English law. It is true that by their bankrupt acts, the suspension of payment by a debtor is resolved into an act of bankruptcy, by summoning him before the court of bankruptcy, and if such debt is not paid or arranged to the satisfaction of the creditor within a prescribed time, such non-payment or non-arrangement constitutes an act of bankruptcy. But a fraudulent stopping alone, whether followed by a re­sumption or not, is an act of bankruptcy never before heard of. If, therefore, it was intended by the framers of our act to make this for the first time an act of bankruptcy, it might be presumed that they would have declared their intention in clear and unmis­takable language. Certain it is, that we ought not to wrest their language from its plain and obvious meaning in order to infer That they had any such intention. But what is meant by a fraudulent stopping? Does it mean that the debtor is unable to pay. that he is insolvent? If so. he ought to stop. 1-Ie has no right under these circumstances to pay one creditor to the exclusion of an­other. This of itself would be an act of bankruptcy. It must mean, therefore, if it means anything, an unwillingness to pay, al­though he has the means of doing so. But suppose he pays the day after his eomrner cial paper arrives at maturity. Would not that negative the idea of fraud? Must we not wait, therefore, to see whether payment is resumed within a reasonable time, before we pronounce the original suspension to be fraudulent? Undoubtedly the stopping pay­ment might be accompanied by circum­stances which would clearly indicate a fraudulent purpose; such, for instance, as the concealment or removal of property or the fraudulent sale or conveyance of it. But these would he in themselves independent acts of bankruptcy, upon which proceedings might be instituted. But how the mere act of suspension, if followed by resumption within a few days, could be deemed fraudu­lent, I do not very well see. I do not be­lieve, therefore, it was the intention of con­gress to make the stopping of payment, un­der any circumstances, an act of bankruptcy in itself, and without reference to resump­tion. If the debtor is perfectly solvent, and if he resumes payment within the fourteen days, so that no one is defrauded, why should he be adjudged a bankrupt?</p>
                <p pgmap="561" id="b561-3">What, then, is the true meaning and in­tent of the clause in question? I under­stand it to mean, according to the obvious sense of the language made use of, that when a banker, merchant, or trader fraudu­lently stops or suspends payment of his com­mercial paper, and does not resume within fourteen days, he commits an act of bank­ruptcy. To constitute the act, there must be a stopping or suspension of payment, and also a non-resumption within fourteen days, and such suspension and non-resumption must be fraudulent in the sense in which that term is here employed. If the debtor is able to pay, if he has the means of pay­ing, and does not do so, then undoubtedly he commits a fraud upon the creditor who holds his paper. And if he is unable to pay, if he is insolvent, then he commits a fraud upon his other creditors, by not having himself •declared a bankrupt, and making a surren­der of his property to be equally distributed among them. It will be seen that this act of bankruptcy is confined to bankers, mer­chants, and .traders, and that it extends only to the non-payment of commercial paper, that is, to negotiable securities, to bills of exchange and promissory notes. These are securities of a peculiar kind, well known to the law, and held in high respect There is an especial dishonor attached to their non­payment. There is a sort of commercial sanctity about them. They are intended to pass from hand to hand; they are valuable instruments of commerce; they perform many of the functions of money. If, there­fore, a banker, merchant, or trader suffers paper of this description to be dishonored, and does not resume payment within four­teen days, it argues such a state of insol­vency on his part, as to make it a fraud upon his creditors not to surrender his property for equal distribution among them. Such a* suspension and non-resumption may well be termed fraudulent. I do not mean to say that it would be conclusive evidence of fraud, but it would certainly be prima facie evidence, and it would cast upon the debtor the burden of proving that he was perfectly, .solvent, and that such suspension and non-­resumption would not have the effect of de­frauding either the holders of his dishonored paper, or any of his other creditors. Such a construction of the clause in question makes the whole consistent and intelligible, and would render it somewhat analogous, to that provision of the English bankrupt law, to which I have adverted.</p>
                <p pgmap="561" id="b561-6">It would be difficult to imagine any case better calculated than the one now before the court, to illustrate the justice and pro­priety of such a provision. It is alleged on the part of the debtor, and not denied by the counsel of the company, that they have is­sued a series of promissory notes, falling due at successive periods, and that they are ut­terly unable to pay them. It is admitted, also, that they had it in contemplation to apply by their petition to be declared bank­rupts, but that upon taking the advice of counsel they concluded not to do so. Now it would be a serious defect in our bankrupt act, if no provision were made by which the creditors of such a company could compel them to surrender all their estate and effects for the benefit of their creditors, without proving any other facts than their continued suspension and utter insolvency. If, there­fore, it had been alleged in this case that such suspension and non-resumption -within fourteen days were fraudulent, I should have had no hesitation in declaring it to be an act of bankruptcy. I see no objection, however, to allowing the petition to be amended by the insertion of that word.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="559" ORDERLABEL="557" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00280_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00280_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00280_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_559.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00280_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="560" ORDERLABEL="558" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00280_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00280_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00280_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_560.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00280_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="561" ORDERLABEL="559" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00281_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00281_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00281_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_561.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00281_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b559-32" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0290"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_559.39" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00280_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b560-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0290"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_560.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00280_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b560-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0290"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_560.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00280_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b560-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0290"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_560.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00280_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b559-24" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0290"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_559.30" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00280_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b559-23" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0290"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_559.29" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00280_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b559-22" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0290"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_559.28" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00280_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b559-21" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0290"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_559.27" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00280_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b561-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0290"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_561.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00281_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="ALl" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0290"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_560.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00280_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_560.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00280_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_560.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00280_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_561.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00281_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b561-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0290"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_561.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00281_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_561.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00281_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Asa" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0290"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_559.31" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00280_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
