<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044049817315_0233" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="C.C.N.D.N.Y." jurisdiction="United States">United States Circuit Court for the Northern District of New York</court>
          <name abbreviation="In re Jaycox">In re JAYCOX et al.</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 7,237</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">13 F. Cas. 390</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">12 Blatchf. 209; 13 N. B. R. 122</citation>
          <decisiondate>1874-06-16</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-10T00:25:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:27:33Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:41:27Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00196_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="26e614bac9630854dbd56d56bae75847" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="80350">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00196_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00197_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="e9d3f6206e33c256c290513154c0b79f" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="105032">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00197_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00197_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="c549bc87a58e4d851ce6d7897fd48c97" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="115028">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00197_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00198_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="aaf999bdafd41dcb33da19defd4d4ce4" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="86968">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00198_0.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00196_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="658d756dede96c7a3fad79e7c90bd877" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3016473">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00196_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00197_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="d896642608979fa853fef4eae459495a" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3774473">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00197_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00197_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="0b740ea942e55d84113983add1fe1aac" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3830237">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00197_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00198_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="ce9bc586f088e16a33d9bb66194be948" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3242463">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00198_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00196_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="05cb27c10963673a6f9d5592e9081f80" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="176451">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00196_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00197_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="56d9f143dcbbc0e310ce4bf8ff2ad634" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="231728">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00197_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00197_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="9847c80b904e69c076bc2b88a96b9e6b" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="243374">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00197_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00198_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="b16ca95a66eec8ccdd9a59e6207f666b" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="182843">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00198_0.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0233" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="393" firstpage="390">
              <court pgmap="392" id="Aaz">Circuit Court, N. D. New York.</court>
              <docketnumber pgmap="392" id="b392-10">Case No. 7,237.</docketnumber>
              <citation pgmap="392" id="AjZL">[12 Blatchf. 209; <footnotemark>1</footnotemark> 13 N. B. R. 122.]</citation>
              <parties pgmap="392" id="AicE">In re JAYCOX et al.</parties>
              <decisiondate pgmap="392" id="A0yZ">June 16, 1874.</decisiondate>
              <attorneys pgmap="393" id="b393-4">Daniel Pratt, for appellants.</attorneys>
              <attorneys pgmap="393" id="b393-5">Prank Hiscock, for assignee in bankruptcy.</attorneys>
              <attorneys pgmap="393" id="b393-6">William C. Buger, for creditors.</attorneys>
              <footnote label="1">
                <p pgmap="392" id="b392-19">1 [Reported by Hon. Samuel Blatchford, Dis­trict Judge, and here reprinted by permission.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author pgmap="393" id="b393-7">WOODEUPP, Circuit Judge.</author>
                <p pgmap="393" id="ALDO">1. It is im­possible to discover, from the papers sub­mitted herein, that the circuit court has any jurisdiction,' or of what proceeding. It was stated by counsel., on the argument, and is assumed in the briefs, that an appeal has been taken to this court by the assignees of the People’s Safe Deposit and Savings In­stitution of the State of New York, from an order of the district court disallowing their proof of debt against the estate of the bank­rupts [Case No. 7,241]; and there are among the papers a statement of claim, and an an­swer thereto, intended to conform to the 24th section of the bankrupt law, relating to such appeals. On the trial which that 24th section provides for, the parties waived a jury, and gave in evidence a part only of the proceedings in the district court relating to such claim. Probably, the defects in the pa­pers would be supplied, so far as the case is susceptible of supplement, and I will, there­fore, deal with the case according to the in­formation I have of its nature and condition.</p>
                <p pgmap="393" id="b393-8">2. But I cannot omit to observe, that this court has no original jurisdiction to receive and allow debts against the estate of a bank­rupt. The claims of creditors must first be presented In the district court; and It is not proper to present one claim in the district court, and, under cover of an appeal to this court, transform the claim into a new and distinct cause of action. In other words, this court ought not, on appeal, to be called upon to decide questions, either of law or fact, that were not raised or involved in the de­cision of the district court The same cause of action is to be pursued in this court though it may happen that new or further proofs in support of that cause of action may here establish facts not proved below, and new questions of law may arise thereupon. The cause of action, however, must be the same; otherwise, this court would assume to allow or reject a debt which had been neither allowed nor rejected in the district court. To do this, I am of opinion this court has no jurisdiction.</p>
                <p pgmap="393" id="b393-9">3. The only order which I find among the papers submitted, and the only order which, so far as I have any information, the dis­trict court has made rejecting the claim of the assignees, (the appellants,) is an order which rejects certain promissory notes set forth as proof of debts due from the bank­rupts to the People’s Safe Deposit and Sav­ings Institution. The ground of such rejec­tion, appearing in the opinion of the^court, is, that those notes are void and constitute no cause of action. But, the order expunging the proof of those notes, and rejecting that proof, is declared, in the order itself, to be without prejudice to any right of the cred­itors so claiming to make proof of a debt or claim for money loaned to said bank­rupts, or had and received by them to the use of the said corporation or its assignees, or proof of any other debt or claim, other than upon the notes or security taken or re­ceived on the making of discounts in viola­tion of the restraining acts, or other stat­utes, of the state of New York. Instead of acting upon the suggestion of the court thus given, and amending their claim and proof of debt, so that it should not depend upon the question of the validity of those notes, the alleged creditors have, it would seem from the papers, come into this court and here set out or stated, for the first time, a cause of action for money lent and advanced upon these notes, and for money lent and advanced generally to the bankrupts, and for money had and received by the bankrupts to the use of the claimants. They thus pre­sent here a cause or causes of action never presented to the district court, and seek to establish a debt which that court has not re­jected. I think, therefore, that this court would perform its whole duty by consider­ing the only question which<footnotemark>1</footnotemark> was decided in the district court, namely, whether the prom­issory notes, which were alone stated as con­stituting the cause of action or debt presented below, were or were not void.</p>
                <p pgmap="393" id="b393-12">4. I have, however, no wish to avoid the examination of the whole case, or the ex­pression of my opinion thereon, by suggest­ing embarrassments which counsel or parties may deem technical. Very able counsel have discussed the case in this court, assuming that both of the questions which arise out of the transactions between the bankrupts and the safe deposit and savings institution were properly before me. The fact that proofs of debt in the district court are not formal, and that promissory notes are themselves treated as evidence of money had and received by the promissor, gives some color to the claim that the district court might have received them as such proof, and ought not only to have passed upon their validity, but upon the evidence taken by the register that the said corporation did advance money to the bankrupts thereon, by discounting the notes. I, therefore, state my conclusions upon both questions, and, if counsel can make my de­cision useful in the case, as it has been con­ducted and is now urged, it will save time and expense*.</p>
                <p pgmap="393(28) 394(303)" id="b393-13">5. I find, then, the facts to be as stated in the report of the register, and as recited in the opinion of the district judge. The principal and important of them are, that the People’s Safe Deposit and Sayings Institution was in­corporated by act of the legislature of the state of New York, passed May 14th, 1808, and its charter (2 Laws N. Y. 1868, p. 1839, c. 816), must, for any purposes for which my finding is material, be taken as part and parcel thereof; that such corporation opened offices for banking in Utica and Syracuse, and at such offices conducted a regular bank­ing business, employing its capital and de­posits therein; that it kept a large number of accounts, not only for deposit of savings, but -merchants’ accounts, for discounts and deposits, after the usual custom of batiks of discount and deposit in this state; that, in such banking business, it, prior to its failure and assignment to the appellants, had dis­counted, in the ordinary course of business, promissory notes and other commercial pa­per, at the banking office in Syracuse, to the amount of more than six hundred thousand dollars; that it so discounted, from time to time, several hundred thousand dollars in all, for the firm of Jaycox &amp; Green, (the bank­rupts;) that, of. such commercial paper, so 'discounted for Jaycox &amp; Green, promissory notes to the amount of over thirty-five thou­sand dollars remain unpaid, and are held by the said corporation or the appellants, the re­ceivers of such corporation, of which notes, the promissory notes made by Jaycox &amp; Green, now in question, to the amount of $27,772.50, were presented and claimed as a debt against the bankrupts, in the district court; and that the proceeds of the discounts thereof were paid to Jaycox &amp; Green by checks or drafts on New York, less a charge of one-half of one per cent, charged as ex­change oñ New York.</p>
                <p pgmap="394" id="b394-4">Upon these facts, 1st, I concur fully in the opinion of the late lamented and learned dis­trict judge, that the said notes were wholly void, and, neither as contracts or securities, constituted any ground of claim or debt against the bankrupts. I do not deem it necessary to repeat the discussion embodied in that opinion. It may be taken as the opinion of this court upon the question. The charter of the corporation in no wise author­ized the carrying on of that business. The constitution and the statutes of the state of New York forbade it. Heavy penalties were declared by statute against the corporation and Its officers, for carrying it on. The acts by which the notes were received by the cor­poration were illegal; and the statutes, in ex­press terms, declare such notes void. The decision of the district court was, upon this point, as I think, beyond all question, cor­rect</p>
                <p pgmap="394" id="b394-5">2d. The said corporation, thus violating the laws of the state, can no more allege an im­plied contract to pay the money mentioned in the notes, than it could set up and rely upon the express promise of Jaycox &amp; Green to do so. To say. that, when a statute de­clares that all notes and other securities for the payment of any money, made or given •to secure the payment of any money loaned or discounted by any incorporated company, or its officers, contrary to the provisions of the statute, shall be void, the courts may, nevertheless, imply a contract to pay it, is practically to repeal the statute. Such a holding throws open the business of unau­thorized banking to be fearlessly conducted and without danger of loss. Such a'holding makes the stringent provisions of the con­stitution and statutes have this effect and no more — the mode of pleading in an action to recover the money is altered. Unauthorized corporations may discount notes without lim­it; but, if a note should be protested, they must sue for its amount as for so much mon­ey lent, or had and received, and will recov­er. Nearly all of the efficiency of the stat­utes, as a restraint, is eliminated by such a holding.</p>
                <p pgmap="394" id="b394-7">•I shall not enter upon an examination of all the cases which have been referred to as bearing upon this subject It is proper, however, to notice what are commonly spo­ken of as the Utica Ins. Co. Cases, 15 Johns. 358, 19 Johns. 1, 8 Cow. 20, 3 Wend. 296, Id. 369, and 4 Wend. 652. It was undoubtedly held, in reference to notes taken by that company, that although the notes were void, the money advanced on discounting the same could be recovered, as money lent; and the court go so far even as to say that the void notes could be used as evidence of money lent and so be made, as evidence, the ef­fective means of a recovery of the amount thereof. As to these cases I have two ob­servations to make:</p>
                <p pgmap="394" id="b394-8">First. They have long been the subject of criticism, and doubts of their correctness, have been freely expressed, both at the bar and on the bench. In New Hope &amp; Dela­ware Bridge Co. v. Poughkeepsie Silk Co., 25 Wend. 650, Mr. Justice Nelson, lately the venerable and distinguished justice of the supreme court of the United States assigned to this circuit, then in the supreme court of this state, says: “Whether the doctrine of these cases is well founded, and may be up­held upon established principles, or not, or whether the result was not materially in­fluenced by the peculiar phraseology and powers of the charter of the Utica Insurance Company, in respect to which they arose, it is not necessary at present to examine. I am free to say, in either aspect I should have great difficulty in assenting to them.” In Tracy v. Talmage, in the court of appeals of this state (14 N. Y. 162, 189), Mr. Justice Samuel L. Selden says: “These cases have never been overruled; and yet, I think I may say, they have generally been regarded with some suspicion as to their soundness. * * * There is undoubtedly great difficulty in reconciling these cases with the settled rules in regard to illegal contracts.”</p>
                <p pgmap="394(14) 395(130)" id="b394-9">Second. Those cases are distinguished from the. present; and in a particular which has -been referred to as constituting the possible ground upon which the decisions there made ■could be upheld, or, as I should better say, in the feature which was deemed to furnish the ground on which those cases proceeded, namely, that that company had a general power to lend money, and, therefore, though it received therefor a void security, it could Teclaim the loan. Without assenting to the reasoning by which this result was reached, it is sufficient to say, that the premises are wanting in the present case. In Beach v. Fulton Bank, 3 Wend. 573, 583, contempo­raneously with some of those decisions, Chief Justice Savage states their ground as above indicated, and declares, that, as the Hudson Insurance Company had no such power, those cases do not apply.</p>
                <p pgmap="395" id="b395-4">The charter of the People’s Safe Deposit and Savings Institution declares in what that corporation may invest its funds. This is fully discussed and made clear in the opin­ion of the district judge. It has no power to loan money on personal security; and the very ground on which the court placed their decision in the Utica Insurance Company Cases, therefore, fails. In accordance with this view, the supreme court of this state, in Life &amp; Fire Ins. Co. v. Mechanic Fire Ins. Co., 7 Wend. 31, where the action was assumpsit, and the plaintiff claimed to re­cover for money lent, held, that, as the plain­tiff had no power, by its charter, to loan money except on bond and mortgage, any other contract of loan was void, and could not be the foundation of an action; and, in the case of Gillet v. Phillips, in the court of appeals (13 N. Y. 114, 119), the court say, of a contract in violation of our • banking acts:. “The contract was not only unauthor­ized, but illegel. No action cduld be sus­tained upon, it, if executory, in his favor, nor to set it aside, if executed. Nor could it become the foundation of an implied as-­sumpsit in behalf of the offending party.” The cases of Brady v. Mayor, etc., of New York City, 2 Bosw. 173, 20 N. Y. 312, and Donovan v. Mayor, etc., of New York City, 33 N. Y. 291, by analogy, affirm the same doctrine. My conclusion is. that the appel­lants have established no debt against the bankrupts, and a judgment for the assignee must be entered.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="392" ORDERLABEL="390" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00196_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00196_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00196_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_392.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00196_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="393" ORDERLABEL="391" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00197_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00197_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00197_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_393.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00197_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="394" ORDERLABEL="392" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00197_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00197_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00197_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_394.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00197_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="395" ORDERLABEL="393" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00198_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00198_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00198_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_395.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00198_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AicE" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0233"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_392.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00196_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b394-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0233"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_394.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00197_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_394.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00197_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="ALDO" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0233"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_393.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00197_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_393.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00197_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b393-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0233"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_393.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00197_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b393-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0233"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_393.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00197_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b393-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0233"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_393.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00197_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b393-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0233"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_393.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00197_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b393-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0233"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_393.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00197_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Aaz" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0233"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_392.15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00196_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="A0yZ" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0233"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_392.16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00196_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b394-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0233"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_394.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00197_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b393-12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0233"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_393.15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00197_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b393-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0233"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_393.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00197_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_393.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00197_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b393-13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0233"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_393.16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00197_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_394.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00197_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b394-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0233"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_394.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00197_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_395.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00198_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b394-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0233"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_394.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00197_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b392-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0233"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_392.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00196_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b394-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0233"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_394.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00197_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b395-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0233"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_395.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00198_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b392-19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0233"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_392.23" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00196_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AjZL" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0233"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_392.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00196_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
