<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044046873683_0250" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="C.C.E.D. Pa." jurisdiction="United States">United States Circuit Court for the Eastern District of Pennsylvania</court>
          <name abbreviation="The Ellen Holgate v. The Illinois">The ELLEN HOLGATE v. The ILLINOIS</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 4,376</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">8 F. Cas. 513</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">35 Leg. Int. 194; 13 Phila. 470; 6 Reporter, 40; 6 Wkly. Notes Cas. 353; 24 Int. Rev. Rec. 159; 25 Pittsb. Leg. J. 157</citation>
          <decisiondate>1878-04-10</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-12T19:40:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-26T10:42:09Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-26T10:56:34Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00258_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="ea50aec3010e35500595004652b1bb70" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="54032">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00258_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00258_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="2f5e28dd7e31e8bda2d53ffda98fc240" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="116986">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00258_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00259_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="9975a4c7e6525eb039264ed79314a975" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="85760">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00259_0.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00258_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="83074045bf1bbed3fd97edd249a6652c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2431147">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00258_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00258_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="f6e59a065397d692940ed71b7d0c84fb" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3876986">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00258_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00259_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="f42075594a085c72192c16b712996f9e" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3140651">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00259_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00258_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="2733bf4b652b4382792eea6cf2f77903" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="108266">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00258_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00258_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="e554c230b2c6c31bc3a3cb2da01ebb86" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="249707">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00258_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00259_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="be43de0b4530305bdfc265032027a2ac" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="178932">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00259_0.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0250" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="515" firstpage="513">
              <court id="b515-8" pgmap="515">Circuit Court, E. D. Pennsylvania.</court>
              <docketnumber id="b515-6" pgmap="515">Case No. 4,376.</docketnumber>
              <citation id="AluE" pgmap="515">[35 Leg. Int. 194;<footnotemark>1</footnotemark> 13 Phila. 470; 6 Reporter, 40; 6 Wkly. Notes Cas. 353; 24 Int. Rev. Rec. 159; 25 Pittsb. Leg. J. 157.]</citation>
              <parties id="b515-7" pgmap="515">The ELLEN HOLGATE v. The ILLINOIS.</parties>
              <decisiondate id="AiU" pgmap="515">April 10, 1878.<footnotemark>2</footnotemark>
              </decisiondate>
              <attorneys id="b515-22" pgmap="515">Morton P. Henry and Henry R. Edmunds, for respondents and appellants.</attorneys>
              <attorneys id="b515-23" pgmap="515">J. Warren Coulston, for libellant and ap-­pellee.</attorneys>
              <footnote label="1">
                <p id="b515-11" pgmap="515">1 [Reprinted from 35 Leg. Int. 194, by per­mission.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <footnote label="2">
                <p id="b515-12" pgmap="515">2 [Affirmed in 103 U. S. 298.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author id="b515-24" pgmap="515">McKENNAN, Circuit Judge.</author>
                <p id="AgP" pgmap="515(21) 516(145)">It is the duty of a vessel overtaking anolher to keep clear of the vessel ahead; and this duty is especial­ly imperative upon a steamer, which has the control of her own motive power, and can therefore more promptly and accurately gov­ern her own movements; Hence she must carefully observe the course and conditions of the vessel in advance of her, and, in view of these adapt her own rate of speed and line of movement to the avoidance of danger of collision with such vessel; and if a col­lision occurs she is regarded as prima facie in fault, unless it appears to have been in­evitable. But the preceding vessel is not without correlative obligations. She is bound to maintain a proper lookout, to keep her course, and not to change it, at a time and under circumstances which would in­volve danger of collision with a vessel ap­proaching from either direction, except under the pressure of an imminent greater peril.</p>
                <p id="b516-3" pgmap="516">Now, it is apparent that if both vessels had kept their course, the collision com­plained of could not have occurred. The steamer.would then have given the schooner so wide a berth in passing her as to involve no risk of collision. The steamer did not violate her duty to keep out of the schooner’s way, in adopting and pursuing a line of movement which was, in the first instance, attended with no danger to either of them, but was only rendered unsafe by a change of the schooner’s course. She had a right to assume that the schooner would keep her course, or, at least, would not attempt to change it when the vessels were in such close proximity to each other as to create a peril which could not otherwise exist. As was said by Mr. Justice Strong, in The Scotia, 14 Wall. [81 U. S.] 181: “Nor is a steamer called to act, except when she is approaching a vessel in such direction ­as to take no precaution when there is no apparent dan­ger." While, therefore, the steamer selected a line of movement, which seemed to be, and really was, safe for both vessels, she might rightfully follow it, and was not called, upon to act further in the way of precaution, "apprehe­nd." And when this danger became immiment-not by any act of hers-­such precautions were promptly taken by her as seem to have been adapted to hte emergency. In the moment of peril she did all that could be done to avert it, or to miti­gate its consequences. Under such cicumtances nor fault is imputable to her, unless the schooner had an absolute right to vhange her course, as she did, amd the steamer was bound to anticipate it.</p>
                <p id="b516-4" pgmap="516">However rigidly a steamer is, and ought to be, held to the duty of keeping out of the way of a sailing vessel which she is approach­ing, it is only justly enforcible by regarding the conduct of both vessels, in its contribu­tory connection, with the emergency in which the steamer is suddenly called upon to act. The ultimate test of the steamer’s liability is, whether, under subsisting con­ditions, she did any thing which she ought not to have done, or omitted any precaution which she ought to have taken. Accordingly it was determined in The Scotia, supra, that where a steamer and a sailing vessel were approaching each other, and the steamer took a course which would carry her at a safe distance, in passing, from that apparently pursued by the other, and the latter changed her direction and a collision resulted, the steamer was not responsible, when she had not “failed to adopt such precautions as were in her power, and were necessary to avoid a collision,” as soon as that peril arose. Why should a different rule of accountability be applied, when the only difference in the cir­cumstances consists in this, that both vessels were proceeding in the same direction, and the steamer sought to go ahead of the sailing vessel? A steamer may rightfully avail her­self of the superior speed which she derives from her special motive power; and, if she keeps a proper lookout, and, in view of the apparent course of the vessel ahead of her, takes a direction unattended with risk of collision, does she not, in this regard, ob­serve all the precaution which the law exacts from her? But it was argued, that the tack­ing of the schooner was rendered necessary by the ice, and that this necessity ought to have been perceived by the steamer and her movements have been determined accord­ingly.</p>
                <p id="b516-7" pgmap="516">It is fully proved, that there was a suffi­cient lookout on the steamer, that the master and pilot were on the bridge looking ahead, that the movements of the schooner were carefully noted, and that no immediate ne­cessity for a change of the schooner’s course was discerned by those in charge of the steamer. It is difficult to determine how near the schooner was to the field of ice when she tacked. None of the witnesses, who were on board of her, state the distance. That a change in her course was necessary to avoid it is undoubted, but whether she was in such close proximity to it as to make such change imperative at the time when it was made, does not satisfactorily appear from the libellant’s proofs. It did not seem so to those on board the steamer, for, as her master testified “the water was clear for a mile ahead, and a quarter to a half mile to leeward;” and the testimony of the other witnesses for the respondent is not incon­sistent with this aspect of the situation. With a sufficient lookout, then, on the steam­er, if no immediate necessity for the schoon­er’s going about was observed by those en­gaged in this duty, as is fairly inferrible from the proofs, negligence is not predicable of the steamer’s failure to anticipate the schoon­er’s variation. We must therefore seek else­where for the fault which the collision in­volved. I think it resulted from the unques­tionable negligence of the schooner.</p>
                <p id="b516-8" pgmap="516(33) 517(266)">It is evident that the steamer was not seen by the schooner until the latter had changed her course. The testimony of her captain is decisive on this point He says: “I first discovered the steamer after our vessel filled off and started ahead,” and the steamer was then at a distance of, “I should think be­tween two and three hundred yards some­where.” This ignorance of the proximity of the steamer was doubtless the result of a failure of observation. Although, while the schooner kept her course, this omission was excusable, because it would have been harm­less, yet it is undeniable that, when she was about to change her course, she was bound to look out astern, so as to avoid peril to herself or others, if the surrounding circum­stances might induce an apprehension of it Can it be doubted that she would not have executed such a movement, if she had ob­served the steamer when she resolved upon it? It would have been apparent to her, as it was to all others who were in the vicinity at the time, that to tack then was either recklessly to invite a collision, or to increase the immediate danger of it By executing it a few minutes before she did, she could have crossed the course of the steamer with entire safety, or by holding her luff for a minute or two longer the steamer could have passed her without risk of injury to either. Pretermitting, however, the precaution she was bound to observe, she put herself in the way of the steamer, at a time when the latter could not avoid her, and thus rendered the collision inevitable. She, therefore, is alone responsible, and so all the libels must be dis­missed with costs.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="515" ORDERLABEL="513" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00258_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00258_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00258_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_515.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00258_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="516" ORDERLABEL="514" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00258_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00258_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00258_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_516.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00258_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="517" ORDERLABEL="515" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00259_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00259_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00259_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_517.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00259_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AluE" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0250"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_515.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00258_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b515-11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0250"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_515.18" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00258_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b515-22" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0250"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_515.27" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00258_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b515-23" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0250"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_515.28" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00258_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AgP" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0250"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_515.30" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00258_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_515.31" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00258_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_516.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00258_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b515-12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0250"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_515.19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00258_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b515-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0250"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_515.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00258_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b515-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0250"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_515.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00258_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b515-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0250"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_515.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00258_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b516-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0250"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_516.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00258_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_516.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00258_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b516-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0250"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_516.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00258_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b516-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0250"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_516.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00258_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AiU" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0250"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_515.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00258_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_515.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00258_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b516-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0250"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_516.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00258_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_517.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00259_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b515-24" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0250"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_515.29" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00258_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
