<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044049817315_0234" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="C.C.N.D.N.Y." jurisdiction="United States">United States Circuit Court for the Northern District of New York</court>
          <name abbreviation="In re Jaycox">In re JAYCOX et al.</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 7,238</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">13 F. Cas. 393</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">13 Blatchf. 70</citation>
          <decisiondate>1875-07-01</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-10T00:25:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:27:33Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:41:27Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00198_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="aaf999bdafd41dcb33da19defd4d4ce4" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="86968">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00198_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00198_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="c6e9b05e6e97803782be77e8a5a6d0a6" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="115654">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00198_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00199_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="d115296d2770308083c20b508372e839" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="116674">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00199_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00199_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="b5ec873a64f1fae3c644143b0e278911" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="112130">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00199_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00200_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="b735681301f9e2c5cf4121b5229a32f8" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="111474">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00200_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00200_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="509962a5c764281162ec4fe9d31a2203" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="91200">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00200_1.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00198_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="ce9bc586f088e16a33d9bb66194be948" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3242463">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00198_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00198_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="18ba0d4aeb0f6767f44f805e0919ef28" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3844625">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00198_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00199_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="9a95a13e4afa0f95419b00e649bbcd0a" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="4399331">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00199_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00199_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="c1e8a9e9c46833d62e9ee6ad6961725d" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3786921">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00199_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00200_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="c3c1857564b852b7530030a06400a4bb" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3766897">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00200_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00200_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="0d687cedef6703f8b4ee781ccea8f258" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3317743">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00200_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00198_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="b16ca95a66eec8ccdd9a59e6207f666b" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="182843">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00198_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00198_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="ec9c10e7c9bce75f7f4d3926f2e23acb" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="235480">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00198_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00199_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="7dfc3e52bc559495e38ddc82fd2e6c20" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="245474">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00199_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00199_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="08bbf4d6070c3eac09e9185fc7a76b9b" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="242872">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00199_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00200_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="552a4a7bd8cef87bae41769fa72fd46b" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="246701">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00200_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00200_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="552daac4d8a62b90340fc371395aa223" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="198660">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00200_1.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0234" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="398" firstpage="393">
              <court pgmap="395" id="AT2J">Circuit Court, N. D. New York.</court>
              <docketnumber pgmap="395" id="b395-6">Case No. 7,238.</docketnumber>
              <citation pgmap="395" id="AMl2">[13 Blatchf. 70.] <footnotemark>1</footnotemark>
              </citation>
              <parties pgmap="395" id="AcLA">In re JAYCOX et al.</parties>
              <decisiondate pgmap="395" id="A6o">July 1, 1875.</decisiondate>
              <attorneys pgmap="395" id="AyG">George Doheny, for assignees in bank­ruptcy.</attorneys>
              <attorneys pgmap="395" id="AuBv">William M. Brown, for creditor.</attorneys>
              <footnote label="1">
                <p pgmap="395" id="b395-12">1 [Reported by Hon. Samuel Blatehford, Dis­trict Judge, and here reprinted by permission.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author pgmap="395" id="b395-20">HUNT, Circuit Justice.</author>
                <p pgmap="395(313) 396(433)" id="AglS">Upon an applica­tion to expunge the proof of debt made by the assignees of the People’s Safe Deposit and Savings Institution of the State of New York, the register reports that lie has taken the evidence offered, and that the facts following are established by said evi­dence: (1.) That no claim is made by the assignees of said People’s Safe Deposit and Savings Institution of the State of New York against the estate of Jaycox &amp; Green, except the notes set out in schedule “A” annexed to the proof of debt, filed April 23d, 1873, amounting, of principal, to $35,-­272.20. (2.) That the People’s Safe Deposit and Savings Institution of the State of New York was a corporation organized under and by virtue of the provisions of chapter 816 of the Session Laws of the State of New York for 1868, the capital stock of which corporation was $300,000, owned by divers individuals. (3.) That said corpora­tion had a banking office in Utica and one in Syracuse. (4.) That, from April, 1871, until the bankruptcy of Jaycox &amp; Green, in May, 1872, the corporation, in its office at Syracuse, discounted the paper of Jaycox &amp; Green, to the amount of several hundred thousand dollars, and that, at the time of their bankruptcy, said corporation held their discounted paper, which paper is par­ticularly described in the schedule annexed to the amended or supplemental proof of debt, filed September 15th, 1874. (5.) That, from April, 1871, until the bankruptcy of said corporation, it carried on a regular banking business, except that it did not is­sue circulation of its own, discounting, dur­ing that period, a large amount of paper, selling exchange, and doing, in fact, the ordinary business of a bank of discount and deposit, and doing a large business of that character for a city like Syracuse, so that, at the bankruptcy of said corporation, it had between $600,000 and $700,000 of dis­counted commercial paper standing out; and that, during the period referred to, the corporation kept a regular office for dis­counts and deposits in Syracuse, kept a large number of mercantile accounts, and made large discounts for merchants. (6.) That Jaycox &amp; Green were wholesale gro­cers at the time the notes set out in the proofs of debt were-discounted; that these notes were discounted at about their re­spective dates, and their proceeds were ap­plied to the payment of other commercial paper of Jaycox &amp; Green, which had been discounted for them; and that the line of accommodation paper discounted by said corporation for Jaycox &amp; Green, for a year previous to their failure, amounted to $35,-­000 and upwards. (7.) That there were fif­teen trustees and directors of said corpora­tion, and of these some resided in Syracuse or its vicinity, but they were not at the banking room very frequently. (8.) That the stock ledger of the corporation shows that, at the time of its bankruptcy, the trustees and directors held $193,000 of its capital stock. (9.) That the corporation, be­sides discounting notes, made loans on bonds and mortgages and stocks, and re­ceived deposits, and issued pass-books there­for in the same form as those of savings banks; and that, at the time of its suspen­sion, the entire deposits in the corporation at Utica and Syracuse, was between $1,300,000 and $1,400,000. (10.) That the capital stock paid in at the time of the suspension of said corporation, was $75,000, and the residue of the money used by the corporation in dis­counting paper consisted of deposits and accumulations, and such accumulations amounted to $40,000. (11.) That the office of the corporation at Syracuse commenced discounting commercial paper and keeping commercial accounts soon after April 1st, 1S71, and this was done by a resolution of the board of directors. (12.) That, at the time of the suspension of the corporation, pretty much all of the deposits in it at Utica were of the character of savings bank deposits, and upwards of $1,000,000 of the deposits were of that character. The .reg­ister reported that said proof of debt should be expunged. The matter came on to be heard before Judge Wallace, the district judge, and he having been of counsel in the matter, declined to hear it, and ordered that fact to be entered of record. It was, therefore, ordered that the proceedings be certified to, and transferred into this court.</p>
                <p pgmap="396" id="b396-5">The findings of the register are sustained by the proof, and present a clear and suc­cinct statement of the facts of the case. Whether, upon these facts, a- claim exists in favor of the Deposit Savings Bank, against the estate of Jaycox &amp; Green, is the question to be decided.</p>
                <p pgmap="396" id="b396-6">For the purpose of brevity and conven­ience, the Institution described in the peti­tion in this case as “The People's Safe De­posit and Savings Institution of the State of New York,” will be termed the “Safe De­posit Company.” This company was or­ganized under and by virtue of the provi­sions of the act of the legislature of New York, passed May 14th, 1868 (chapter 816, p. 1839, Laws 1868). By the first section of that act the persons named were created a corporation, by the name and style above-­given, to be located outside of the cities of New York and Brooklyn, and, by the sec­ond section, the persons named were to con­stitute its board of directors for the first year. The provisions of the chapter are pe­culiar in many respects, but, for the purpose before us, it will only be necessary to notice the following: Section five provides that “the business and general object of the said corporation shall be to take and receive on deposit, as bailee, for safe keeping and storage, coin, bullion, gold and silver plate, jewelry, United States bonds, &amp;c., and to-­receive money from any estate * * * or persons on deposit and give a book, receipt, or certificate therefor, * * * and any rate of interest not exceeding that by law allowed for deposits.” By the eleventh section, the board was required to “invest its capital in good se­curities, * * * in bonds and mortgages, pub­lic securities or stocks of any state or of the United States, or in the stocks or bonds of any city, county or town, corporation or as­sociation, or otherwise, of any state, or the United States, in maimer and form as the directors and officers might think proper.”' By section fourteen, it was declared to pos­sess the powers, and be subject to the re­strictions, contained in title third of chap­ter eighteen* of the first part of the Revised Statutes, so far as applicable. That title enumerated the general powers of corpora­tions, of suing and being sued, succession and the ordinary powers of incorporations. It contained also the following: Section 3: “In addition to the powers enumerated * * * no corporation shall possess or ex­ercise any corporate powers except such as shall be necessary to the exercise of the powers so enumerated and given.” Section 4: “No corporation, * * * not expressly incorporated for banking purposes, shall, by any implication or construction, be deemed to possess the power of discounting bills * * * receiving deposits * * * buying and selling bills of exchange,” &amp;c. 1 Rev. St. p. 600.</p>
                <p pgmap="396(70) 397(398)" id="b396-11">The constitution of the state of New York, of 1S46, contained the following pro­vision: “Corporations may be formed un­der general laws, but shall not be created by special act, except for municipal purposes, and in cases when, in the judgment of the legislature, the objects of the corporation cannot be attained under general laws.” Article 8, § 1. Under this authority, the legislature had passed a general banking law, providing that any persons might ‘.‘es­tablish offices of discount, deposit and cir­culation, upon the terms and conditions, and subject to the liabilities, prescribed in the act.” Act April 18, 1838 (Laws 1838, c. 260). There was not at that time, nor until the year 1875, any general system for the incorporation of savings banks. In each case it was necessary to apply to the legisla­ture for an act of incorporation. What is familiarly called the restraining act of the state of New York, contains the following provisions: “No person unauthorized by law shall subscribe to, or become a member of, or be in any way interested in, any asso­ciation, institution or company, formed or to be formed for the purpose of receiving-­deposits, making discounts or. issuing notes or other evidences of debt to be loaned or put in circulation as money; nor shall any per­son unauthorized by law subscribe to, of be­come in any way interested in, any bank or fund created or to be created for the like purposes or either of them.” 1 Rev. St. p. 712, § 1. “No incorporated company, without being authorized by law, shall employ any part of its effects * * - * for the purpose of receiving deposits, making discounts, or issuing notes or other evidences of debt, to be loaned or put into circulation as money.” Id. § 3. “All notes and other securities for the payment of any money, or the delivery of any property, made or given to any such as­sociation, institution or company, that shall be formed for the purpose expressed in the first section of this title, or made or given to secure the payment of any money loaned or discounted by any incorporated company, or its officers, contrary to the provisions of the third section of this title, shall be void.” Id. § 5. By an act passed February 4th, 1837 (Laws 1837, p. 14, § 1), the provisions of the above act, so far as they prohibited persons not incorporated from keeping of­fices for the purpose of receiving deposits, or discounting notes or bills, were repealed. As to incorporated companies, the act yet remains in force, as above set forth. With these references to the constitution and laws, we are prepared to decide without difficulty some of the preliminary questions of the case.</p>
                <p pgmap="397" id="b397-5">1.The safe deposit company was not a bank of discount and deposit, authorized to do the ordinary banking business of receiv­ing current deposits, paying dealers’ checks and discounting commercial paper. It was a savings bank, authorized to do the ordi­nary business of a savings bank, and au­thorized to receive on deposit, as bailee, and for safe keeping, the articles of value and se­curities mentioned in its charter. The legis­lature did not intend and had no power un­der the constitution, to organize by special charter a bank of discount and deposit. If those obtaining the charter had such an in­tention, it was a dishonest and a furtive one. There is no language in the charter that con­fers powers other than those conferred on ordinary savings banks, except in relation to its capacity to receive, as bailee, the valua­ble articles referred to.</p>
                <p pgmap="397" id="b397-7">2. The directors and managers of the bank intentionally and habitually violated the law in carrying on an ordinary banking business, including that of making discounts of notes. The proof shows, that, at the time of bank: ruptcy, it had more than $600,000 of dis­counted commercial paper outstanding, and that this business was done by the express direction of its board of directors, and by the sanction of the stockholders.</p>
                <p pgmap="397" id="b397-8">3. The notes in controversy, amounting to $33,272.20, • were thus discounted by the safe deposit company, in known violation of the laws of the state. Jay cox &amp; Green, the bor­rowers, are in bankruptcy, and the safe de­posit company is in bankruptcy. The estate of the borrowers, ordinarily, should stand in­debted for money actually received as a loan by its principals. This is the ordinary rule of law, and the enquiry is, whether other and counteracting principles must in this case prevail against it.</p>
                <p pgmap="397" id="b397-9">The objection to the right of recovery by the safe deposit company while in existence, and by its assignees after its bankruptcy, is based upon the provisions of the Revised Statutes and of the restraining act. By the third section of this latter act, already quoted, every incorporated company not au­thorized by law is forbidden to make dis­counts of commercial paper. By the fifth section, it is enacted, that every note or oth­er security made in contravention of the pre­ceding section “shall be void.” It is plain, from-what has been said, (1st,) that the .safe deposit company is an incorporated com­pany; (2d,) that it had not the authority of law to discount this paper, (People v. Utica Ins. Co., 15 Johns. 358); and (3d,) that, with­out such authority, it did discount it. The restraining statute first forbids the transac­tion, and, secondly, declares that the notes given for such a transaction shall be void. The contract itself is forbidden, and. there­fore, illegal, and the security is also declared to be void. It is forbidden, both by section 4 of title 3 of chapter 18, above cited, the company not being “expressly incorporated for banking purposes,” within the meaning of that act, and by section three of the re­straining act, also herein before referred to.</p>
                <p pgmap="397(121) 398(44)" id="b397-10">The illegal character of the contract, and its invalidity, as well as the invalidity of the security given upon it, is not an unusual condition of things under the laws of New York. The loaning of money at a greater rate of interest than seven per cent, per an-­num is forbidden by law. The contract of loan, when thus made, is illegal, and any se­curity taken in in furtherance of it is void. 1 Rev. St. p. 772, §§ 2, 5. A contract to pay money arising out of a betting or gaming transaction is forbidden by law, and the con­tract itself, and any security connected with it, are equally void. Id. p. 6G2, § S. A con­tract for the sale or purchase of lottery tick­ets, or articles by raffle, is in like manner forbidden by law, and the contract itself and all securities arising out of it are void. Id. p. C65, §§ 22, 24, 26, 27, 34, etc.</p>
                <p pgmap="398" id="b398-4">•The argument to sustain the claim of a re­covery on the part of the safe deposit com­pany, is based upon the idea that the loan of money by the bank is legal, that its char­ter authorized the company to make loans, and that it was the form, time and manner of the loan which was objectionable; and that hence, while the security which em­bodies these objections is illegal and void, and cannot be recovered upon, the loan or the debt may and does remain valid. To support this view are cited what are called the “Utica Insurance Cases”: Utica Ins. Co. v. Scott, 19 Johns. 1; Same v. Cadwell, 3 Wend. 296; Same v. Bloodgood, 4 Wend. 652; Same v. Kip, 8 Cow. 20; Same v. Scott, Id. 709.</p>
                <p pgmap="398" id="b398-5">The case in Johnson’s Reports, against Scott, arose upon a demurrer, and simply went to the point adjudged in the “Per Curiam” opinion, that the security was void under the restraining act, and judgment was ordered accordingly. The remark that, al­though the security was void, the money lent might be recovered, was entirely obiter.</p>
                <p pgmap="398" id="b398-6">In the case against Kip (8 Cow. 20), the question was presented upon the second plea, which was for money lent, and the court held, that, although the security was void, the loan constituted a valid cause of action, and gave judgment for the plaintiff. The only direct authority cited was the case against Scott, above referred to. The obiter remark of the court in that case is quoted in full.</p>
                <p pgmap="398" id="b398-7">The case of Scott was carried to the court of errors (8 Cow. 709), where the judgment below was .reversed. It was there held, (1st,) that the insurance company had the right to loan their surplus funds, and to take a note as evidence of the debt (page 718); (2d,) that the restraining act did not apply to that com­pany, by reason of the provision of their charter allowing them to invest their funds (page 719). These were the conclusions of Spencer, J., in the only prevailing opinion reported.</p>
                <p pgmap="398" id="b398-8">In Utica Ins. Co. v. Cadwell, 3 Wend. 296, the decision in Kip’s case was adopted with­out comment or discussion. The court (Suth­erland. J.) say, that there is a distinction, as held by the former cases, between the se­curity and the contract of lending; and that, as the lending was not declared to be void, wherever money was lent it might be recov­ered under the common counts, although no action could be sustained upon the security. The note was held to be competent evidence of money lent, under the common counts.</p>
                <p pgmap="398" id="b398-9">In relation to these cases I observe:</p>
                <p pgmap="398" id="b398-10">1.That they are distinguishable from the present in one important feature, viz., that the insurance company had the right to make personal loans of their surplus funds, and whether they made the loan upon the se­curity of a bond or a note, or without either; it was declared, made no practical difference. This was the opinion of Spencer, Senator, in Scott’s Case, 8 Cow. 709. The company, in the present case, had no power to make per­sonal loans. Its powers were restricted and limited to those contained in its. charter. This is expressly declared in the provision of the Revised Statutes, already cited. Upon turning to the authority to make its loans, we find the subjects specifically set forth, as the stocks of the United States, or of the states, bonds and mortgages, bonds of cities or towns. Personal ioans are not mentioned, and are, therefore, by statute, excluded from the class in which the moneys of this com­pany can be invested.</p>
                <p pgmap="398" id="b398-12">2. The terms of the restraining act now in force, as well as the language of the Re­vised Statutes, are quite different from the language of the act in force when the Utica Insurance Cases were decided. “No incor­porated company, without being authorized by law, shall employ any part of its effects * * * for the purpose of making dis­counts.” 1 Rev. St. p. 712, | 3. Here Is a positive prohibition against investing the funds of a corporation in discounted bills. Such a contract is illegal, as being posi­tively forbidden by law. The language of the old act was aimed at the creation of a company and the establishment of an office, like that of section one of the present act, forbidding the becoming members of a company for the purpose of issuing notes, making discounts &amp;c., and not containing the language above quoted. 2 Rev. Laws, 1813, p. 234, | 2. Neither does the old law contain the provision of title 18 of the Re­vised Statutes, that no corporation not ex­pressly created for banking purposes, shall, by any implication or construction, be deem­ed to possess the power of discounting bills. Had the Revised Laws of 1813, which were in force when the Utica Insurance Cases were decided, contained these provisions, there is no reason to think they would have been decided as they were.</p>
                <p pgmap="398" id="b398-15">3. The correctness of the decisions in those cases, has been repeatedly questioned, and their authority much weakened. See New Hope &amp; D. Bridge Co. v. Poughkeepsie Silk Co., 25 Wend. 650, opinion of Mr. Justice Nel­son; Tracy v. Talmage, 14 N. Y. 189, opin­ion of Mr. Justice Selden; and the opinion of Mr. Justice Comstock, in Curtis v. Leavitt, 15 N. Y. 98. To give them the force con­tended for, will render the restraining act substantially useless. If their holding is as broad as is contended for, they are in direct hostility to an almost endless line of authori­ties, to the effect that the violator of the law cannot recover upon a contract embracing or founded upon that violation.</p>
                <p pgmap="398(15) 399(349)" id="b398-16">4. The Utica Insurance Cases should not be confounded with that class of cases of which Oneida Bank v. Ontario Bank, 21 N. Y. 490, and Curtis v. Leavitt, 15 N. Y. 9, are instances, in which the plaintiffs re­covered for-money advanced, although their security was repudiated. In the first of these cases, the statute of New York (Act May 14, 1S40; Laws 1840, p. 300, § 4) was involved which declared that “no banking association shall issue or put in circulation any bill or note of such association, unless the same shall be made payable on demand and with­out interest.” Mr. Augustus Perry loaned to the Ontario Bank 814,000 and took its drafts on Duncan &amp; Sherman of New York, for the amount, all being made and delivered about four weeks before their dates. The court held, (1) that these were drafts, within the statute mentioned; (2) that they were not’ payable on demand; (3) that they were il­legal and void; and, (4) that the lender or holder could recover from the bank issu­ing them the amount of money so loaned. The principle of this decision was this, that Perry had done nothing prohibited by law. He had simply loaned his money to the bank, and the bank had received it. The bank violated a positive provision of the statute in making its security for the loan payable on time, but Perry violated no law. All the cases recognize the distinction be­tween the guilty party to an illegal con­tract and the innocent party. The bank violated a provision of the statute, in mak­ing its drafts payable on time, and was liable to its penalties, but Perry violated no law, statutory or moral, and was sub­ject to no punishment. The cases of Tra­cy v. Talmage, 14 N. Y. 162, Curtis v. Lea­vitt, 15 N. Y. 9, and Sackett’s Harbor Bank v. Codd, 18 N. Y. 240, involve the same prin­ciple. In the case before us it is the guilty party, the violator of the law, the safe de­posit company, that seeks to enforce the il­legal contract, against a party comparatively innocent.</p>
                <p pgmap="399" id="b399-4">It is further contended, admitting these loans to be illegal, that no title to the money received by Jaycox &amp; Green passed to them, that the assignees represent stockholders and creditors, and .that they have the right to recall the money, in an action for money had and received. The powers and authority of an assignee in bankruptcy are such as are given to him by the statutes of the United States. Every assignee appointed under the bankrupt act possesses the same power, whether the scene of his action is in New York, Illinois or Texas. The statutes of a state cannot take away from him any of his lawful powers, nor, I apprehend, are his powers to be increased by the effect of state statutes. He is strictly and essentially a creation of the United States authority, in­tended to be subject to the United States jurisdiction, under a system of bankruptcy which shall be uniform throughout the whole country. It is to the statutes of the United States, therefore, and not to the statutes of the state of New York, giving power to local and state trustees, executors or as­signees, that we are to look for the solution of the question now under consideration. Curtis v. Leavitt, 15 N. Y. 44.</p>
                <p pgmap="399" id="b399-6">The powers and the authority of an as-­signee in bankruptcy are particularly specifi­ed in the fourteenth section of the bankrupt act 14 Stat -522. The register is, in that section, directed to make a conveyance to the assignee of “all the estate, real and personal, of the bankrupt,” and thereupon, “the title to all such property and estate, both real and personal, shall vest in said assignee.” It is further declared, “that all the property conveyed by the bankrupt in fraud of his creditors, all rights in equity, choses in ac­tion, * * * all debts due him or any per­son for his use, * * * all his rights of ac­tion for property or estate, real or personal, and for any cause of action which the bank­rupt had against any person, arising from contract or from the unlawful taking or de­tention of, or injury to, the property of the bankrupt * * * shall ♦ * * be at once vested in such assignee.” It is further de­clared, that the assignee “may sue for .and recover the said estate, debts and effects, and may prosecute and defend all suits at law or in equity pending at the time of the adjudication in bankruptcy, in the same man­ner and with the like effect” as the bankrupt could have done. There are numerous pro­visions scattered through the act to carry out these powers, but the powers enumerated above, it is believed, embrace every au­thority that can bear upon the point under consideration, in substance, the statute gives authority to the assignee, (1st,) to seize, sue for and recover any and all prop­erty, estate or rights belonging to the as-­signee at the time of the commencement of the proceedings in bankruptcy; and, (2d), to sue for and recover any property conveyed by the bankrupt in fraud of his creditors. If the property belonged to the bankrupt at the time specified, or he then had an interest in it, legal or equitable, whatever might be its form, a right at once vested in the assignee. If the bankrupt had no such right or in­terest, but would have had, except that he had previously made a conveyance of his property for the purpose of defrauding his creditors, the assignee was authorized to at­tack such fraudulent conveyance and recov­er the property which had passed under it. As against the bankrupt, that conveyance was good, but, as representing his creditors, who, under certain circumstances, could at­tack it, the assignee was authorized to take measures to set it aside.</p>
                <p pgmap="399(56) 400(116)" id="b399-7">The claim against Jaycox &amp; Green does not fall within either branch of this authority. The money loaned by the safe deposit com­pany to Jaycox &amp; Green became the property of the latter, was taken by them into their possession, and became mixed with, and a part of, their general funds. It was, for this purpose, the case of an ordinary loan of money, by which the lender parts absolutely with his money and all right and interest in it, and receives in return the note or other security of the borrower. The lender has no rights in law or equity to the money loan­ed, or any lien or claim upon the same. The present loan, although forbidden to be made by the safe deposit company, and illegal on their part, was nevertheless, made in fact. It was an accomplished fact, and the money and all interest in it passed beyond the con­trol of the company, more completely, if pos­sible, than in the ordinary case of money loaned.</p>
                <p pgmap="400" id="b400-4">Nor can the transaction come under the head of a conveyance by the bankrupt of his property “in fraud of his creditors.” That is a case of one who, for his own benefit or that of his family, conveys property in which he secretly reserves an interest for his own benefit, or by which he intends dishonestly to prefer one class of creditors to another. Here, the safe deposit company intended no reserved benefit to itself. Jaycox &amp; Green were parties to no such intention. Nor was it intended to prefer one creditor or. class to another.</p>
                <p pgmap="400" id="b400-5">The safe deposit company, in violation of law, entered upon a general banking busi­ness. As a part of that business, it loaned the money in question. It was an illegal contract. • It was made, however, by the cor­poration, under a formal resolution of its board of directors, and sanctioned by the ac­quiescence of its stockholders at its annual meetings. It has been already shown that the company could not recover either upon the security received or for money loaned. If it is possible for a corporation itself to make a contract so that the question of an excess of power on the part of its agents can­not arise, thisfis such a case.</p>
                <p pgmap="400" id="b400-6">The point under consideration is not well taken, and, upon the whole case, I am of the opinion that the claim of the assignees against the estate of Jaycox &amp; Green can­not be sustained, and that the proof of the debt of the safe deposit eompanj1’ must be ex­punged.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="395" ORDERLABEL="393" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00198_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00198_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00198_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_395.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00198_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="396" ORDERLABEL="394" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00198_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00198_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00198_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_396.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00198_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="397" ORDERLABEL="395" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00199_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00199_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00199_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_397.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00199_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="398" ORDERLABEL="396" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00199_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00199_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00199_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_398.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00199_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="399" ORDERLABEL="397" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00200_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00200_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00200_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_399.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00200_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="400" ORDERLABEL="398" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00200_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00200_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00200_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_400.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00200_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AcLA" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_395.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00198_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b398-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_398.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00199_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b397-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_397.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00199_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b398-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_398.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00199_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b398-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_398.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00199_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b398-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_398.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00199_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b398-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_398.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00199_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b399-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_399.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00200_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b399-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_399.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00200_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_400.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00200_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b396-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_396.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00198_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_396.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00198_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b396-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_396.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00198_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b400-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_400.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00200_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AyG" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_395.20" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00198_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b395-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_395.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00198_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b397-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_397.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00199_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b396-11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_396.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00198_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_397.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00199_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b397-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_397.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00199_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b399-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_399.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00200_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_399.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00200_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b397-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_397.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00199_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_397.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00199_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b400-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_400.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00200_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b398-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_398.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00199_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AT2J" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_395.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00198_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b397-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_397.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00199_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_398.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00199_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AuBv" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_395.21" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00198_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b398-15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_398.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00199_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b395-20" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_395.22" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00198_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AglS" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_395.23" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00198_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_395.24" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00198_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_396.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00198_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b395-12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_395.16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00198_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="A6o" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_395.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00198_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b398-12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_398.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00199_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b400-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_400.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00200_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b398-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_398.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00199_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_398.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00199_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b398-16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_398.15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00199_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_399.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00200_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AMl2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0234"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_395.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00198_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
