<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044046873683_0237" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="D. Or." jurisdiction="United States">United States District Court for the District of Oregon</court>
          <name abbreviation="The Eliza Ladd">The ELIZA LADD</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 4,364</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">8 F. Cas. 491</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">3 Sawy. 519; 1 N. Y. Wkly. Dig. 517; 8 Chi. Leg. News, 98; 21 Int. Rev. Rec. 48; 2 Cent. Law J. 822; 1 Law &amp; Eq. Rep. 28; 7 Leg. Gaz. 414</citation>
          <decisiondate>1875-11-24</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-12T19:40:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-26T10:42:09Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-26T10:56:34Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00247_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="8f710c6a4289c5e8b6a406df8775fb10" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="99624">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00247_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00247_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="9ed182c69cfb218d6eda0c0d034cb770" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="99362">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00247_1.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00247_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="e592517b02c29ee4667a8a5bc3ef711e" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3567615">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00247_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00247_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="b700111cf393067c3561116a15d7ea29" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3508994">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00247_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00247_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="d54099b37a6a3ed19dbb4d401de5c9a5" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="222863">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00247_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00247_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="a12374c5db0b5ea5b1ae98bc6b47ccea" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="216467">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00247_1.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0237" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="492" firstpage="491">
              <court id="b493-8" pgmap="493">District Court, D. Oregon.</court>
              <docketnumber id="b493-2" pgmap="493">Case No. 4,364.</docketnumber>
              <citation id="b493-4" pgmap="493">[3 Sawy. 519; 1 N. Y. Wkly. Dig. 517; 8 Chi. Leg. News, 98; 21 Int. Rev. Rec. 48; 2 Cent. Law J. 822; 1 Law &amp; Eq. Rep. 28; 7 Leg. Gaz. 414.] <footnotemark>1</footnotemark>
              </citation>
              <parties id="b493-3" pgmap="493">The ELIZA LADD.</parties>
              <decisiondate id="A1uS" pgmap="493">Nov. 24, 1875.</decisiondate>
              <attorneys id="b493-15" pgmap="493">John W. Whalley, for libellant.</attorneys>
              <attorneys id="b493-16" pgmap="493">E. C. Bronaugh, for claimant</attorneys>
              <footnote label="1">
                <p id="b493-19" pgmap="493">1 [Beported by L. S. B. Sawyer, Esq., and here reprinted by permission. 1 N. Y. Wkly. Dig. 517, contains only a partial report.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author id="b493-17" pgmap="493">DEADY, District Judge.</author>
                <p id="AXv" pgmap="493">The amended li­bel in this case was filed October 18, 1875, and alleges substantially that the Eliza Ladd is a domestic vessel, propelled by steam, of the burden of 118.47 tons, and was enrolled at Portland on August 31, 1875, and is em­ployed in navigating the waters of the Willa- : mette; that she was launched at Portland near Smith’s mill, in October, 1874, and on May 28," 1875, she made a voyage in tow of another vessel to the foot of Stark street, and there took on her boilers, engines and machinery, the same having been in the ferryboat Portland No. 1, and from thence, on June 1, 1875, made a voyage in like man­ner to the libellant’s works at Albina on said Willamette river; that on June 1, 1875, the libellant, the Oregon Iron Works, a corpora­tion duly formed under the laws of Oregon, and engaged in business at Albina, was . em­ployed by the owner and claimant of said vessel, Joseph Knott, to furnish the mate­rial in addition to the boilers, engines and machinery aforesaid, and perform the la­bor necessary to fit, equip and furnish said vessel for such sum as the same should be reasonably worth; that between said last-­mentioned date and August 18, 1875, said li-­bellant performed said contract, and that the reasonable value of the materials and labor furnished by libellant in so doing is $1,498, in lawful money of the United States, and that no part of said sum, except $13.84, in old iron, has been paid libellant.</p>
                <p id="b493-18" pgmap="493">The claimant excepts to the libel, that the contract described therein is not a maritime one, and that this court has no jurisdiction to enforce the supposed lien incident thereto. It is admitted that according to the ruling of the supreme court in People’s Ferryboat v. Beers, 20 How. [61 U. S.] 393, and Roach v. Chapman, 22 How. [63 U. S.] 129, a con­tract to build or construct a ship, is not a maritime one, and therefore not within the admiralty jurisdiction of the United States. This rule is founded upon the assumption that such a contract is one “made on land to be performed on land.” On the other hand it is admitted that, by the general maritime law of the civilized world, a contract to build a ship is a maritime contract, because it has relation to a ship as the agent or ve­hicle of commerce upon a navigable water. Ben. Adm. §§ 213, 264.</p>
                <p id="b493-22" pgmap="493">Under the law of the cases above cited, it is not always easy to determine what is a maritime contract In the case in 20 How. [61 U. S.] the contract was for “work done and materials employed in constructing the hull of a new steam ferryboat,” while the case in 22 How. [63 U. S.] was for furnish­ing “boilers and engines” to be placed in a steamboat at the time and place of the con­struction of the hull/ It is well established that a contract to furnish work and nTate-­rials to be employed in making repairs on a vessel is a maritime contract. The St. Law­rence, 1 Black. [66 U. S.] 522; Peyroux v. How. ard, 7 Pet. [32 U. S.] 324. And in such cases, even if the vessel is a domestic one, if the local law gives the material-man a lien, it may be enforced in the admiralty. The Gen­eral Smith, 4 Wheat [17 U. S.] 438; The Lot­tawana, 21 Wall. [88 U. S.] 579. Now, re­pairs include all alterations and additions made to a vessel, short of destroying her identity. “A ship is always the same ship, although the original materials of which it was composed may, by successive repairs and alterations, have been in the course of time entirely changed.” Ben. Adm. § 223.</p>
                <p id="b493-23" pgmap="493(203) 494(22)">Suppose the Eliza Ladd to have been built and used as a barge, and that afterwards her owner had concluded to use her as a steam ferry or tug boat, and for this pur­pose should make a contract with A. B. to put the necessary boilers and machinery in­to her, suclran agreement would doubtless be a maritime contract And yet a contract to build a steam ferry or tug boat outright would not be, under the decisions cited, a maritime contract.'My own impression is that any contract made to equip, fit or fur­nish a vessel after she is launched and afloat is a maritime contract .It is not in the lan­guage of 20 How. [61 U. S.) supra, “a con­tract made on land to be performed on land,” but one made with reference to a ship al­ready in existence and floating upon the element for which she was originally de­signed. Such a contract is to be performed on water-as much as an ordinary contract, of affreightment or repairs. When the con­tract to build includes the fitting, furnishing, and equipping also, it may be said, that as it is an entirety and not divisible, and the principal feature of it — the building and launching the hull — being non-maritime, it gives character to the whole of it</p>
                <p id="b494-4" pgmap="494">When the contract set up in the libel was made, the Eliza Ladd had been launched eight months, and for aught that appears was in the same condition she is now, as to her ca­pacity for changing place or carrying freight and passengers, less the machinery necessa­ry to propel her by steam. She was then, it appears to me, a Ship, within the defini­tion in Ben. Adm. § 215: “A locomotive ma­chine adapted to transportation over rivers, seas, and oceans.” She was certainly a ma­chine — an artificial contrivance, and one ca­pable of locomotion or change of place, as is shown by the two short voyages she made before the performance of this contract; nor does it make any difference whether she was “propelled by the wind, the tide or pad­dles, by steam, by animals, or by the human arm, or towed by another vessel” (Id. § 217), so that she floated in and moved through the water. Being of one hundred and eigh­teen tons burden, she was also adapted to the transportation of freight and passengers so far as she had capacity for locomotion. Separate pieces of timber or iron, or both, being put together in a certain form, so as to float upon the water and transport or bear up freight or passengers, may become a ship. At what point of time is this chánge accomplished? I am inclined to think that the correct answer to this question is sug­gested in the brief for the libellant, and that it is “at the moment when she leaves the ways, and her keel strikes the element for which she was originally designed.” That is the moment of her birth as a ship, and the occasion when a name is usually bestow-­ed on her. Thereafter all contracts to equip, furnish or repair this machine have direct reference to a vessel in esse, with capacity for locomotion and transportation on navi­gable waters, and are, therefore, maritime,'</p>
                <p id="b494-5" pgmap="494">Although a contract to build a ship is in fact a maritime one, yet under the rule laid down in 20 and 22 How. [61 and 63 U. S.] supra, it is to be otherwise regarded in this court. The difficulty is to determine what is ' included in building a ship — the contract for which, says the court, is not maritime, be­cause it is “made on land to be performed on land.” But, even under that rule, it seems safe to say, that a contract made after a vessel is launched and afloat, to furnish her with a particular means of propulsion, as sails or steam paddles, or to change the mode of her propulsion, is a maritime con­tract. Certainly it is not a contract to be performed on land; neither is it a contract to build any more than any contract for re­pairs.</p>
                <p id="b494-6" pgmap="494">Although this is a domestic vessel, and this work and materials were furnished in her home port, yet the libellant has a lien for the amount of his claim under section 17, p. 656, of the Oregon Code, and the con­tract being a maritime one, the lien may be enforced in admiralty.</p>
                <p id="b494-8" pgmap="494">The exception is overruled.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="493" ORDERLABEL="491" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00247_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00247_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00247_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_493.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00247_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="494" ORDERLABEL="492" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00247_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00247_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00247_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_494.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00247_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="A1uS" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0237"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_493.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00247_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b493-19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0237"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_493.22" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00247_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b493-18" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0237"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_493.20" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00247_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_493.21" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00247_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AXv" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0237"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_493.18" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00247_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_493.19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00247_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b493-16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0237"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_493.16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00247_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b494-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0237"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_494.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00247_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_494.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00247_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b494-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0237"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_494.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00247_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b494-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0237"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_494.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00247_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b493-23" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0237"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_493.24" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00247_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_494.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00247_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b493-22" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0237"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_493.23" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00247_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b493-15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0237"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_493.15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00247_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b494-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0237"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_494.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00247_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b493-17" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0237"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_493.17" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00247_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b493-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0237"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_493.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00247_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b493-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0237"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_493.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00247_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b493-2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0237"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_493.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00247_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b493-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0237"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_493.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00247_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
