<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044049817315_0188" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="E.D.N.Y." jurisdiction="United States">United States District Court for the Eastern District of New York</court>
          <name abbreviation="The James Guy">The JAMES GUY</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 7,195</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">13 F. Cas. 331</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">1 Ben. 112; 5 Int. Rev. Rec. 68</citation>
          <decisiondate>1867-02</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-10T00:25:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:27:33Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:41:27Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00167_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="6df86dda7aee7751c1ac42ff9505977b" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="89406">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00167_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00167_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="862c7fa08cfd8ffab2c469efb73a1068" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="90456">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00167_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00168_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="7dc34e347e653acd1122b94017ef3254" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="97340">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00168_0.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00167_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="291726b1a3a0bdc7d3b70540994075a2" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3516113">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00167_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00167_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="14d7a33466bf15a3aafe5d12c23d8720" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3291611">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00167_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00168_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="93aab52d3fddac194cf01a2c61f3a033" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3515526">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00168_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00167_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="20f9b177ce7f2830db82d6773875de16" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="193734">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00167_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00167_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="6061851701487fd304b171061227497c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="198873">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00167_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00168_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="b8546c157f714f13812aae8f9ed95360" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="218594">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00168_0.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0188" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="333" firstpage="331">
              <court pgmap="333" id="A4lB">District Court, E. D. New York.</court>
              <docketnumber pgmap="333" id="b333-10">Case No. 7,195.</docketnumber>
              <citation pgmap="333" id="AzX">[1 Ben. 112;<footnotemark>1</footnotemark> 5 Int. Rev. Rec. 68.]</citation>
              <parties pgmap="333" id="ATL">The JAMES GUY.</parties>
              <decisiondate pgmap="333" id="A5XX">Feb., 1867.<footnotemark>2</footnotemark>
              </decisiondate>
              <attorneys pgmap="334" id="b334-12">Emerson &amp; Goodrich, for libellant.</attorneys>
              <attorneys pgmap="334" id="b334-13">Beebe, Dean &amp; Donohue, for claimant.</attorneys>
              <footnote label="1">
                <p pgmap="333" id="b333-17">1 [Reported by Robert D. Benedict, Esq., and here reprinted by permission.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <footnote label="2">
                <p pgmap="333" id="b333-18">2 [Affirmed in Case No. 7,196.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author pgmap="334" id="b334-14">BENEDICT, District Judge.</author>
                <p pgmap="334" id="Au8x">This is an notion brought to recover of the steamer James Guy the sum of 82,534, being the amount of a bill of repairs put on that ves­sel in July, 1866, by Young Tall, the libel-­lant. No question is raised as to the per­forming of the work or the correctness of the amount charged. The sole controversy is whether the facts establish a lien upon ’the vessel.</p>
                <p pgmap="334" id="b334-15">It appears in evidence, that the work in question was ordered by George Olney in Baltimore, where both Olney and the ves­sel were at that time. Olney was the own­er of the boat, and a resident of the city •of Brooklyn, New York. The vessel is con­ceded to have been foreign to the port of Baltimore. The work was commenced on the 17th of July, and soon after it was com­pleted the vessel left Baltimore, and has never since returned. In April following, she came to this port, having shortly be­fore been transferred by Olney to his son-­in-law, who is the claimant in this action, and who, as I understand the evidence, must be held chargeable with a knowledge of the existence of this demand at the time he took title.</p>
                <p pgmap="334" id="b334-16">The work was necessary for the vessel in her then business. Its character shows this, and the fact that the owner himself, being then present, directed the work, also estab­lishes this. One test of necessity is, wheth­er a prudent owner would sanction the ex­penditure. The Alexander, 1 W. Rob. Adm. 362.</p>
                <p pgmap="334" id="b334-17">The work was, moreover, done on the cred­it of the vessel, and not upon the exclusive personal credit of Olney. Upon this point, the testimony of the libellant is positive. He is supported by the circumstance, that the work was at the time charged to the boat, and not to Olney, on the bills. Olney, the owner, knew that it was so charged, for he received without objection the bills made out against the boat; and two time drafts which he gave for the amount, contained the words, “Charge to account of steamer James Guy.” Circumstances like these have •repeatedly been held sufficient to show an agreement based upon the credit of the ves­sel.</p>
                <p pgmap="334" id="b334-20">Furthermore, Olney himself when examin­ed, does not undertake to deny the state­ment of the libellant, that the credit of the vessel was relied on, and nowhere says that the work was contracted solely upon his personal responsibility. It is indeed true that, as he says, time was stipulated for and time drafts taken for the amount, but that does not show or tend to show that the re­sponsibility of the vessel was not looked to when the debt was contracted, and the cred­it of the' vessel made a part of the agree­ment. Time is the very foundation and rea­son of a maritime lien upon a vessel. The maritime law gives the lien in order that the material man may give time, and so the vessel may proceed to make voyages, and earn freight to pay her bills. The Nes­tor [Case No. 10,126]. And provisions for the credit of the vessel, and for delay of payment, are not only not inconsistent with each other, but the latter feature tends somewhat to show the existence of the for­mer in the agreement. The evidence here, if it be not sufficient to warrant finding an express hypothecation of the vessel as se­curity, shows very satisfactorily to me that the responsibility of the boat for the bill was a feature in the transaction, recognized by both parties at the time of contracting the debt, and this being so, according to the general maritime law, as I understand it, a lien was created which a court of admiralty is bound to enforce. And such, it is con­ceded, would have been the law of this case previous to the decision of the supreme court in the case of Pratt v. Reed [19 How. (60 U. S.) 359]; but it is contended, that, accord­ing to the ruling in that case, this libel must be dismissed, for the reason that it has not been made to appear that at the time of making the agreement in question, Olney, the ship owner, was without credit in Balti­more.</p>
                <p pgmap="334" id="b334-21">Now with the most sincere desire to give to this and all other decisions of the appellate court their full force and effect as the au­thoritative guides of the courts below, I find it difficult to consider the case of Pratt v. Reed [supra], as deciding more than this: that when the circumstances of the case are such as to raise a presumption that there was no necessity for an implied hypotheca­tion, it then becomes incumbent on the libel-­lant to show a necessity for a credit</p>
                <p pgmap="334(9) 335(117)" id="b334-22">But whether such be or be not the true construction to put upon the decision in the case of Pratt v. Heed, I am quite confident that no such sweeping effect as is here con­tended for should be given to it. The claim now is that, under that decision, no matter how insolvent in point of fact the ship own­er may be, and no matter how devoid of credit he may be. in the place of his resi­dence, and no matter what other circum­stances attend the contracting of the- debt, no implied lien for supplies can ever be held established, in the absence of proof that the ship owner was without personal credit at the time and place of incurring the debt.</p>
                <p pgmap="335" id="b335-4">Now the opinion delivered in the case of Pratt v. Heed seems to me to indicate that such could not have been the understanding of the court, for if such be the law intended to be declared, it is conceded that it is con­trary to the whole current of former de­cisions upon the subject; but the opinion contains no intimation of an intention to disturb the adjudged eases. Moreover, the case of The Alexander, cited in the opinion in support of the decision, is adverse to such a view of the law, and the facts of the case before the court called for no such deter­mination.</p>
                <p pgmap="335" id="b335-5">Such a doctrine would have the effect to enable a ship owner to take advantage of a fraudulent credit, temporarily established in a strange community, to deprive material men of that security which under the real facts of the case the maritime law, looking to the interests of commerce and on the con­siderations affecting public policy, has al­ways given.</p>
                <p pgmap="335" id="b335-6">And such is the effect sought here. Olney, the owner of this vessel, who contracted the debt in question, was in fact a bankrupt. In the place of his residence, he was, and had been for years, notoriously insolvent. Over thirty judgments, rendered within the past ten years, stand recorded against him in Brooklyn. He was at the time in ques­tion so destitute of money that his hotel bill due on his leaving Baltimore, was left partly unpaid. Any personal credit which he might have been able to acquire in Bal­timore was wholly fictitious, based upon a concealment of his real position, and at once to be dissipated upon a declaration of the truth. Can such a credit, assuming it to have been proved in this ease, in justice to the parties or to the community, be availed of by him as a defence to an action like this? I cannot think that the general lan­guage of some parts of the opinion of the supreme court, in the case of Pratt v. Reed, can, with justice to that court, be sep­arated from the facts of the case before it, and considered as decisive of a case like this. My opinion, on the contrary, is, that when the libellant here proved, as he did beyond dispute, that Olney, the ship own­er, was in fact bankrupt,, without money, he sufficiently proved a necessity for the credit of the vessel. And this I believe to be in accordance with the late decision of Judge Shipman, in the case of The Neversink [Case No. 10,132], and with the decision of Judge Sprague, in the case of The Sea Lark [Id. 12.579].</p>
                <p pgmap="335" id="b335-8">The result, then, is that the libellant has a subsisting lien upon this vessel, unless it was waived by the taking of two time drafts-­for the amount, one at sixty and the other at ninety days. Here the burden is upon the claimant to show that the libellant agreed to receive the drafts in lieu of and in place of the original claim. The St. Law­rence. 1 Black [66 U. S.] 532. The drafts were drawn by Olney upon himself, and gave no additional security, and I find no evidence in the case which will warrant the conclusion that the libellant intended by tak­ing them to change the character of the 'de­mand from an account against the vessel to an account against Olney personally. Nor do I consider that the fact that one of these drafts had not matured at the commence­ment of this suit, can be available in re­ducing the amount of the decree. Both drafts are now due, and both unpaid, and both are surrendered in court; all the delay of pay­ment agreed on has been obtained, and, both drafts having been surrendered, I see no reason why the decree should not be for the whole bill.</p>
                <p pgmap="335" id="b335-9">My determination, therefore, is that under the facts of this case a lien is established in favor of the libellant for the amount of his bill, and while it is a satisfaction to me to feel that not only the law but the jus­tice of the case require such determination, it is also satisfactory to know that the amount of the claim is sufficient to enable an appeal to be taken to an appellate court, where any error I may have committed can be promptly corrected. Let a decree be en­tered for the amount of the bill, with inter­est</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="333" ORDERLABEL="331" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00167_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00167_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00167_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_333.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00167_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="334" ORDERLABEL="332" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00167_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00167_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00167_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_334.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00167_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="335" ORDERLABEL="333" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00168_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00168_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00168_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_335.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00168_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b335-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0188"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_335.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00168_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b335-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0188"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_335.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00168_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b335-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0188"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_335.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00168_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b334-13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0188"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_334.15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00167_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b334-12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0188"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_334.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00167_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b334-15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0188"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_334.19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00167_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b334-17" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0188"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_334.21" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00167_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_334.22" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00167_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b334-14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0188"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_334.16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00167_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="A5XX" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0188"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_333.17" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00167_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b333-18" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0188"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_333.23" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00167_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b334-22" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0188"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_334.25" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00167_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_335.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00168_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b334-21" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0188"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_334.24" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00167_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b334-16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0188"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_334.20" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00167_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="A4lB" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0188"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_333.16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00167_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b334-20" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0188"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_334.23" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00167_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Au8x" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0188"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_334.17" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00167_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_334.18" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00167_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AzX" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0188"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_333.15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00167_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="ATL" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0188"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_333.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00167_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b335-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0188"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_335.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00168_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b333-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0188"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_333.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00167_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b335-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0188"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_335.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00168_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_335.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00168_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b333-17" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0188"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_333.22" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00167_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
