<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044046873683_0445" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="N.D.N.Y." jurisdiction="United States">United States District Court for the Northern District of New York</court>
          <name abbreviation="Evans v. The John F. Warner">EVANS v. The JOHN F. WARNER</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 4,563</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">8 F. Cas. 870</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">4 West. Law Month. 193</citation>
          <decisiondate>1862-03</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-12T19:40:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-26T10:42:09Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-26T10:56:35Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00436_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="1e27649f5554280d133780526b77b166" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="86036">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00436_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00437_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="809dd99ff6a543b923ec16f8e95487b9" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="116314">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00437_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00437_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="cb70d65e329006f5be4593bb9bcf5b5a" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="51426">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00437_1.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00436_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="a88aee34ed6877fb1bd8f48368f00840" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3221946">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00436_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00437_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="9c0305cf1d7ed9260dcefb6cc84da05e" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3825476">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00437_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00437_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="ba4efd2a7f7e5a695f849f15f960226b" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2335148">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00437_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00436_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="c37d9c418a18e36d974ff85cdffa0e89" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="185334">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00436_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00437_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="5666a5df5902a21e41e91a29191126b8" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="255634">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00437_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00437_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="562260e61b43d513c0df24cfb0349a4f" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="109650">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00437_1.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0445" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="872" firstpage="870">
              <court id="b872-16" pgmap="872">District Court, N. D. New York.</court>
              <docketnumber id="b872-13" pgmap="872">Case No. 4,563.</docketnumber>
              <citation id="b872-15" pgmap="872">[4 West. Law Month. 193.]</citation>
              <parties id="b872-14" pgmap="872">EVANS v. The JOHN F. WARNER.</parties>
              <decisiondate id="ATyW" pgmap="872">March Term, 1862.</decisiondate>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author id="b872-20" pgmap="872">HALL, District Judge.</author>
                <p id="A74" pgmap="872(37) 873(461)">This is a case of collision. The libellant is the owner of the canal boat Mygatt, which was run into and sunk on the 11th November, 1861, whilst en­deavoring to turn in Buffalo creek, outside of the propeller Euphrates, which then lay at the dock near the foot of Commercial street The Warner was coming into port, with the wind blowing a gale directly up the stream. At a slight bend in the creek, a few rods be­low the Mygatt, she took a rank sheer to port, and ran against and earned away the stern of that boat before she could be brought up by her starboard anchor, which was cast as soon as possible after the sheer commenced. After a careful review of the testimony, I retain the impression made by the evidence at the hearing, and X shall there­fore dismiss the libel with costs. Consider­ing the necessity of carrying all the sail the Warner had up, in order to cross the bar at the mouth of the harbor; the season of the year; the violence of the gale; the wet and swollen condition of the rigging, and the con­sequent difficulty in taking in sail, the evi­dence which was given to show that the mas­ter of the Warner took in sail as rapidly as possible, is entirely satisfactory; and the preparations which he made before entering the harbor, and the whole conduct of the master, were of the most satisfactory char­acter, evincing superior' skill and more than ordinary prudence and forecast. No fault can be attributed to those in charge of the Warner; on the contrary, the evidence shows that her master was skillful, careful and en­ergetic, and that he did all that could be reasonably required of him in order to pre­vent a collision. That his vessel took a sud­den sheer, when she “smelt ground” on the spit referred to by the witnesses, was no fault of his; and when the sheer occurred, he did all that could be done to prevent the injury which ensued. In view of the possi­bility of being required to anchor in a sud-' den emergency, he had cleared away his anchors and stationed a man forward at the starboard anchor, ready to let it go, “stock and fluke;” and when the sheer to port oc­curred, the orders to put the helm hard-a-­port and let go the starboard anchor, fol­lowed in rapid succession. There was, how­ever, not sufficient space between the Warner and the Mygatt to allow the former to be brought up by her anchor before the colli­sion occurred, and the stem of the canal boat was crushed betwen the Warner and a schooner lying above the Euphrates and the Mygatt; a schooner which lay outside of two canal boats and two other schooners, ly­ing side by side, and extended far out to­wards the center of the channel of the creek.</p>
                <p id="b873-3" pgmap="873(639) 874(37)">It is probable from the evidence that the unusual accumulation on the spit at the point where the sheer occurred, was produced by the extraordinary freshet which had a few weeks before brought down mud, sand, and other deposits in the creek; and it may have been increased by the current which the gale then in progress had sent up the creek. At all events, it could not have been anticipated by the master of the Warner, that with the water of the creek at least two feet above its ordinary height, there could be any dan­ger in passing that point with his schooner; and' as he endeavored to avoid the spit as far as practicable-by going as near the op­posite side of the creek as the opening in the channel would allow, the Warner must be held entirely free from fault. The man­agement of the master of the canal boat in extending the stem of his boat so far out into the channel, after being warned, that a vessel was coming in, was extremely care­less. After he knew the Warner was ap­proaching, there was abundant time for him to haul his boat so far from the space left open by the unusual crowd of vessels in port as to be entirely out of danger, but he impru­dently, if not recklessly, crowded the stem of his boat into this open space, which, in con­sequence of the very extraordinary crowd of vessels in the creek, had been already narrow­ed to less than half the width of the channel, and thus brought on his boat the conse­quences of this collision. The master of the canal boat was bound to exercise extraordi­nary vigilance, as well as to act with great prudence and caution, in attempting to change the position of his boat under the cir­cumstances of the case. The harbor was crowded to excess with vessels lying three, four, and five abreast, in violation of the city ordinances, and narrowing the channel in many places — and particularly at that point where the Mygatt attempted to turn — to such an extent as to require the utmost care and skill on the part of those in charge of vessels, coming into port; vessels were frequently coming in and passing up this narrow chan­nel; the wind was blowing a gale up the creek; the weather had been wet and cold, and the sails and rigging of vessels were difficult of management; anchoring in the creek was dangerous to a vessel under way; and it was hardly possible that a vessel could be stopped by any other means below the point where the Mygatt lay; which was just above a slight bend in the creek, and just above the spit which caused the sheer of the Warner. The Mygatt was a canal boat, and therefore too frail to bear even a glancing blow from the heavier and stronger vessels coming in from the lake; her master was warned that a vessel was approaching, and of the danger of going out into the open channel; and yet he proceeded heedlessly and carelessly to place the stem of his boat a considerable distance outside of the vessels lying above and below him; and in such a position as to be crushed between the ap­proaching vessel and the outer vessel of those lying above him. To hold the master and crew of a sail vessel coming into port on a raw, chilly day, near the middle of Novem­ber, after the wearisome and exhausting la­bors of a stormy and tempestuous night, and with the wind still blowing a gale, in any degree responsible for a collision occurring under the circumstances of this case — a col­lision which very little exertion and less' than ordinary precaution on the- part of those in charge of the canal boat would have ren­dered impossible — would, in my opinion, he gross injustice. The libel in this case is dis­missed with costs.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="872" ORDERLABEL="870" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00436_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00436_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00436_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_872.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00436_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="873" ORDERLABEL="871" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00437_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00437_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00437_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_873.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00437_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="874" ORDERLABEL="872" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00437_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00437_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00437_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_874.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00437_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b872-16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0445"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_872.16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00436_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b872-15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0445"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_872.15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00436_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b872-14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0445"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_872.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00436_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b872-13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0445"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_872.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00436_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="A74" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0445"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_872.23" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00436_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_872.24" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00436_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_873.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00437_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b872-20" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0445"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_872.22" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00436_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="ATyW" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0445"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_872.17" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00436_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_872.18" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00436_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b873-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0445"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_873.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00437_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_873.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00437_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_874.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00437_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
