<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044046873683_0009" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="C.C.S.D. Ala." jurisdiction="United States">United States Circuit Court for the Southern District of Alabama</court>
          <name abbreviation="Duncan v. Mobile &amp; O. R.">DUNCAN et al. v. MOBILE &amp; O. R. CO. et al.</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 4,139</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">8 F. Cas. 25</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">3 Woods, 597</citation>
          <decisiondate>1879-06</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-12T19:40:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-26T10:42:09Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-26T10:56:32Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00014_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="c137e7b0deb21446f34e8bbcf793e17e" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="41566">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00014_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00014_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="047263215ebff804a9b984f9a7fda9ce" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="87180">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00014_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00015_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="31a671d63fab8ca1ff514c278cc72816" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="104588">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00015_0.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00014_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="be86084df45aa18b2a90c58a924080e3" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2039616">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00014_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00014_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="6a453920cf6b00f21b05691a26c9ef4f" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3120158">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00014_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00015_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="491f65e90165d11e18f62edd15d39ab0" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3842476">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00015_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00014_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="d8254297a3e2585201c4020e3e777394" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="82186">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00014_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00014_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="d7caf6361beb83f71dd13dba764cf2f6" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="187890">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00014_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00015_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="4120af308db74d969086cc5a62954929" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="221351">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00015_0.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0009" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="27" firstpage="25">
              <court id="b27-12" pgmap="27">Circuit Court, S. D. Alabama.</court>
              <docketnumber id="b27-9" pgmap="27">Case No. 4,139.</docketnumber>
              <citation id="b27-11" pgmap="27">[3 Woods, 597.] <footnotemark>1</footnotemark>
              </citation>
              <parties id="b27-10" pgmap="27">DUNCAN et al. v. MOBILE &amp; O. R. CO. et al.</parties>
              <decisiondate id="AvH" pgmap="27">June Term, 1879.</decisiondate>
              <judges id="b28-7" pgmap="28">Before BRADLEY, Circuit Justice, and WOODS, Circuit Judge.</judges>
              <attorneys id="b28-6" pgmap="28">John A. Campbell, Peter Hamilton, T. A. Hamilton, F. N. Bangs, J. A. Garfield, George N. Stewart, W. G. Jones, George Hoadly, E. H. Grandin, and E. L. Andrews, representing the various parties in interest</attorneys>
              <footnote label="1">
                <p id="b27-15" pgmap="27">1 [Reported by Hon. William B. Woods, Cir­cuit Judge, and hero reprinted by permission.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author id="b28-8" pgmap="28">BRADLEY, Circuit Justice.</author>
                <p id="AkE" pgmap="28">Bondholders secured by a common mortgage have equal rights in the common security, proportional to the amount held by each. If the mort­gaged property be sold to a stranger, the pro­ceeds are equally distributed and perfect jus­tice is dono to all. If bondholders purchase the entire property, they have an equitable right, after satisfying the costs and charges of the litigation and trust, to pay the balance in bonds, so far as their own proportion of such balance extends, for it is to come to them. But it is evident that those who singly, or in combination, hold a lai-ge portion of the bonds, have a great advantage over the minority; for they can pay their own propor­tion of the purchase money, which is much the largest, in bonds, and have only a small amount of cash to pay, whilst the minority can only pay a small proportion in bonds, and have a large amount to pay in cash, which, as a generality, they are totally unable to pay. This practically puts it in the power of the majority to get the property at a large sacrifice, and turn the minority off with a mere pittance. This is inequitable, and to be avoided if possible. Perhaps the most equita­ble mode of disposing of the property (when practicable), when it cannot be sold for cash to an amount sufficient to pay the bondhold­ers, is to decree a strict foreclosure, in which all will participate alike, or to make a sale-­for the equal benefit of all the bondholders who choose to come in and participate. A strict foreclosure may be attended with diffi­culties in those states where a mortgage is a mere security, and does not give a legal title, besides which, it places the property in the hands of a vast number of beneficiaries whose consent may be very difficult to obtain in per­fecting a new organization for conducting the business. A sale for the benefit of all is attended with the difficulty of determining who shall make the bid. The court has some­times authorized the trustees of the mortgage to bid for the bondholders. In this case, it is obvious that one class or the other of the bondholders would be dissatisfied with any selection of trustees which the court might make. To decree that all the bondholders, shall be allowed to participate in any sale that may be made, would practically nullify an auction sale. Who would bid on such, terms?</p>
                <p id="b28-11" pgmap="28">In this case, it has been brought to our no­tice that a scheme for reorganizing the com­pany, or the interests represented in its prop­erty, has been agreed to and subscribed by about seventy-eight per cent (in interest) of the first mortgage bondholders. We have examined this scheme, and if not perfectly equitable, we are unable to point out any want of fairness in it. It would give to those who have not joined in it, should they do so, about twenty and one-half per cent interest in the entire purchase; whilst if all first mortgage bondholders (including the Tennes­see bonds in the number) were placed on an exact proportionate division, the non-subscrib­ing interest in the purchase would amount to-­about twenty-one and five-eighths per cent But they run the risk of the Tennessee bonds being placed ahead of the others. If the lat­ter were given the preference, then, subject to that incumbrance, the non-subscribing in­terests would, by an equal division with the others, take about twenty-four eight-tenths per cent of the purchase, which is probably less advantageous to them than the proposed plan of reorganization would be.</p>
                <p id="b28-12" pgmap="28(135) 29(156)">Looking at the difficulties which beset the-­subject on every side, we think- that if we al­low the non-subscribing bondholders to par­ticipate in the purchase of the property, should it be made in behalf of the reorganiz­ing combination, on an equal footing with those who have joined it, that we shall have done all that we can do under the circumstan­ces to protect their interests. The parties-­representing the reconstruction scheme, through their counsel, have offered to allow them to come in, and to extend the time for doing so until the first of August. We sug­gest that this time should be extended to the day of sale of the property. We perceive that the trustees have the power to do this— and keep the agreement on foot bjr extending the time sixty days at a time. We have, therefore, proposed an additional proviso to tile decree to carry out this view. We hope that it will he acceded to hy the counsel for the complainants and those representing the re­construction scheme. We do not wish to dic­tate these terms to the parties who propose to purchase, hut suggest that, in our judgment, the interest of all parties would he. subserved by an arrangement of this sort. (The counsel for the complainants here suggested that it was very desirable, if the plan of reconstruc­tion should be generally adopted, to avoid any sale at all, and proposing to extend the time for other bondholders to come to an' arrange­ment, to the 1st of September, the court adopted that modification, and announced that the decree would be made accordingly, unless very forcible objections to it should be presented at to-morrow’s session of the court.)</p>
                <p id="b29-3" pgmap="29">Counsel for Ketebum &amp; Moran having ap­plied for a rehearing, the court denied the ap­plication. Counsel for Ketchum &amp; Moran then applied for the allowance of an appeal, and also to fix the amount of the appeal bond at $10,001). On this application the court, aft­er consideration, delivered the following opin­ion, fixing the bond at $100,000.</p>
                <author id="b29-4" pgmap="29">BRADLEY, Circuit Justice.</author>
                <p id="AF" pgmap="29">An appeal be­ing granted and allowed in these cases from the decree rendered therein on the 15th day of June, 1ST7, the question is raised as to the amount of the appeal bond to be given by the appellants, they being the plaintiffs in the second and third suits, and defendant^ in the first. The decree appealed from sus­tained the claim of Alexander Duncan, as holder of certain first mortgage coupons to the amount of over $500,000 to come in pari passu with the first mortgage bondholders, and directs a foreclosure of the first mort­gage and a sale of the mortgaged property to pay the bonds secured thereby, and also certain other bonds given for interest, amounting in the aggregate to about ten mil­lions of dollars. Purchasers are, by the de­cree, allowed to pay the purchase money in bonds and coupons to the extent of their pro­portionate interest as bondholders in the whole amount of first mortgage bonds. About four-fifths of the bondholders have agreed to and subscribed a scheme for reor­ganizing the company and purchasing the road. The court has allowed the remaining bondholders until the 1st of' September to join in said scheme. A portion of the bond­holders, holding less than one-tenth of the entire mortgage interest, are dissatisfied with the decree, and promote the appeal.</p>
                <p id="b29-5" pgmap="29">The property being in the hands of a re­ceiver, and not producing much, if any, more than the expenses and necessary repairs of the road, the bondholders to whom the prop­erty or its proceeds really belongs, will be kept out of possession for two or three years by the intervention of the appeal. This de­lay in obtaining possession of the property or its proceeds we regard as calculated greatly to injure them. By having immediate pos­session they could make the necessary im­provements and connections required for making the property much more remunera­tive, and could manage it much more to their advantage generally than a receiver can do. Or, if the property were immediately sold, they would be in possession of the interest of the purchase money, of which they will now be deprived for two or three years by the appeal. In our judgment, therefore, an appeal bond for one hundred thousand dol­lars is very moderate in amount.</p>
                <p id="b29-8" pgmap="29">The appellants contend that on the princi­ples of the decision of the supreme court in the case of Jerome v. McCarter, 21 Wall. [88 U. S.] 17, a bond for one hundred thousand dollars is greatly in excess of what should be required. They insist that, in contempla­tion of law, possession by a receiver is equal­ly beneficial to those who are interested in the property, as possession by the parties themselves. Whilst this may be the case with regard to dead property, or even real estate generally, we think it is not so where the property, like a railroad, is perishable in its character, and has to be managed, work­ed, repaired and taken care of, in order to preserve it. We think that the owner is a better manager than a trustee or receiver, who is hampered and restrained in his man­agement, and cannot take advantage of all those means and opportunities which the owner could do for rendering the property most profitable and productive. On these grounds, we think that the damage sustain­ed by the delay will be much more than the mere costs and expenses of the suit, and that the actual loss and injury to the owner, or in this case, the bondholders, may be tak­en into consideration by the court in fixing the amount of the bond, and that loss and damage, we think, will not be less than the amount we have required.</p>
                <p id="b29-9" pgmap="29">The most forcible difficulty which presents itself to our minds is the measure of dam­ages which would be applicable in a suit on the bond. Would it be admissible for the plaintiffs to show a loss to the bondholders by reason of advantages lost for the cause above referred to? Of this there may be a question. But our opinion is, on the whole, that such a damage would be the subject of a recovery. If damages are really sustain­ed, there seems no good reason why they should not be recovered.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="27" ORDERLABEL="25" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00014_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00014_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00014_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_27.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00014_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="28" ORDERLABEL="26" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00014_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00014_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00014_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_28.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00014_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="29" ORDERLABEL="27" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00015_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00015_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00015_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_29.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00015_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AF" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_29.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00015_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_29.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00015_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b29-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_29.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00015_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b29-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_29.15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00015_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b29-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_29.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00015_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b29-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_29.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00015_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_29.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00015_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b29-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_29.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00015_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AkE" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_28.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00014_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_28.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00014_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_28.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00014_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b27-12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_27.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00014_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b27-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_27.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00014_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b27-11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_27.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00014_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b27-15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_27.19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00014_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b28-12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_28.15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00014_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_29.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00015_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b28-11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_28.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00014_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b28-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_28.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00014_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b28-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_28.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00014_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AvH" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_27.15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00014_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_27.16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00014_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b28-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_28.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00014_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b27-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_27.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00014_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
