<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044049817315_0152" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="C.C.S.D. Ohio" jurisdiction="United States">United States Circuit Court for the Southern District of Ohio</court>
          <name abbreviation="Jacobs v. Hamilton County">JACOBS v. HAMILTON COUNTY</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 7,161</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">13 F. Cas. 276</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">4 Fish. Pat. Cas. 81; 1 Bond, 500</citation>
          <decisiondate>1862-01</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-10T00:25:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:27:33Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:41:26Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00139_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="846001e2c3546832208805332b5ffaa9" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="75702">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00139_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00140_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="455ac2b27e03c60e34e324549c6de3a5" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="106440">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00140_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00140_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="e3d700fc10d2f671e91ad5853c4dbe57" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="103398">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00140_1.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00139_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="7a4fcf6b35314e87dc9ca1fa595a6f4d" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2882140">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00139_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00140_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="d70f57cff6bcdeb529edae6391e747d3" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3675175">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00140_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00140_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="30e1387c3cbb6d94018b331aaf7287a6" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3671230">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00140_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00139_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="71c600e372458c5d39396893daceef88" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="148232">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00139_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00140_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="060d869964b469938678527f0550b4d0" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="227631">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00140_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00140_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="e25ee55c0e373a1f3fada90e7daa3887" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="218788">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00140_1.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0152" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="278" firstpage="276">
              <court pgmap="278" id="Af0a">Circuit Court, S. D. Ohio.</court>
              <docketnumber pgmap="278" id="b278-16">Case No. 7,161.</docketnumber>
              <citation pgmap="278" id="b278-18">[4 Fish. Pat. Cas. 81; 1 Bond, 500.] <footnotemark>1</footnotemark>
              </citation>
              <parties pgmap="278" id="b278-17">JACOBS v. HAMILTON COUNTY.</parties>
              <decisiondate pgmap="278" id="At_X">Jan., 1862.</decisiondate>
              <attorneys pgmap="279" id="b279-3">George M. Lee and S. S. Fisher, for plain­tiff.</attorneys>
              <attorneys pgmap="279" id="b279-4">W. S. Scarborough and E. A. Ferguson, for defendants.</attorneys>
              <footnote label="1">
                <p pgmap="278" id="b278-30">1 [Reported by Samuel S. Fisher, Esq., and by Lewis H. Bond.. Esq., and here compiled and reprinted by permission.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author pgmap="279" id="b279-5">LEAVITT, District Judge.</author>
                <p pgmap="279" id="AhZ">This is an ac­tion on the case against the board of com­missioners of Hamilton county for an al­leged infringement of the plaintiff’s exclusive right to certain improvements in the con­struction of jails, secured to him by -a patent granted by the United States.</p>
                <p pgmap="279" id="b279-6">The declaration is in the usual form, aver­ring that the defendants “unlawfully and un­justly, against the will of said plaintiff and without his leave or license,” made certain prisons in imitation of the plaintiff’s inven­tion, and in violation of his exclusive right under his patent, for which he claims a large sum in damages. To this declaration the defendants have filed a general demurrer, which presents the question now before the court</p>
                <p pgmap="279" id="b279-7">There can be no controversy as to the na­ture of the claim against the defendants as asserted in the declaration. It is a claim against the commissioners of Hamilton coun­ty, as a body corporate under the laws of Ohio, for an alleged act of malfeasance com­mitted by them in their corporate character. It is equally clear that, if damages are re­covered for the wrongful act charged, they can only be paid out of a fund raised, or to be raised, by taxation on the property of the people of the county.</p>
                <p pgmap="279" id="b279-8">It is not denied by the counsel for the de­fendants that- corporations created by law, enjoying special franchises conferred for the benefit of its members, as well as for the public good, are liable for acts of misfea­sance, malfeasance, or nonfeasance, if in­juries result to others from such acts. But it is insisted that, under the laws of Ohio, the board of commissioners of a county is not such a corporation, and is not liable in an action sounding in tort.</p>
                <p pgmap="279" id="b279-9">It is clear this question must be decided by a reference to the statutes of Ohio, creat­ing a board of commissioners in every county of the state, and defining their powers and duties. Unless the legislative power of the state, either by express enactment, or by clear implication, has imposed a liability on' the people of a county to respond to an in­jured' party for damages sustained by the wrongful acts of the commissioners, it does not exist, and can not be enforced. Now, it is undoubtedly true that the laws of Ohio have imposed it as a duty on the commission­ers of every county to provide a court-house and jail, and such other buildings as are needful for the due administration of jus­tice or other specified purposes. But we look in vain for any provision in those laws authorizing the commissioners to do a wrong­ful act, and pledging the property or the funds of the county to respond in damages for such act.</p>
                <p pgmap="279" id="b279-12">But the question involvéd in this case has been settled by the supreme court of Ohio, and the decision of that court is authorita­tive on this court It involves a construc­tion of the statutes of Ohio, relating to the powers and duties of county commissioners, and by the long-settled rule of the supreme court of the United States, scrupulously fol­lowed by the lower courts of the Union, such a decision, even if against the views and opinions of those courts, will constitute a rule of decision for them.</p>
                <p pgmap="279" id="b279-13">The case of the Commissioners of Hamil­ton Co. v. Mighels, 7 Ohio St 109, is de­cisive of the case before this court. In that case Mighels brought suit against the com­missioners, alleging, in substance, that in the progress of the construction of the coun­ty court-house, a certain opening or hole in the stairway leading from the first to the second story of the building was negligently suffered to remain without any guard or pro­tection, and that the plaintiff, in pursuit of his lawful business, fell into it, thereby sus­taining serious bodily injuries for which he claimed compensation.</p>
                <p pgmap="279(276) 280(32)" id="b279-14">In deciding that case the court, after an extended review of the legislation of the state as to the powers and duties of the board of county commissioners, were brought unanimously to the conclusion that they were not liable to the suit of the plaintiff, so far as he claimed damages from the county, for the alleged wrongful acts of the commis­sioners. The court held that, although the statute conferred on the commissioners the power of suing and being sued, which is a capacity or attribute- of a corporation, the board was only a quasi corporation; and that its power to sue, and its liability to suit, must be controlled and limited by the terms of the statute prescribing in what cases such power and liability existed. And as the power to sue and liability to suit were limited to cases of contract, the stat­ute could not by implication be extended to the case of a tort. The court say: “It is worthy of notice that this statutory enumera­tion of the matters in respect to which the board of commissioners may sue, is confined to matters of contract. As to all actions, or subject matter- of actions sounding in tort, the statute is silent.” And in the closing paragraph of the opinion of the court on the point in question, the court says: “We con­clude, therefore, whether we look solely to the language of our statute and apply to it those principles of construction which seem to be indicated by the narrow range of the objects and purposes of the county organiza­tion, or are governed by the light to be de­rived from analogous cases elsewhere de­termined, that if this action can be main­tained at all, a foundation for it must be •found elsewhere than in the provisions of our statute.”</p>
                <p pgmap="280" id="b280-3">The case referred to must be viewed as decisive of the question raised on this de­murrer. It can make no difference in the principle of the two cases, that in the case before the supreme court of Ohio, the tort charged, and for which it was sought to make the board of county commissioners li­able in their official capacity, was an act of nonfeasance, while in this it • is an act of misfeasance. The principle involved is pre­cisely analogous, whether the cause of action alleged is the wrongful omission to perform a duty, or a positive act of misfeasance. In either case there is no law by which the peo­ple of a county are responsible to the in­jured party for an injury sustained by the tort The right to recover in either case must rest on an express statutory provision. There can be no pretense of any such right in virtue of the common law. This proposi­tion is beyond all doubt in an action for the infringement of a patent right granted under the laws of the United States. The patent itself, with all the privileges which it con­fers, is the creature of the statute; and, it is clear, there can be no remedy for a vio­lation of a patent, except as it is conferred by the statute.</p>
                <p pgmap="280" id="b280-4">I am not able to see the force of the argu­ment, urged by plaintiff’s counsel, that he may be without a remedy for his alleged wrong, unless this action can be sustained against the board of commissioners. It is urged that the grant to the plaintiff secures to him the exclusive right to make, use, and vend the patented improvement, without .any exception or reservation. Hence, it is in­sisted, if any person or corporation can vio­late it with impunity, the patentee suffers a wrong without the possibility of a redress. To this it may be replied, that the tax-pay­ers of the county, being the parties alone in­terested, and virtually the defendants in the action, have had no agency in the commis­sion of the alleged wrong. They have nei­ther violated the plaintiff’s rights, nor have they authorized the commissioners, as their agents, to do so. There would be no justice, therefore, in holding that their funds, con­tributed in the form of taxes, should be ap­plied to the payment of damages for an act not authorized by them, and which has no sanction in the laws of the state.</p>
                <p pgmap="280" id="b280-5">But the plaintiff is not without remedy if there has been an infringement of the plain­tiff’s patent, as alleged by him. The fact alleged in the declaration is that the injury to the plaintiff consisted in the unlawful use, by the defendants, of certain improve­ments in the construction of iron prisons, embraced in the patent. Now, the court will take notice, that, by the statute of Ohio, the county commissioners can authorize the erec­tion of buildings for the use of the county only by contract. As a necessity, therefore, there must be a contractor, who obligates himself to do the work according to a pro­posed plan or specification, for a fixed com­pensation. There can be no question, that if the contractor, in the fulfillment of his ob­ligation, violates the patent right of another, he is answerable for the infringement He can not defend himself against the claim of the patentee by asserting that he committed the wrong under a contract with the coun­ty commissioners. It was his own folly to have imposed on himself such an obligation, and he alone is responsible for the injury which another may sustain as the conse­quence. If he had foreknowledge that the work he had bound himself to perform in­volved an infringement of a patent right, it was his business to have procured a license for the use of the improvement; and, failing to do so, he takes on himself the responsibil­ity of a violation of the patent If he en­tered into the contract in ignorance of the fact that the work he had agreed to do would violate a patent right, he is not, there­fore, protected from liability. This fact may have a bearing on the question of the amount of damages to be recovered, but does not destroy the right of action by the injured party. And it is no answer to this view of the subject, that cases may occur in which the patentee may fail in the enforcement of his just rights by the insolvency or irrespon­sibility of the contractor. This is an inci­dent often connected with cases of legal lia­bility, which can have no influence upon the application of known and settled legal prin­ciples. Such a result may be a great mis­fortune to a losing party, but can not fur­nish a reason for casting responsibility up­on another party, not legally chargeable with it</p>
                <p pgmap="280" id="b280-8">The question whether the commissioners are liable, personally and individually, for the infringement charged in the plaintiff’s declaration, is not before the court for its decision, and has received no consideration.</p>
                <p pgmap="280" id="b280-9">Upon the whole, the demurrer must be sustained.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="278" ORDERLABEL="276" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00139_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00139_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00139_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_278.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00139_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="279" ORDERLABEL="277" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00140_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00140_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00140_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_279.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00140_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="280" ORDERLABEL="278" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00140_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00140_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00140_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_280.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00140_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b280-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0152"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_280.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00140_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_280.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00140_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b280-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0152"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_280.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00140_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b280-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0152"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_280.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00140_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b279-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0152"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_279.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00140_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b280-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0152"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_280.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00140_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b278-30" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0152"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_278.35" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00139_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b278-16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0152"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_278.19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00139_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b280-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0152"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_280.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00140_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b278-18" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0152"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_278.21" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00139_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b279-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0152"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_279.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00140_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b279-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0152"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_279.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00140_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b278-17" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0152"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_278.20" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00139_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b279-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0152"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_279.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00140_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="At_X" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0152"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_278.23" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00139_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b279-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0152"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_279.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00140_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_279.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00140_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AhZ" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0152"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_279.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00140_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_279.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00140_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Af0a" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0152"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_278.22" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00139_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b279-13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0152"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_279.16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00140_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b279-12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0152"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_279.15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00140_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b279-14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0152"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_279.17" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00140_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_280.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00140_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b279-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0152"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_279.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00140_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b279-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0152"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_279.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00140_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
