<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044046873683_0013" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="S.D.N.Y." jurisdiction="United States">United States District Court for the Southern District of New York</court>
          <name abbreviation="In re Dunham">In re DUNHAM et al.</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 4,143</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">8 F. Cas. 33</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">2 Ben. 488; 2 N. B. R. 17 (Quarto, 9); 1 Am. Law T. Rep. Bankr. 89</citation>
          <decisiondate>1868-07</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-12T19:40:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-26T10:42:09Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-26T10:56:33Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00018_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="46462e2207f48e0fb0a61eefcecf85e6" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="51880">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00018_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00018_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="4d09547afe8bbc7599f6387a8d0b9e63" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="113530">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00018_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00019_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="f4fa08dd4def4a1b035f2580bcf0c58d" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="79996">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00019_0.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00018_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="ca3182cf25515cf05157fc4b34d8d91d" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2912505">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00018_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00018_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="617d15354b1138f4b44787ac2fe27471" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3768408">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00018_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00019_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="4d9b524dea23690a7907766a1529c84f" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3610607">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044046873683_00019_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00018_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="4de4de8dff9f08d8cf6f96f2234d664c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="110779">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00018_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00018_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="ad85368641bad23c147f868a2d27d931" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="250296">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00018_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00019_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="87a3dd4be08efb39c810f95833967344" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="169934">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044046873683_redacted_ALTO_00019_0.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0013" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="35" firstpage="33">
              <court id="b35-21" pgmap="35">District Court, S. D. New York.</court>
              <docketnumber id="b35-17" pgmap="35">Case No. 4,143.</docketnumber>
              <citation id="b35-19" pgmap="35">[2 Ben. 488;<footnotemark>1</footnotemark> 2 N. B. R. 17 (Quarto, 9); 1 Am. Law T. Rep. Bankr. 89.]</citation>
              <parties id="b35-18" pgmap="35">In re DUNHAM et al.</parties>
              <decisiondate id="AAX" pgmap="35">July, 1868.</decisiondate>
              <attorneys id="b35-28" pgmap="35">Thomas McGovern, for petitioning credit­ors.</attorneys>
              <attorneys id="b35-29" pgmap="35">L. J. Lansing, for respondents.</attorneys>
              <footnote label="1">
                <p id="b35-30" pgmap="35">1 [Reported by Robert D. Benedict, Esq., and here reprinted by permission.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author id="b36-2" pgmap="36">BLATCHFORD, District Judge.</author>
                <p id="AjA" pgmap="36">The peti­tion in this case alleges two acts of bank­ruptcy: (1.) That the debtors, on or about the first of November, 1867, being possessed of certain estate, property, rights, or credits, to wit, a stock of millinery goods, consisting of feathers, flowers, and numerous other ar­ticles, together with the lease, fixtures, and furniture of the premises known as number 684 Canal street, in the city of New York, made a sale, conveyance, or transfer of the same to one Robert Orr, of said city, with intent to delay, hinder, and defraud the creditors of the said debtors; (2.) That the debtors, on or about the-day of January, 1868, being bankrupt or insolvent, made to the said Robert Orr an assignment, convey­ance, or transfer of certain property, rights, and credits, to wit, the book accounts, claims, demands, and debts due or to become due to the said debtors, with intent to give a prefer­ence to said Robert Orr, he being or claiming to be a creditor of the said debtors, or with the intent, by such disposition of their prop­erty, to defeat, delay, or hinder the operation of the bankruptcy act.</p>
                <p id="b36-5" pgmap="36">The debtors have denied the acts of bank­ruptcy sot forth in the petition, and testi­mony has been taken on the issues thus raised.</p>
                <p id="b36-6" pgmap="36">An objection is taken on the part of the debtors, that, as no replication has been filed by the petitioners to the answer of the debt­ors, the answer must be taken as true, and the proceedings must be dismissed. The an­swer is merely the form of denial contained in form No. (51, and states that the debtors deny that they have committed the acts of bank­ruptcy set forth in the petition, and aver that they should not be declared bankrupt for any cause in the petition alleged. Such an answer sufficiently raises an issue as to the acts of bankruptcy alleged in the petition. It amounts to the general issue, and no rep­lication is necessary. The objection is. there­fore, overruled.</p>
                <p id="b36-7" pgmap="36">The first act of bankruptcy alleged is found­ed on that clause of the thirty-ninth section of the act which provides, that if a debtor shall make a sale, conveyance, or transfer of his estate, property, rights or credits, with intent to delay, defraud, or hinder his credit­ors. ho shall be deemed to have committed an act of bankruptcy. It is not an element of this act of bankruptcy that the debtor shall be, at the time of committing it, bank­rupt or insolvent, or be contemplating bank­ruptcy or insolvency, nor is any allegation to that effect made in the petition, in connec­tion with the first alleged act of bankruptcy.</p>
                <p id="b36-8" pgmap="36(613) 37(106)">The testimony in support of the first act of bankruptcy alleged shows that the debtors, on the first of November, 1S07, executed and delivered to Robert Orr a chattel mortgage on “six bunches of flowers, and all other the stock in trade, fixtures, lease, and furniture, and all other goods and chattels mentioned” in a schedule annexed to the mortgage, and 'then “in the store and premises No. 364 Canal street, in the city of New York” (the schedule specifying the lease of the premises, and sundry flowers, straw goods, feathers, and the fixtures and furniture in the store), to se-­ciu-e the payment of the sum of five thou­sand dollars on demand, with,interest there­on from the date of the mortgage to the time of payment, bfeing (as the mortgage states) “the amount of my promissory note bearing even date herewith, this mortgage being given as collateral security thereto.” This mort­gage was filed on the 26th day of November, 1867, in the proper office to make it a valid mortgage under the laws of New York, in the absence of an actual and continued change of possession of the mortgaged- property. The evidence shows, that the debtors com­menced business in January, 1867, and failed the last of December, 1867; that the mort­gage was given at the suggestion of Robert Orr, to secure a debt of $5,000 due by the debt­ors to Robert Orr, and evidenced by a note or notes of the debtors for that amount, held by Robert Orr; that the value of the mort­gaged property, at the time the mortgage was given, was between 82,000 and $3,000; that the mortgage covered all the property of the debtors, except their book accounts; and that the debtors continued business, and remained in possession of the mortgaged property, aft­er the mortgage was given, until the 2d of January, 1868, when Robert Orr foreclosed the mortgage, and a sale was had of the mortgaged property. It is not shown affirma­tively that the debtors were insolvent at any time prior to the last of December, when they failed. Under these circumstances, al­though the mortgage was not given for a present consideration, within the provision of section fourteen of the act, still it was a mortgage on personal property of the debt­ors, held by the creditor, Robert Orr, for se­curing the payment of a debt owing to him from the bankrupts, and thus within the sav­ing clause of section twenty of the act; and, it not being alleged in the petition, or shown by the evidence, that the mortgage was given when the debtors were bankrupt or insolvent, or contemplated bankruptcy or insolvency, it cannot, although it was made with the intent to give a preference to Robert Orr as a creditor, be held to be within any of the inhibitions of the thirty-ninth section of the act. or to have been made with intent to “delay, defraud, or hinder” the creditors of the mortgagors, with­in the meaning of those terms as used in that section. There is nothing to impeach the bona fides of the debt due to Robert Orr, and, to hold that these debtors, when not bankrupt or insolvent, or contemplating bank­ruptcy or insolvency, had no right to secure that debt by a chattel mortgage so long as they owed other debts, and that the giving of such mortgage is to be taken as evidence of an intent to delay, defraud, or hinder the creditors of the mortgagors, and is to be 10-­garded as forbidden by the thirty-ninth sec­tion of the act, would render invalid all chat­tel mortgages by solvent debtors. There cer­tainly was no intent to delay, defraud, or hinder Robert Orr as a creditor. The inhibi­tion is against the hindering, delaying, or de­frauding by the debtor of “his creditors,” that is, all his creditors, as a body, generally. The only inhibition against giving a prefer­ence to a creditor by a mortgage is found in a subsequent clause in the thirty-ninth sec­tion, which is confined to the case where the •debtor so giving the preference is bankrupt or insolvent, or is contemplating bankruptcy or insolvency. The first act of bankruptcy al­leged i£, therefore, not sustained.</p>
                <p id="b37-3" pgmap="37">■ As to the second alleged act of bankruptcy, the only evidence to sustain it is an instru­ment in writing, signed by the debtors, dated December 2Sth, 1SG7, purporting to transfer to Robert Orr, in order to secure the indebt­edness of the debtors to him, sundry accounts ¿against sundry persons named in the transfer, and amounting to $2,593.98. This instrument has no internal revenue stamp upon it. It ■ought to have had upon it a stamp of at least five cents, as an agreement or contract, under Schedule B following section 170 of the in­ternal revenue act of June 30th, 1804, as amended. By section 15S of that act, every instrument not stamped according to law is declared to be invalid and of no effect. Not •only did the petitioning creditors, on the hear­ing, claim that this instrument was void for want of the proper stamp, but the debtors also insisted that it was void for the same reason. It was and is void for that reason, and the second alleged act of bankruptcy is, therefore, unsustained by proof.</p>
                <p id="b37-4" pgmap="37">The proceedings are, therefore, dismissed, ■with costs to the respondents.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="35" ORDERLABEL="33" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00018_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00018_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00018_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_35.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00018_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="36" ORDERLABEL="34" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00018_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00018_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00018_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_36.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00018_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="37" ORDERLABEL="35" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00019_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00019_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00019_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_37.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00019_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b36-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0013"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_36.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00018_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b35-17" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0013"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_35.23" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00018_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b35-19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0013"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_35.25" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00018_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b35-18" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0013"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_35.24" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00018_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b36-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0013"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_36.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00018_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b35-28" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0013"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_35.34" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00018_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b35-29" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0013"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_35.35" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00018_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b36-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0013"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_36.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00018_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_36.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00018_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_37.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00019_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AjA" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0013"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_36.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00018_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_36.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00018_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b36-2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0013"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_36.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00018_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b35-21" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0013"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_35.26" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00018_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b35-30" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0013"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_35.36" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00018_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AAX" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0013"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_35.27" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00018_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b37-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0013"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_37.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00019_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b37-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0013"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_37.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00019_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b36-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0013"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_36.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00018_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
