<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044049817315_0294" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="C.C.S.D.N.Y." jurisdiction="United States">United States Circuit Court for the Southern District of New York</court>
          <name abbreviation="The Jesse Williamson, Jr.">The JESSE WILLIAMSON, JR. The BLANCHE PAGE and The JAMES A. BURDEN</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 7,296</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">13 F. Cas. 566</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">17 Blatchf. 106</citation>
          <decisiondate>1879-08-28</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-10T00:25:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:27:33Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:41:28Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00284_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="1c584abf504a1b7876fc03cfceb98c59" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="88186">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00284_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00285_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="bdc7da6d476d082ef4e35b7a52eb2aec" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="6724">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00285_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00285_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="aecb63bb44dd53a3c8ab567568fb4537" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="7774">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00285_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00286_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="eedfe1a1d9b382308dc554c461892a7c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="7034">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00286_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00286_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="9a3097bfaed59960bd7b7ff3bfaac173" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="6570">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00286_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00287_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="221b9c4033998d4ffc25f7f31fbb3976" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="62048">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00287_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00287_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="f08e2cef22eebc1dc40f314bd592c5f7" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="97244">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00287_1.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00284_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="0c9233b3f4672b035600b2bccb5ecdad" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3350790">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00284_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00285_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="864d695e36c95a21fa3e11dd63ce4b7e" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="1096171">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00285_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00285_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="e23c127d79dd29c490679117035559e1" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="968036">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00285_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00286_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="2611af5824cd42a8d6258173af0bd1f5" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="1039607">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00286_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00286_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="825423b4955aca44f6ad253d449d00af" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="977328">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00286_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00287_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="d3a1bcf0fbbfb9b9652782d282f5cfd3" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2529133">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00287_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00287_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="55db0c5fe0e2a366fc14df7d1aaf5bf4" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3476369">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00287_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00284_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="797fd7de3ed439ab26b467ebe0feff6a" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="198187">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00284_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00285_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="42f85099a162063f7272f67984bde80a" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="1920">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00285_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00285_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="c66c642326dab873d813da740841deae" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2018">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00285_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00286_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="e5a02c35c6f459f9fd3b0dffca77b390" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="1997">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00286_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00286_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="ffc8ed9e010aa14bb1b6f5cf2798a7f8" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2020">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00286_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00287_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="8df5a19351b0415bd38e136c88173872" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="139235">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00287_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00287_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="6f23f67e4f08fc61a700352b1ddd2269" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="220057">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00287_1.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0294" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="572" firstpage="566">
              <court pgmap="568" id="b568-20">Circuit Court, S. D. New York.</court>
              <docketnumber pgmap="568" id="b568-15">Case No. 7,296.</docketnumber>
              <citation pgmap="568" id="b568-19">[17 Blatchf. 106.] <footnotemark>1</footnotemark>
              </citation>
              <parties pgmap="568" id="b568-16">The JESSE WILLIAMSON, JR. The BLANCHE PAGE and The JAMES A. BURDEN.</parties>
              <decisiondate pgmap="568" id="A9Y">Aug. 28, 1879.</decisiondate>
              <attorneys pgmap="573" id="b573-4">George A. Black, for schooner..</attorneys>
              <attorneys pgmap="573" id="b573-5">Robert D. Benedict, for tug and barge.</attorneys>
              <footnote label="1">
                <p pgmap="568" id="b568-24">1 [Reported by Hon. Samuel Blatehford. Cir­cuit Judge, and here reprinted by permission.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author pgmap="573" id="b573-6">WAITE, Circuit Justice.</author>
                <p pgmap="573" id="A1a">The only ques­tion which I think it necessary to consider in this case is, whether the tug carried “two bright white mast-head lights vertically,” or their legal equivalent. Rule 4 of the statu­tory navigation rules (Rev. St. § 4233), pro­vides, that “steam vessels, when towing other vessels, shall carry two bright white mast­head lights vertically, in addition to their side lights, so as to distinguish them from other steam vessels. Each of these mast­head lights shall be of the same character and construction as the mast-head lights prescrib­ed by rule 3;” that is to say (rule 3) “a bright white light, of such a character as to be visible on a dark night, with a clear at­mosphere, at a distance of at least five miles, and so constructed as to show a uniform and unbroken light over an arc of the horizon of twenty points of the compass, and so fixed as to show the light ten points on each side of the vessel, namely, from right ahead to two points abaft the beam on either side.” Such a light must be car­ried at the foremast-head of an ocean-going steamer, or a steamer carrying sail. Steam vessels not carrying sail and navigating bays, lakes, rivers, .or other inland waters, are re­quired, by rule 7, to carry, in addition to their colored lights, “a central range of two white lights, the after light being carried at an elevation of at least fifteen feet above the light at the head of the vessel. The head light shall be so constructed as to show a good light through twenty points of the compass, namely, from right ahead to two points abaft the beam on either side of the vessel, and the after light so as to show all around the horizon.”</p>
                <p pgmap="573" id="b573-8">This tug could not carry a light at her mast-head, for she had no mast, but she could carry two bright white lights vertical­ly, of a character to be visible five miles away on a dark night, with a clear atmosphere, and so constructed as to show a uniform and unbroken light ahead, and from ten points on one side to ten points on the other of the vessel. This would be a light of the character and construction which ocean steamers, and steamers carrying sail, are required to have at the foremast-head. I deem it unnecessary to decide, in this case, whether, if two lights of a power equal to what is required for mast-head lights, are suspended vertically on the flag-staff at the stern of a tug. in such a manner as to show a uniform and unbroken light ahead over an are of twenty points of the compass, they would be the legal equivalent of two mast­head lights; for, I am clear, that, unless there are two lights of that power and ef­ficiency, carried vertically somewhere on the vessel, rule 4 is not complied with.</p>
                <p pgmap="573(71) 574(359)" id="b573-9">That such lights were not carried on this tug is very apparent from the evidence. It is conceded, that ordinary globe lanterns only were used. The mate, when acting as lookout on the schooner, must have been vigilant. He saw. first, the green light, then the white at the head, then the red, and then the green shut in, as the tug approached and rounded the buoy, and put herself on her course down the river. The head light was seen, while those from the flagstaff were not. The presumption is, that the light ahead was such as was required by rule 7, and, therefore, of the same character and con­struction as that prescribed by rule 3, for the mast-head. As that light was seen, the •conclusion is irresistible, that the stern lights were not of the. same power, or were not so placed as to present the view which the law required. This, under the circumstances, is not only a fault in law, but a fault in fact. The schooner, while, to my mind, in all par­ticulars vigilant, was not actually informed that she was to meet a tow, until the hull •of the barge loomed up out of the darkness, immediately ahead, almost at the very mo­ment of the collision. Clearly, if the cir­cumstances are such as to make it proper for a tug to keep a tow four to five hundred feet away from her, she should be specially careful not only to notify approaching ves­sels that a tow is following, but, as near as may be, where it is. A sailing vessel must hold her course while a steamer is keeping •out of her way in passing, but this obligation continues only so long as the steamer is passing. The sailing vessel should, there­fore, be told where the steamer is. and as, for the purposes of this rule, the tug and her tow are to be considered as one vessel, and that the tug, it is necessary' that the requir­ed information should extend to both tow and tug. In the day time, the tug may as­sume that both will be seen from the sail' vessel, and act accordingly; but, at night, and in the dark, this is impossible, and, consequently, the law has supplied a sys­tem of arbitrary signals, intended to make up for the loss of vision by day. If these signals are omitted, and the sailing vessel comes into collision for want of them, the loss must fall on the tug, where the fault lies.</p>
                <p pgmap="574" id="b574-4">There can be no doubt that this collision was caused, in part, at least, by a want of proper towing lights. Had the schooner been told, in the appropriate way, of the approach and presence of a tug and tow, she would have watched as well for the tow as the tug, and, if she had found the tow driven out of its course, as this one undoubtedly was, by force of the wind, or otherwise, she would have taken some measures herself to prevent a collision. From the manner in which this schooner was navigated, I have no doubt whatever, if she had known that a tow was following the barge, the loss never would have happened. She was keeping up as close to Throgg’s Point as she could, iu order to take advantage of the wind and save herself from going off too much to leeward, when she got by. There was room enough for her to keep off; and there can be no reasonable doubt that she would have done so had she known it was necessary. Not knowing of the barge, she held her course, as she certainly had the right to do, with the information she had. In this I recognize fully the rule, that, while a tug must keep herself, as well as her tow, out of the way. a sailing vessel is not per­mitted to run down a tow, if it gets beyond the control of a tug, and she can, with rea­sonable effort, avoid it.</p>
                <p pgmap="574" id="A4mm">Holding, as I do, that a tug, while towing in inland waters, must exhibit vertically two bright white lights, of equal power with, the mast-head lights of sea-going steamers, so fixed as to present a uniform and unbroken light right ahead and ten points on either side, and that this tug was in.fault in this particular, it is unnecessary to inquire whether rule 9 of the board of supervising inspectors has the force of law, as a rule of navigation. By section 4412 of the Revised Statutes, the board has the right to “estab­lish such regulations, to be observed by all steam vessels, in passing each other, as they shall, from time to time, deem necessary for safety,” and, by section 4403. these rules, when approved by the secretary of the treas­ury, “have the force of law.” The statu­tory navigation rules (section 4233, Rev. St., rule S), prescribe lights for sailing vessels while being towed, but omit any provision for canal-boats, barges, &amp;c., when towed, as is customary in rivers and other inland wa­ters. This is an important omission, and, if there is really any doubt as to the power of the board to bind towing steamers by this rule, in passing sailing vessels, the necessary legislation to remedy the defect should at once be obtained. The absolute necessity there is for some such rule must certainly be acknowledged, if tugs are permitted to sep­arate themselves long distances from their tows, and then make up the tow of any size or form they please.</p>
                <p pgmap="574" id="b574-7">I see no reason for disturbing the report of the commissioner as to the amount of dam­ages. A decree may' be prepared, dismissing the libel of Starin. with costs in both courts, and in favor of Sise and others, for §1,07(1 7-1. and interest on §G27 SO from November 20th, 1S73. and on §440 8S from November 20th. 1S77, at six per cent., that being the amount allowed by the commissioner.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="568" ORDERLABEL="566" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00284_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00284_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00284_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_568.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00284_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="569" ORDERLABEL="567" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00285_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00285_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00285_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_569.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00285_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="570" ORDERLABEL="568" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00285_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00285_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00285_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_570.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00285_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="571" ORDERLABEL="569" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00286_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00286_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00286_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_571.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00286_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="572" ORDERLABEL="570" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00286_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00286_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00286_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_572.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00286_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="573" ORDERLABEL="571" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00287_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00287_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00287_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_573.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00287_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="574" ORDERLABEL="572" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00287_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00287_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00287_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_574.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00287_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b568-19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0294"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_568.25" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00284_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b573-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0294"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_573.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00287_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b573-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0294"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_573.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00287_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b573-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0294"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_573.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00287_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b568-16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0294"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_568.23" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00284_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_568.24" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00284_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b568-15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0294"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_568.22" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00284_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b568-20" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0294"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_568.26" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00284_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="A4mm" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0294"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_574.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00287_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b574-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0294"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_574.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00287_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_574.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00287_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b574-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0294"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_574.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00287_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="A9Y" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0294"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_568.27" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00284_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b568-24" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0294"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_568.31" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00284_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="A1a" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0294"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_573.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00287_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_573.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00287_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_573.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00287_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b573-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0294"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_573.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00287_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b573-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0294"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_573.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00287_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_574.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00287_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
