<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044049817315_0256" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="C.C.D.R.I." jurisdiction="United States">United States Circuit Court for the District of Rhode Island</court>
          <name abbreviation="Jencks v. Coleman">JENCKS v. COLEMAN</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 7,258</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">13 F. Cas. 442</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">2 Sumn. 221</citation>
          <decisiondate>1835-06</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-10T00:25:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:27:33Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:41:27Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00222_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="8895b6b5c0fb5f213ee0c976dbbaa6f1" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="61334">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00222_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00223_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="b8a773355b4aab05344264135404980c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="47146">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00223_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00223_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="e6001d4b82110e7c1200467e8714f1f7" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="113136">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00223_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00224_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="0fc0cd6894ab772a87f9ec5e5ba6a9cb" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="34858">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00224_0.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00222_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="d8f7f7078a44bb7dd852808815c15150" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2548846">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00222_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00223_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="394611c35a41b1ce159c30a979a868d4" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2131296">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00223_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00223_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="9aa36d69a02c0e6dadf7691d02f0804c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3799294">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00223_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00224_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="ec8afdd9d49da092b56c3d2c8d229e73" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2197598">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00224_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00222_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="c8edcba7a415885f9ce73412de541068" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="134455">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00222_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00223_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="f9d7ef921c1d7e96d1939d9fd62f444f" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="87493">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00223_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00223_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="17e904eb9298326a78ebe0fe58bd3157" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="242854">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00223_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00224_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="886f2e31e0c011ed92422103a53c6387" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="67142">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00224_0.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0256" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="445" firstpage="442">
              <court pgmap="444" id="AMh2">Circuit Court, D. Rhode Island.</court>
              <docketnumber pgmap="444" id="b444-5">Case No. 7,258.</docketnumber>
              <citation pgmap="444" id="AZO">[2 Sumn. 221.] <footnotemark>1</footnotemark>
              </citation>
              <parties pgmap="444" id="Ahm7">JENCKS v. COLEMAN.</parties>
              <decisiondate pgmap="444" id="AyYL">June Term, 1835.</decisiondate>
              <attorneys pgmap="445" id="b445-3">R. W. Greene and Daniel Webster, for plaintiff.</attorneys>
              <attorneys pgmap="445" id="b445-4">Rivers &amp; Whipple, for defendants.</attorneys>
              <footnote label="1">
                <p pgmap="444" id="b444-22">1 [Reported by Charles Sumner, Esq.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author pgmap="445" id="b445-9">STORY, Circuit Justice</author>
                <p pgmap="445" id="AOA">(charging jury). There is no doubt, that this steamboat is a common-carrier of passengers for hire; and, therefore, the defendant,- as commander, was bound to take the plaintiff as a passenger on board, if he had suitable accommodations, and there was no reasonable objection to the character or conduct of the plaintiff. The question, then, really resolves itself into the mere consideration, whether there was, in the present case, upon the facts, a reason­able ground for the refusal. The right of passengers to a passage on board of a steam­boat is not an unlimited right. But it is subject to such reasonable regulations as the proprietors may prescribe, for the due ac­commodation of passengers and for the due arrangements of their business. The pro­prietors have not' only this right, but the farther right to consult and provide for their own interests in the management of such boats, as a common incident to their right of property. They are not bound to admit pas­sengers on board, who refuse to obey the reasonable regulations of the boat, or who are guilty of gross and vulgar habits of con­duct; or who make disturbances on board; or whose characters are doubtful or dissolute or suspicious; and, a fortiori, whose char­acters are unequivocally bad. Nor are they bound to admit passengers on board, whose object it is to interfere with the interests or patronage of the proprietors, so as to make the business less lucrative to them. While, therefore, I agree, that steamboat proprie­tors, holding themselves out as common-car­riers, are bound to receive passengers on board under ordinary circumstances, I at the same time insist, that they may refuse to receive them, if there be a reasonable objec­tion. And as passengers are bound to obey the orders and regulations of the proprietors, unless they are oppressive and grossly un­reasonable, whoever goes on board, under or­dinary circumstances, impliedly contracts to obey such regulations: and may justly be refused a passage, if he wilfully resists or violates them.</p>
                <p pgmap="446" id="b446-2">Now, what- are the circumstances of the present case? Jencks (the plaintiff) was, at the time, the known agent of the Tremont line of stage coaches. The proprietors of the Benjamin Franklin had, as he well knew, entered into a contract with the owners of another line (the Citizens’ Stage Coach Com­pany) to bring passengers from Boston to Providence, and to carry passengers from Providence to Boston, in connection with and to meet the steamboats plying between New York and Providence, and belonging to the proprietors of the Franklin. Such a con­tract was important, if not indispensable, to secure uniformity, punctuality, and certainty in the carriage of passengers on both routes; and might be material to the interests of the proprietors of those steamboats. Jencks had been in the habit of coming on board these steamboats at Providence, and going therein to Newport; and commonly of coming on board at Newport, and going to Providence, avowedly for the purpose of soliciting pas­sengers for the Tremont line, and thus inter­fering with the patronage intended to be secured to the Citizens’ line by the arrange­ments made with the steamboat proprietors. He had the fullest notice, that the steamboat proprietors had forbidden any person to come on board for such purposes, as incompatible with their interests. At the time when he came on board, as in the declaration men­tioned, there was every reason to presume, that he was on board for his ordinary pur­poses as agent. It has been said, that the proprietors had no right to inquire into his intent or motives. I cannot admit that point I think, that the proprietors had a right to inquire into such intent and motives; and to act upon the reasonable presumptions, which arose in regard to them. Suppose a known or suspected thief were to come on board; would they not have a right to refuse him a passage? Might they not justly act upon the presumption, that his object was unlawful? Suppose a person were to come on board, who was habitually drunk, and gross in his behavior, and obscene in his lan­guage, so as to be a public annoyance; might not the proprietors refuse to allow him a passage? I think they might, upon the just presumption of what his conduct would be.</p>
                <p pgmap="446" id="b446-3">It has been said by the learned counsel for the plaintiff, that Jencks was going from Providence to Newport, and not coming back; and that in going down, there would, from the very nature of the object, be no solicita­tion of passengers. That does not necessar­ily follow; for he might be engaged in mak­ing preliminary engagements for the return of some of them back again. But, supposing there were no such solicitations, actual or intended, I do not think the case is essen­tially changed. I think, that the proprietors of the steamboats were not bound to take a passenger from Providence to Newport, whose object was, as a stationed agent of the Tremont line, thereby to acquire facili­ties, to enable him successfully to interfere with the interests of these proprietors, or to do them an injury in their business. Let us take the case of a ferryman. Is he bound to carry a passenger across a ferry, whose object it is to commit a trespass upon his lands? A case, still more strongly in point, and which, in my judgment, completely meets the present, is that of an innkeeper. Suppose passengers are accustomed to break­fast. or dine, or sup at his house; and an agent is employed by a rival house, at the distance of a few miles, to decoy the pas­sengers away, the moment they arrive at the inn; is the innkeeper bound to entertain and lodge such agent, and thereby enable him to accomplish the very objects of his mission, to the injury or ruin of his own interests? I think not. It has been also said, that the steamboat proprietors are bound to carry passengers only between Providence and New York, and not to transport them to Bos­ton. Be it so, that they are not absolutely bound. Yet they have a right to make a con­tract for this latter purpose, if they choose; and especially if it will facilitate the trans­portation of passengers, and increase the patronage of their steamboats. I do not say, that they have a right to act oppressively in such cases. But, certainly, they may in good faith make such contracts, to promote their own, as well as the public interests.</p>
                <p pgmap="446" id="b446-6">The only real question, then, in the pres­ent case is, whether the conduct of the steam­boat proprietors, has been reasonable and bond fide. They have entered into a con­tract, with the Citizens’ line of coaches, to carry all their passengers to and from Bos­ton. Is this contract reasonable in itself; and not designed to create an oppressive and mischievous monopoly? There is no pre-­tence to say, that any passenger in the steam­boat is bound to go to or from Boston in the Citizens’ line. He may act as he pleases. It has been said by the learned counsel for the plaintiff, that free competition is best for the public. But that is not the question here. Men may reasonably differ from each other on that point. Neither is the question here, whether the contract with the Citizens’ line was indispensable, or absolutely necessary, in order to insure the carriage of the passen­gers to and from Boston. But the true ques­tion is, whether the contract is reasonable and proper in itself, and entered into with good faith, and not for the purpose of an op­pressive monopoly. If the jury find the con­tract to be reasonable and proper in itself, and not oppressive, and they believe the pur­pose of Jencks in going on board was to ac­complish the objects of his agency, and in violation of the reasonable regulations of the steamboat proprietors, then their verdict ought to be for the defendant; otherwise, to be for the plaintiff.</p>
                <p pgmap="446(15) 447(84)" id="b446-7">Mr. Webster, for plaintiff, then requested the court to charge that the jury must be satisfied, that this agreement was necessary or clearly expedient for the public interest, and the interest of the proprietors of the boats, or otherwise the captain of the boat could not enforce it, by refusing the plaintiff a passage; — or, that the defendant must show, that the substantial interest of the proprie­tors, or of the public, required an arrange­ment, such as that they entered into, in or­der to justify their refusal to carry the plain­tiff for the cause assigned.</p>
                <p pgmap="447" id="b447-3">THE COURT refused to give instruction in the manner and form as prayed; but did in­struct the jury, that it is not necessaiy for the defendant to prove, that the contract in the case was necessary to accomplish the ob­jects therein stated; but it is sufficient, if it was entered into by the steamboat pro­prietors bonfi fide and purely for the purpose of their own interest, and the accommoda­tion of the public, from their belief of its necessity, or its utility. If the jury should be of opinion, that under all the circum­stances of the case, it was a reasonable con­tract. and the exclusion of the plaintiff was a reasonable and proper regulation, to carry it into effect on the part of the steamboat proprietors, then their verdict ought to be in favor of the defendant; .otherwise, in favor of the plaintiff. Verdict for defendant.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="444" ORDERLABEL="442" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00222_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00222_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00222_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_444.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00222_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="445" ORDERLABEL="443" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00223_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00223_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00223_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_445.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00223_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="446" ORDERLABEL="444" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00223_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00223_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00223_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_446.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00223_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="447" ORDERLABEL="445" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00224_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00224_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00224_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_447.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00224_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b445-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0256"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_445.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00223_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Ahm7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0256"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_444.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00222_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b445-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0256"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_445.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00223_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b445-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0256"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_445.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00223_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b446-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0256"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_446.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00223_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_447.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00224_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b446-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0256"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_446.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00223_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AZO" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0256"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_444.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00222_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b444-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0256"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_444.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00222_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b446-2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0256"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_446.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00223_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AMh2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0256"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_444.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00222_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b444-22" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0256"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_444.25" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00222_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b446-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0256"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_446.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00223_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_446.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00223_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AOA" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0256"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_445.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00223_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_445.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00223_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AyYL" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0256"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_444.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00222_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_444.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00222_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b447-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0256"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_447.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00224_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
