<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044049817315_0480" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="C.C.D. Md." jurisdiction="United States">United States Circuit Court for the District of Maryland</court>
          <name abbreviation="Jones v. McMurray">JONES v. McMURRAY</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 7,479</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">13 F. Cas. 989</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">3 Ban. &amp; A. 130; 2 Hughes, 527; 13 O. G. 6</citation>
          <decisiondate>1877-10-31</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-10T00:25:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:27:33Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:41:29Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00496_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="2be43ba1c103c457f4c4d1a7ed09f3a4" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="48404">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00496_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00496_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="83975bc2bc7489f2fd64dd947a858d74" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="113124">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00496_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00497_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="2f0e2309496e29094182d19ec2301e25" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="26784">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00497_0.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00496_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="6d970153055c2442a6e3f0e1421fc4cb" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2317566">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00496_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00496_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="75574b051508196c28fd57c19ce25d2d" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3797314">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00496_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00497_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="8a4f346dbc96508ede503714a3e83711" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="1835679">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00497_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00496_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="104a729dd90a22393b0d634ea0db2efe" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="101694">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00496_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00496_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="7004d43d15f7b55362f2205157c7a5a0" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="246884">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00496_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00497_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="32aa6b3862deba51f157fe26558f21f6" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="46250">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00497_0.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0480" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="991" firstpage="989">
              <court pgmap="991" id="b991-16">Circuit Court, D. Maryland.</court>
              <docketnumber pgmap="991" id="b991-12">Case No. 7,479.</docketnumber>
              <citation pgmap="991" id="b991-14">[3 Ban. &amp; A. 130; 2 Hughes, 527; 13 O. G. 6;</citation>
              <parties pgmap="991" id="b991-13">JONES v. McMURRAY.</parties>
              <decisiondate pgmap="991" id="Ajlq">Oct. 31, 1877.</decisiondate>
              <judges pgmap="992" id="b992-2">Before BOND, Circuit Judge, and GILES, District Judge.</judges>
              <attorneys pgmap="991" id="b991-22">Benjamin F. Butler, Archibald Stirling, Jr.. David Fowler, and T. C. Mattocks, for com­plainant.</attorneys>
              <attorneys pgmap="991" id="b991-23">E. R. Dickerson, Charles C. Beaman, I. Nevitt Steele, Sr., and J. H. Howard, for re­spondent.</attorneys>
              <p pgmap="991" id="AxJ8">Merw. Pat. Inv. 156.] <footnotemark>1</footnotemark>
              </p>
              <footnote label="1">
                <p pgmap="991" id="b991-24">1 [Reported by Hubert A. Banning. Esq., and Henry Arden. Esq., and by Hon. Robert W. Hughes. District Judge, and here compiled and reprinted by permission. The syllabus and opin­ion are from 3 Ban. &amp; A. 130, and the state­ment is from 2 Hughes. 527.]</p>
              </footnote>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author pgmap="992" id="b992-3">BOND, Circuit Judge.</author>
                <p pgmap="992" id="A1UD">As this cause in­volves large pecuniarj- interests, and is also of much importance to the public at large, the court has very carefully read and con­sidered the whole testimony, which was so voluminous that counsel could only refer to it in , their arguments, or but partially read it.</p>
                <p pgmap="992" id="b992-4">This bill is preferred by complainant to es­tablish the validity of four letters patent re­lating to inventions for the canning and pres­ervation of green com. The first patent. No. 34,92S, dated April 8th, 18G2, and its reissue, No. 7067, dated April 18th, 1876, cover the in­vented product, while the second patent. No. 33,271, dated May 13th, 1862, and its reissue, No. 7061, dated April ISth, 1876, relate to the process of making the product.</p>
                <p pgmap="992" id="b992-5">The supreme court of the United States, in 'the case of Sewall v. Jones, 91 U. S. 171, de­termined that the original patents above named were void for want of novelty, and this court is saved the labor of investigating their validity. But the complainant here claims that .though the original patents were declared invalid by the supreme court, he is entitled to the relief he asks, because he has surrendered patents Nos. 34,92S and 35,gi4, and the commissioner of patents has reis­sued the same to him because the originals were invalid merely “by reason of a defective or insufficient specification” under section 4916, Rev. St. U. S. He, therefore, so far as this part of his case is concerned, relies upon the reissued patents, Nos. 7061 and 7067, which relate to both the process of canning and to the product of the canning process.</p>
                <p pgmap="992" id="b992-6">While we are of the opinion that the deci­sion of the supreme court in Sewall v. Jones is much broader that the complainant ad­mits, and that it goes to the whole invention there and now claimed by Jones in the pat­ents we are here considering, and that it determined that both the process and product now claimed by Jones was the invention of Appert, in France, and Durand, in England, more than sixty years ago, and held that Jones’ patents were void for want of novelty, and not merely invalid for want of a proper specification and description of Jones’ claim, nevertheless, since the commissioner of pat­ents has reissued the patents to Jones, we would give him the benefit of them could we discover in what respect they differed essen­tially or substantially from the originals, which the supreme court has decided were not novel. There is no essential difference, however, between the process described in patent 35,274 and its reissue, No. 7061, The first recites that after some difficulty found in preserving the green corn without drying, the inventor, removed the com from the cob and boiled it, but that this process, the corn being broken by removal from the cob, dis­solved the juices and made the corn insipid, and that, finally, he removed the corn from the cob, packed the kernels in cans, hermet­ically sealing them, and boiled them until the com was cooked. The supreme court, in Jones and Sewall, say this is not new.</p>
                <p pgmap="992" id="b992-9">In his reissued patent the complainant states that he takes tender green com and scrapes it from the cob so as not to detach the inner ends of the kernel, which, with the juices and softer parts of the corn, he cooks together and then proceeds with the old pro­cess of Appert for cooking and sealing. He claims as his invention the process described of separating and obtaining the nutritious and edible parts of the com and boiling them in a liquid composed wholly or mainly of their own juices.</p>
                <p pgmap="992" id="b992-10">No one ever cut green corn from a cob who did not accomplish exactly what this claim describes, and no one under the process de­scribed in patent 35,274. which required the com to be removed from the cob, could so remove it without breaking the kernels, and when he proceeded to cook it in a can, as the patent required, he would find necessarily more or less of the juices with it. The reis­sue does not claim that the juices only should be used in the cooking.</p>
                <p pgmap="992" id="b992-11">The process described in the reissue is sub­stantially that of the original patent. But if we admit there is something new and patent­able in the reissued patent which was not in the original, the patent is void, because it is not for the same invention as the original. It may be the subject of a new patent, but can­not be a reissue of an old one, and that, too, of an old one which has been adjudged inval­id by the supreme court for the want of nov­elty. But the fact is that Jones, as far bade as May, 1862, had applied for and obtained a patent, No. 35,346, which described the cut­ting off the com from the cob in very much the same words as he does in the reissued patent, 70uj.. This patent, No. 35,346, Judge Clifford held, and rightly, to be substantially the same with No. 35,274, now under consid­eration. It cannot, therefore, be claimed that the reissued patent contains anything which the original one did not, and the original, says the supreme court, is void for the want of novelty.</p>
                <p pgmap="992" id="b992-12">The two remaining patents which the bill alleges the defendants have infringed are Nos. 51,379 and 54,170, which describe a curved knife for the removal of the com fiom the cob. We are of the opinion that these two patents are also void for thewant of novelty. The knife described in the first pat­ent is simply a curved knife provided with a gauge for the purpose of removing corn from a cob. The second patent makes the gauge adjustable. This, we think, the defendant has shown to be old. The knife differs nothing in principle and little in construc­tion from the knife known as the “spoke­shave,” or from the repairing knife of Adam Oot. (Defendant's Record, 606.')</p>
                <p pgmap="992(17) 993(30)" id="b992-13">But even if we admit the validity of these patents we have looked in vain for any proof that the defendant has infringed them by using complainant’s knife. On the con­trary, the complainant’s proof (Record, 25, 42) shows that the defendant used a different knife entirely.</p>
                <p pgmap="993" id="b993-3">For these reasons, and without considering other, and, as we think, equally fatal objec­tions to the complainant’s ease, we think the complainant’s bill should be dismissed with costs, and will sign a decree to that effect.</p>
                <p pgmap="993" id="b993-4">[The following is the decree: “This cause having been submitted for final hearing, and the counsel for the respective parties having been heard, and the bill, answer, exhimts, and evidence having been read and consider­ed, it is this 31st day of October, 1S77, ad­judged, ordered, and decreed that the bill of complaint filed in this cause be and the same is hereby dismissed, with costs to the defendant”] <footnotemark>4</footnotemark>
                </p>
                <footnote label="4">
                  <p pgmap="993" id="b993-19">4 [From 2 Hughes. 527.]</p>
                </footnote>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="991" ORDERLABEL="989" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00496_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00496_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00496_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_991.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00496_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="992" ORDERLABEL="990" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00496_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00496_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00496_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_992.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00496_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="993" ORDERLABEL="991" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00497_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00497_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00497_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_993.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00497_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b991-16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0480"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_991.19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00496_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b991-14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0480"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_991.17" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00496_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b991-12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0480"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_991.15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00496_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b991-13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0480"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_991.16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00496_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Ajlq" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0480"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_991.20" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00496_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b992-2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0480"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_992.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00496_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="A1UD" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0480"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_992.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00496_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_992.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00496_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b991-24" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0480"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_991.28" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00496_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b991-23" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0480"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_991.27" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00496_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b991-22" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0480"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_991.26" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00496_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b993-19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0480"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_993.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00497_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b992-13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0480"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_992.16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00496_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_993.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00497_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b992-12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0480"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_992.15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00496_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b992-11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0480"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_992.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00496_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b992-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0480"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_992.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00496_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AxJ8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0480"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_991.18" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00496_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b992-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0480"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_992.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00496_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b992-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0480"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_992.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00496_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b992-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0480"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_992.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00496_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b992-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0480"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_992.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00496_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_992.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00496_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b993-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0480"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_993.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00497_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b993-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0480"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_993.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00497_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b992-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0480"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_992.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00496_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
