<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044049817315_0513" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="D. Mass." jurisdiction="United States">United States District Court for the District of Massachusetts</court>
          <name abbreviation="In re Jordan">In re JORDAN et al.</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 7,512</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">13 F. Cas. 1077</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">19 Int. Rev. Rec. 20</citation>
          <decisiondate>1873</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-10T00:25:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:27:33Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:41:29Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00540_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="0fb80bd30cda0d40ca965ac082e023e2" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="94930">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00540_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00540_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="713d2d26aca0744765c4a7fbc2371bf8" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="103020">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00540_1.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00540_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="4a4f4c14c8808c93500bda9ab5cc4cbd" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3446851">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00540_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00540_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="8bd21c9aec88fc930c475c7907681a80" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3591149">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00540_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00540_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="368fff625e3bc70461e44e237906865d" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="206617">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00540_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00540_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="4be8c71820cac71ec7236736a9ad48b2" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="226831">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00540_1.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0513" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="1078" firstpage="1077">
              <court pgmap="1079" id="b1079-7">District Court, D. Massachusetts.</court>
              <docketnumber pgmap="1079" id="b1079-4">Case No. 7,512.</docketnumber>
              <citation pgmap="1079" id="b1079-6">[19 Int. Rev. Rec. 20.]</citation>
              <parties pgmap="1079" id="b1079-5">In re JORDAN et al.</parties>
              <decisiondate pgmap="1079" id="AdVq">1873.</decisiondate>
              <attorneys pgmap="1079" id="b1079-14">B. F. Brooks and F. TV. Hurd, for peti­tioners.</attorneys>
              <attorneys pgmap="1079" id="b1079-15">G. P. Sanger and E. L. Barney, for the government.</attorneys>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author pgmap="1079" id="b1079-16">LOWELL, District Judge.</author>
                <p pgmap="1079(781) 1080(455)" id="AJDu">The act of March 2, 1867, § 2, requires the district judge, whenever it shall he made to appear to his satisfaction, by complaint and affi­davit, that any fraud on the revenue has been committed, in the importation or entry of merchandise at any port within his dis­trict, to issue his warrant requiring the mar­shal, by himself or deputy, to enter any place or premises where any invoices, books, or papers are deposited relating to the mer­chandise in respect to which such fraud is alleged to have been committed, and to take possession of such books or papers and produce them before said judge; and any invoices, books, or papers so seized shall be subject to the order of said judge, who shall allow the examination of the same by the collector of customs of the port into which the alleged fraudulent importations have been made, or by any officer duly author­ized by said collector. And such invoices, books, or papers may be retained by said judge as long as in his opinion the retention thereof may be necessary. But no warrant shall be issued unless the complainant shall set forth the character of the' fraud alleged, the nature of the same, and the importation in respect to which it was committed, and the papers to be seized. This act having been pronounced constitutional by the cir­cuit court for this circuit, I have endeavored to enforce it in accordance with what I con­sider its true intent. Stockwell v. U. S. [Case No. 13,400]. I require that the evi­dence shall be such as to satisfy the mind of a reasonable person that one or more speci­fied frauds have actually been committed in the importation or entry of merchandise in­to some port within this district. When this is established by an affidavit which shows sufficient grounds for the belief of the affi-­ant, I consider it my duty to issue my war­rant. I have heretofore ruled (and that ruling is for the purposes of this case ad­mitted by the defendants to be sound) that from the nature of the case it is impossible that the papers to be seized should be so specified that the marshal can identify them without examining their contents. For this reason the warrant in this case, as in others, identifies the papers by a reference to the particular importations mentioned in the complaint and recapitulated in the warrant. It follows that the marshal must usually make inspection of papers not called for be­fore he can be sure that he has obtained those which he may properly bring before the judge. The objection now taken is that in making what is admitted to be a neces­sary separation between the papers which ought to be taken and those which there is no right to take, the marshal or the court ought not to employ the very officers who. by the statute, are to examine the papers after they are duly seized and returned. I consider this objection to be well taken. It is the intent of the statute that only those papers should be examined by the collector, or other officers of the revenue, acting under him, which may lawfully be taken, and those are only such as relate to the specified importations. The separation, which, in a case of this kind, .it is admitted somebody hab a right to make, ought to be made be­fore the examination by the revenue officers begins. In this case the marshal acted in good faith and without objection, and, in­deed, with the acquiescence of the defend­ants, in taking certain books and papers and bringing them into court before the separa­tion was completed. As the marshal had appointed for his deputies the very same gentlemen who were appointed by the col­lector to examine the papers, it was of no particular consequence to the defendants in which capacity they acted in separating the papers. The marshal then made return that he had brought certain papers before the judge, and the usual order was passed that they be examined by the designated officers. The defendants then applied for permission to be present at the examination, and the court granted leave for them to attend by counsel while the separation was going .on. This work has been begun and is not very far from completion. If this were an ordi­nary case, in which the course of proceeding was well understood, I should probably con­sider that the defendants were estopped at this late period, after so much had been done with their consent, to object to the matter being finished as it was begun. But these cases being rare and without any very well settled course of practice, I ought not to hold any very rigid rule in respect to laches. It has now occurred to the defend­ants that the officers of the revenue are in­terested parties, and that if they are per­mitted to inspect whatever papers the mar­shal has taken, though he may have taken them by consent, information may be ob­tained concerning matters not specified ei­ther in the complaint or in the warrant, and thus the safeguards of the statute be prac­tically lost to the defendants. It is argued on behalf of the government that the statute requires me to permit examination by the revenue officers of whatever papers the mar­shal may return as having been taken under his warrant. This is literally so; but the statute also requires that the marshal should take only specified papers, and I think it entirely clear that all the papers are subject to the order of the court, and if it is suggest­ed to the judge that there are papers brought into court which the warrant does not call for, it is his duty in some mode to ascertain whether.the fact is so, and if it be so, to return to the defendants all such papers. It is further argued that no harm has been done as yet, and none is likely to occur if the examination proceeds as before. This I am happy to believe is true. We are for­tunate in having officers upon whose in­tegrity no imputation has ever been cast. But the rights of the defendants do not de­pend upon the character of the officers, and it is the duty of the court to ascertain the papers which the revenue officers may in­spect before that inspection is permitted. It is said I once ruled that I could not interfere with the marshal in the execution of such a warrant. I think I did so rule in general terms. But if the question were to be raised, which it never yet has been, whether I could not veto the appointment of revenue officers as deputies to the marshal, in a case of this kind, it might, perhaps, be found that such a power is expressly conferred on the district judge by the judiciary act of 1789. As the task of separation is a somewhat delicate one, ánd that no imputation may seem to rest upon the persons who have ex­amined the books and papers thus far, I will myself finish the work in the presence of counsel on both sides, or at. least attempt to do so.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="1079" ORDERLABEL="1077" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00540_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00540_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00540_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_1079.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00540_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="1080" ORDERLABEL="1078" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00540_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00540_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00540_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_1080.15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00540_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1079-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0513"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1079.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00540_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1079-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0513"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1079.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00540_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1079-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0513"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1079.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00540_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1079-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0513"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1079.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00540_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AJDu" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0513"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1079.20" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00540_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1079.21" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00540_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1079.22" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00540_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1080.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00540_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1079-16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0513"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1079.19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00540_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AdVq" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0513"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1079.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00540_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1079-14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0513"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1079.17" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00540_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1079-15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0513"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1079.18" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00540_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
