<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="32044049817315_0536" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="S.D.N.Y." jurisdiction="United States">United States District Court for the Southern District of New York</court>
          <name abbreviation="The Joseph Cunard">The JOSEPH CUNARD</name>
          <docketnumber>Case No. 7,535</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">13 F. Cas. 1132</citation>
          <decisiondate>1845-04</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-12-10T00:25:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-04T14:09:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:27:33Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-04-25T05:41:30Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170308.post165</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00567_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="1ae43c58b39030dca33c1cf6c009197b" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="54404">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00567_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00568_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="531af6b441b469304dea18361a399618" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="70294">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00568_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00568_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="35275071fdebc2942cd998e36fd95918" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="101736">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00568_1.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00567_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="9dd7a750067198282eef7f2b04683939" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2527393">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00567_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00568_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="002a39280488f72d4dcbec8f1cf41c98" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2752435">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00568_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00568_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="243e6ea47f668f2f5f3dcc1ca952de40" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3613072">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/32044049817315_00568_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00567_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="1edcf9b20a796a4394c49d1dd4dfadf3" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="110473">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00567_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00568_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="f77ee5488d50857ea9457194320b97e6" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="152378">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00568_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00568_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="2a05b44f0d2eecc4cf03644292bbdae4" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="230964">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/32044049817315_redacted_ALTO_00568_1.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0536" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="1134" firstpage="1132">
              <court pgmap="1134" id="b1134-25">District Court, S. D. New York.</court>
              <docketnumber pgmap="1134" id="b1134-22">Case No. 7,535.</docketnumber>
              <parties pgmap="1134" id="b1134-23">The JOSEPH CUNARD.</parties>
              <decisiondate pgmap="1134" id="AQvF">April, 1845.</decisiondate>
              <attorneys pgmap="1135" id="b1135-7">L. Hoyt, for libellants.</attorneys>
              <attorneys pgmap="1135" id="b1135-8">F. It. Tillou, for claimant.</attorneys>
              <p pgmap="1134" id="b1134-24">[Olc. 120.] <footnotemark>1</footnotemark>
              </p>
              <footnote label="1">
                <p pgmap="1134" id="b1134-33">1 [Reported by Edward R. Olcott, Esq.J</p>
              </footnote>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author pgmap="1135" id="b1135-9">BETTS, District Judge.</author>
                <p pgmap="1135(623) 1136(77)" id="AoVC">The proofs pro­duced consisting principally of the charter-­party, the letter of instructions to the master, the correspondence and account stated between Davies and Challinor, the depositions of the master and of Davies himself, establish, in sub­stance, this case. That the vessel sailed from London March 1, 1813, under a charter to Challinor. engaging she should arrive at Mo­bile by the 10th of May, and there be loaded with cotton at the charge and expense of the charterer, but in other respects she was to be under the charge and directions' of the owners. She was consigned to John H. Da­vies, at Mobile. The master was specially instructed not to draw bills on the owners for expenses or disbursements of the ship, but was referred to their agents, Messrs. Pope &amp; Son, at Mobile, for supplies and ad­vances, if necessary. Davies was the agent of the charterer, and saw the charter-party before he made any advances to the master for the vessel, and also the letter of instruc­tions to the master before the bill of ex­change was drawn, and the bill was drawn by the master on the owners at the urgent instance of Davies. It is further shown, that the disbursements made by Davies were chief­ly for pressing the cotton, and transporting it by lighters from the shore to the vessel, and charges connected with his agency for the charterer in obtaining and shipping the cargo, there being out of the amount of the bill (£590, with exchange), only the sum of about $GG1.1G, which would seem to have any direct application to the necessities or serv­ice of the vessel, with the exception of a ques­tionable charge of $87.01 in jail fees, board, &amp;c., advanced in favor of sailors, and includ­ing $15 for medical attendance for one of them on shore. I can perceive no foundation under the special appointment of Davies as agent or broker for the charterer in procuring a cargo, and placing it on board, upon which he can raise a claim against the ship or own­ers for those services, although he may have acted with the concurrence of the master; and even if the owners could be made per­sonally liable for the charges, several of them are not of a nature to admit their being im­posed in invitum on the ship, and enforced in rem by an admiralty court. The ac­count charges $1.027.50 for compressing the cotton. This is mere shore business, per­formed in cotton presses on land, at the port or in the interior, as may be desired by the purchaser, and would probably be alike useful and important whether the transportation is to be on land or on ship­board, the only object being to fit it for more convenient carriage and stowage. Charges for advertising and posting ($10) and com­missions on procuring .freights ($338.80) on the employment of the charterer, and not that of the owner or master, cannot be re­garded demands or services attaching as liens to the vessel. It may be inferrable from the facts, that the freight was expected to be made by purchasing and shipping cot­ton for the charterer, but there is no higher reason for charging the vessel with commis­sions on such operation, than upon the pur­chase price of the cargo itself. Nor would the privilege be varied, if the shipment was solicited or procured by the agent from a third party for consignment to the owner. The service of the agent would be simply a mercantile one rendered on land, and bear­ing none of the qualities necessary to bring it under the seeurityship of the vessel. Fur­thermore, in this case, Davies was employed l&gt;y the charterer, and had direct notice that the owners had their own agent at the port to respond for the ship. The charge of $457.-­CO, for stevedores’ work, is only for labor at the wharf or moorings of the vessel, in stowing cargo, and is not distinguishable in character from charges of draymen or light-­ermen, who bring the cargo to the ship to be laden on board.</p>
                <p pgmap="1136" id="b1136-4">It has been decided in this court, that steve­dores cannot proceed by libel against a ves­sel for their services in loading or unloading her. The Amstel [Case No. 339]. And the charge of $481.17, for lighterage, would seem in principle to stand on the same footing. It is an employment outside of the vessel, not contributing to her capabilities or securi­ty in navigation or serviceable to her voy­age; there is no difference of principle, whether the cargo is brought to her side in the stream or placed near her on a wharf. The ship is responsible for disbursements necessary to equip and put her in a condition (by men, provisions, &amp;c) to perform her voy­age, but it would be giving a novel extension to the notion and range of tacit liens to sub­ject her also to all claims collateral and in­cidental to her despatch. A cargo is no more than an incident to a voyage, and in no sense necessary to enable the ship to perform one. Debts arising out of such collateral sendees or engagements may be chargeable upon the owner personally, as resting upon his im­plied contracts; but the ship is not neces­sarily pledged to their satisfaction more than for wages of the master, or other benefits to the mercantile adventure of the owner. In the same category the charge of $70 for com­missions, and $41 for insurance on the mas­ter’s draft, should be placed. There is no reason or equity for the latter charge against the owners. Their letter of instructions to the master shown to Davies, forbids the mas­ter drawing on them for necessities of the vessel, and referred him to an adequate re­source supplied by them for that purpose, in the port where the exj&gt;enses were to be in­curred. I am of opinion, therefore, that not over $763.80 of the amount claimed could be charged against the ship, had Davies been acting under direction of the master, or as agent of the owners; but under the facts in proof, he must be regarded the particular agent of the charterer, making advances on his credit, and relying on his personal re­sponsibility. This responsibility Davies had strengthened by obtaining an assignment of the bill of lading, freights, &amp;c., as collateral security. If these resources have failed him, there is nothing in the legal relation he bore to the ship or her owners, nor in the equity of his debt, which entitles him to claim that he acted as their agent, or that gave him a privilege upon the ship.</p>
                <p pgmap="1136" id="b1136-5">I do not enter into the question, whether taking the bill of exchange by Davies would operate as a waiver of an implied lien against the ship, because, in my opinion, no lien ac­crued to him out of his transactions in the case. The libellants cannot stand in a bet­ter condition than Davies, the drawee and endorsee of the bill; and as he had no claim or lien upon the ship for his demands, he could confer none upon the holder or his as­signees. He was apprised that the master was specially instructed by the owners not to draw bills for expenses, repairs, &amp;c., upon them. He knew, also, that the ship was chartered to Challinor, for whom he was agent. In such case it is clear that the own­ers would not be liable to Davies for any contracts of the master with him. Abb. Shipp. (Ed. 1829) 92 ; 3 Kent, Comm. 163. The master cannot even bind his owners for repairs, &amp;c., when it is known to the creditor that some other person has authority to man­age the business of the vessel in this particu­lar case. Philips v. Ledley [Case No. 11,-­096],</p>
                <p pgmap="1136" id="b1136-7">It is unnecessary to discuss the question, whether the assignment to the libellants by Davies carried with it his privilege of lien for his advances, because, as already stated in the opinion of the court, he was not en­titled to claim the security of the vessel for his demands. They can accordingly stand, in that respect, merely in his place, if they hold a full assignment of the original in-­debtment to him. But it is by no means a clear proposition in law, that a bill of ex­change, drawn to cover that debt, and en­dorsed by him to them, would operate as an assignment of the consideration for which the bill was drawn; and a full assignment of the collateral securities he held for the original claim will not, per se, transfer also the consideration on which the claim rested. But the point of formality or inaptness of the title set up by the libellants, or their ca­pacity to maintain this action, are not ma­terial points in the case. The judgment rests upon the broader ground that Davies ac­quired no right he could transfer to others, or exercise himself, against the vessel by action in rem. The libellants could not. therefore, as holders of the bill of exchange, or as­signees of Davies, set up an equity in their favor beyond their strict legal rights. Libel dismissed, with costs.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="1134" ORDERLABEL="1132" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00567_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00567_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00567_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_1134.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00567_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="1135" ORDERLABEL="1133" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00568_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00568_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00568_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_1135.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00568_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="1136" ORDERLABEL="1134" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00568_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00568_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00568_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_1136.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00568_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AoVC" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0536"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1135.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00568_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1135.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00568_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1135.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00568_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1136.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00568_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AQvF" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0536"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1134.31" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00567_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1135-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0536"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1135.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00568_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1135-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0536"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1135.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00568_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1135-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0536"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1135.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00568_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1136-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0536"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1136.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00568_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1136-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0536"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1136.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00568_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1136.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00568_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1136-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0536"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1136.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00568_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1134-22" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0536"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1134.27" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00567_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1134-23" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0536"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1134.28" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00567_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1134-33" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0536"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1134.39" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00567_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1134-24" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0536"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1134.29" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00567_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b1134-25" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0536"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_1134.30" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00567_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
